- Tonight on
"The Bachelorette"...
- We're gonna get weird.
Do you like it?
- You impress me.
- No, you impress me.
- Gabby's, hands down,
the coolest girlfriend
I ever had.
I love that I can just
be myself around you.
- Me too.
- Every moment I spend
with Rachel,
the connection is just there.
I love that feeling
of seeing you smile.
- My connections
are so much stronger
than I ever thought possible.
- I'll take any piece of you
any day.
- I feel so happy.
- I care about Rachel,
but I can't put
my initial feelings
for Gabby aside.
This is humiliating.
- Yeah.
- Humiliating.
Oh!
- There's Logan coming in.
That's just a huge wild card.
- Is Gabby questioning
her connections
with the rest of us?
- That's, like, what's kind of
going through my head.
- Actions carry weight,
and you can't do something
like that.
It's gonna cause a stir.
Oh.
- Oh.
- Whoa.
- I don't want
to do this anymore.
- It all starts right now.
- Waking up this morning,
I'm so excited.
We're sailing to another
beautiful city in Europe:
Bruges, Belgium.
I'm just excited to explore
a new country
with my group of guys.
I think, ever since we
started traveling,
we've all been
in really good spirits
and truly here to find love.
Thank you.
I just hope that we keep
kind of riding this high.
We are very much in the middle
of this journey,
and I'm developing
deep feelings
for these men already.
But as my connections
get deeper,
I never know who's
going to surprise me.
- Dude, look how beautiful
these towns look.
- I'm so excited
to be in Belgium.
I've never been,
and I'm really excited to try
some real Belgian chocolate.
There are canals,
little alleyways,
horse-drawn carriages,
and it's just so romantic.
It really is
out of a fairy tale.
Moving into this week,
I am excited for a fresh start.
The past couple weeks have
been really difficult for me
because I definitely feel
like there's been
a lot of rejection.
So I do want to put that
behind me.
I have a group date today,
and I feel really confident in
the guys that are here for me.
They step up when I ask them to.
I just only hope that this week,
they can continue
to show up for me.
- It was tough seeing Rachel
upset, you know,
over the past couple days.
You know, as a group,
we gotta make her feel good.
- I think it comes down
to all of us showing
how much we want to be here.
There's not one guy
around here that I don't think
is gonna do that.
- This has been a hard
couple weeks for Rachel,
and we all want her to smile
and enjoy her time,
and, like, I want those things
for her too.
Date card.
- But that doesn't change
what I feel,
which is I feel for Gabby.
And I'm just ping-ponging this
in my head constantly.
- Tino.
Zach.
Meatball.
Ethan.
Tyler.
Logan.
"How sweet it is
to be loved by you...
Love, Rachel."
- Usually, seeing your name
on a date card
is instant gratification, right?
But this one's kind of
mixed feelings for me.
But...
- Yeah.
It's nice to see your name
on the date card,
but you obviously kind of hope
that you were the one person
not on the date card.
But congrats to you, Aven.
Looks like you got
the one-on-one.
- Yeah. That's exciting.
- For this whole journey,
I've gotten to know Rachel
as this wonderful person,
but the worst thing I could do
is get to a point
where relationships
are at a more serious level
and then bring this up.
Before this group date
takes off,
I need to talk to Rachel.
I need to tell her I can't go,
and I need to tell her why.
I have no clue how she'll react,
but maybe she'll understand.
I'm praying she does.
Hi.
- Oh, hi.
- How are you?
- Good, how are you?
- Sorry for the surprise, but...
- Yeah.
- Uh, mind if I come in?
- Do you want to come in?
- Thank you, thank you.
I wanted to have a quick talk,
if you had some time.
- Yeah.
- How are you doing?
- I'm good.
How are you?
Um...
I've, like, never really
gotten a chance
to tell you that, like, uh...
Um...
like, how honored I am,
like, whenever you put
a rose on me.
- This feels really good
to hear you say.
- Yeah. Um...
But I feel like something's
kind of been holding me back
a little bit,
a feeling that I've kind of
been anchored down by a bit.
- Yeah.
- And like, at the beginning
of this journey,
first group date,
going over to your house,
you and I shared, like,
a real connection.
- Mm-hmm.
- And I also got to talk
with Gabby.
- Mm-hmm.
- And me and Gabby
also had a strong connection.
- Yeah.
- And at the end of the night,
I originally thought
that I was going
to receive a rose from Gabby.
- Okay.
- And it's been hard for me
moving forward
to kind of forget
about that connection.
And when I read
that date card today,
I felt that everyone else
on that card
was sure
that you were going to be
someone who they could end up
with at the end of this.
- Mm-hmm.
- Well, I still had reservations
and feelings for Gabby.
- Mm-hmm.
- And that being said, like,
I can't go today.
- Okay.
- And I'm going to have
to, like, step away from...
From pursuing things with you.
I look at myself in the mirror,
and I'm like, "I'm a fool."
Like, look at you.
- Uh-huh.
- I'm surprised
that you even gave me a chance
in the first place.
- Yeah.
I mean, you accepted
so many roses from me,
when the whole time,
you really didn't
even want to spend time?
- No.
- Like, I appreciate
you bringing this to me.
If that's where
your heart is, like,
I appreciate you telling me.
I just wish
it would have been earlier.
- It's also not something
that I've been sure of
until recently.
- Yeah.
Like...
of course,
the first thing I think
when this first popped
into my head
was like, "You're crazy.
Like, look at Rachel.
Look at who she is."
- You don't have
to explain that.
You don't have to keep going.
I got it.
You know,
I'm not trying to be mean.
I just... I get it.
- Okay.
- Obviously,
this is tough to hear,
and no one really
wants to hear this, so...
- Yeah
- Mm-hmm.
- Um... thank you.
- Yeah.
I really thought going this
far, he wouldn't have flipped.
Like, looking forward, like,
I was really hopeful that things
could pick up with Logan and I,
'cause I think he's, like,
a great guy.
I'm attracted to him.
Like, I did give him
the first group date rose,
and this whole time,
he was like,
"How do I tell Rachel
I don't even want to be here?"
Well, good luck.
I'll walk you out.
Everyone is leaving me.
It's just like, the rejection,
that just feels really awful,
and it almost feels like
I'm doing something wrong.
I don't know.
Something's clearly wrong
with me, but I don't know.
I mean, no one can sit here
and honestly tell me
I didn't fail.
It's just... this was
supposed to be, like,
my time to, like, find someone,
and everyone's rejected me
week after week after week.
There hasn't been one week
someone's stayed all week.
I just don't even know
why I'm here.
Everyone's that's not
is gonna leave at some point.
And I feel like now
is the perfect time,
so why don't they all
just leave?
Then at least I don't
have to say that I quit.
I don't wanna do this anymore.
- Dude.
- Wow.
We're in Bruges, baby.
Oh, it's so beautiful here.
I love this place already.
The smell of Belgian
chocolates and waffles,
the beautiful castles,
the beautiful horses
that we see.
Hi, horses.
- I just knocked it
out of the park
on a one-on-one in Paris
with Rachel last week.
Now it's time
to show that, like,
I can make her feel special
and on top of the world
on a group date.
- Yeah!
- Oh, they're in chocolate!
- I'm excited to see Rachel
and kind of enjoy the day
with her.
You know, see her laugh,
see her smile.
- Oh!
- Logan's not with us right now,
and I don't know why.
But one less guy does give me
more of an opportunity
to talk with Rachel,
and I can't wait
to spend more time with her.
I just don't know what to do.
My guys just, like, keep getting
the short end of the stick
constantly.
Like, I feel bad that they
have to keep dealing with this
week after week,
but I'm not ready right now
to just go on a group date
and act like
I don't feel like a huge loser.
- Wow.
- And, like,
the worst part about Logan
is, like, the whole time,
he was just seeing
how far he could get until
he could switch to Gabby.
Logan, how many weeks
were you gonna go
before you did this,
when you knew apparently
at that first group date?
Why did you accept my rose?
This is two weeks
before Hometowns,
this is happening.
Like, I should have
at least seven guys
who want to be here for me,
and I don't.
Like, I'm literally just, like,
such a failure
as a Bachelorette.
- Hey.
Can I come in and talk
with you for a second?
- Yeah.
- I'm so sorry.
- Thanks, Jess.
- Well...
- Talk to me. What's going on?
- I mean,
it seems like I thought
we would be past the point
of people changing their mind,
and we're not.
And it just doesn't seem
out of the realm of possibility
for it to continue to happen.
And not even just, like, Gabby,
but just for people
to change their mind about me.
- Mm.
- And it's just scary,
because it's like,
how could I not keep expecting
it to happen at this point?
- Yeah.
How is it affecting you?
Like, how are you now
towards the other men?
- I definitely feel like
I have walls going up,
and it's just unfair
to the guys who are here.
They have to keep
picking me back up
'cause I keep having, like,
these really bad days,
but I feel like I'm just, like,
getting dealt
really bad cards, like,
pretty much in a row,
so it's, like,
hard to keep having momentum.
I feel like I'm, like, failing
in the role as the Bachelorette.
- You cannot be the
perfect Bachelorette.
- Yeah.
- I wanted to be
the perfect Bachelor.
It's impossible,
Rachel, it's impossible,
all right?
We get put into situations
that we never could have
prepared for.
All we can do, all you can do,
is make the best decisions
in real time
using your intuition.
Even though you're going
through a storm right now,
the hope is for you
to fall in love with someone
who loves you back for you,
and they get down on one knee,
and that is still
totally in play.
Yeah.
It's just, like, hard.
Like, I really appreciate
everything you're saying.
I do, it's just...
It's tough right now to...
- I know.
- Like, I shouldn't
be feeling this sad.
- No, there's no playbook
for this thing.
- I know.
I wish there was.
- Me too.
I'd love to give you mine,
but all of our journeys
are totally different, right?
- I know.
I know.
- So, as you know,
the guys are in town.
- Yeah.
- There's supposed
to be a date today.
- Yeah.
- What do you want to do?
- I just want to do something...
Like, see her,
because that's why we're here.
- I can't wait to see Rachel.
I haven't seen her all day.
I figured I'd see her by now,
but I don't know
how much longer
we got to go here.
- What's up, guys?
- Hey.
How you doing?
- What's up?
- Jesse!
- How's it going, Jesse?
- Fellas, good to see you all.
- Good to see you.
- Welcome to Bruges.
I know you guys were excited
to see Rachel and not me,
but I did have to come here
to tell you that,
unfortunately,
Rachel has decided
to cancel today's date.
Some stuff went down,
and she doesn't feel like
she's in the right mind-set
to go on this group date
with you today in Bruges.
But it doesn't mean she doesn't
want to see you all.
So Rachel is going to see you
at tonight's after party.
So head on back to the ship
and get ready.
Rachel will see you there
tonight.
Gentlemen, again,
I'm very sorry.
See you in a bit.
- Damn.
- I'm feeling
really disappointed.
I want to enjoy these moments
with Rachel.
And, you know, every single day
I don't get a chance
to spend with her, you know,
those are memories
that I miss out on with her.
- Now we don't really even get
to, like, share this with her.
So let's just bring
our A-game tonight,
cheer her up, keep it
as low drama as we can.
I'm really bummed.
I just really wanted to be able
to experience Belgium
with Rachel, because we had
such an extraordinary time
in Paris.
And for anybody else
to bum her out
and it affect,
like, an experience
I can have with her,
I feel stripped
of a wonderful opportunity
with my future wife.
- It's very frustrating.
Just, like, we wanted to have
a really great week with her,
and this is not a great start.
So who knows what's
going to happen next?
- I just did the daunting task
of telling Rachel
that I've wanted
to pursue Gabby.
I feel terrible.
But I couldn't continue on
with the charade,
and now I have to tell Gabby.
The light
at the end of the tunnel
would be the off chance
that Gabby feels
the same thing I feel,
and I can stay.
It seems unlikely,
and I'm aware of that.
And if I end up going home,
it'll be for a good reason,
because I actually went after
what my heart wanted.
Hi.
- Hi.
- How are you?
- Good, how are you?
- Good. Um...
- Yeah. Come in.
- Yeah.
- I'm sure you're surprised
to see me.
- I am.
- Yeah.
Do you think we can sit down?
- Yeah, of course.
- Um...
- How's it going?
- It's going good.
I've actually been wanting
to talk to you for a while.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah.
- Mm-hmm.
- Um...
when I met you at your mansion,
like, I was like,
on fire for you
that first night,
and I was hopeful
that you would give me a rose.
- Yeah.
- And I got one from Rachel,
and we've had some great
moments...
- Yeah.
- But I've come back to, like,
thinking about you.
And it's something
that's gotten in the way.
- Yeah.
- Um...
So this morning, I had
a conversation with Rachel.
- Okay.
- And I told her
that, like, I needed
to step away from dating her.
- How... how did she take it?
- I think she understood,
but she was frustrated.
- Yeah.
- Which, like,
I would never blame her for.
And I know you guys
are so close.
- Yeah.
- And...
I'm not here to, like,
look for a response.
I'm not asking for an answer
or anything like that.
- Yeah.
- But I did want to say it.
- Yeah, no, I appreciate it,
and I feel like
I can just be straight up
with you.
- Yeah.
- But it was kind of...
You were pretty much
our only overlap,
you know,
like, in the beginning.
Like, you were the only one
that both of us
felt like we could comfortably
say, you know, "I'm into him."
And then that night
when you came over,
and you had kissed both of us,
and it sounded like
you and her had a really great
conversation,
I, like, completely backed away.
But that's when
I was like, dang.
Like, I, you know,
am very interested,
and it might not be
as easy for me
to let go of my feelings.
But we are on
our separate journeys now,
and I just want to check in
with Rachel,
but yeah.
- Absolutely.
I'm just glad
you got to, like, sit here
and, like, hear me out.
- Yeah, absolutely.
- Thank you.
- This, like, is my worst
nightmare, you know,
on the outside of things.
- Like, me being here.
- Yeah, you...
- I'm your worst nightmare.
- Yeah.
- Good, thank you.
Not really what I was
looking for, but...
- Right, but it's not you,
it's just I want to always,
always, always put
my friends first.
But... and I am, like, and I have
been interested in you.
It just... I was surprised
to see you, obviously.
I just kept looking at you.
- I wasn't sure if
you'd remember my name.
It was, like,
such a risk for me.
Yeah.
- You would, like,
tell me, like,
"Oh, I have fresh towels.
I'm good."
- Right.
Like, "Not today."
- Yeah.
Not interested.
But yeah,
I'm glad we got to talk.
It feels a lot better already,
just being honest.
- Yeah, totally.
- All right.
- I can walk you out.
- Okay.
I feel good about that.
After talking to her
for 20 seconds,
I realized why I was doing
all this, you know?
- Bye.
- But my future at this point
is completely unknown.
Now I'm moving
into this no man's land.
I'm not in Rachel's group
anymore,
and I'm not in Gabby's group.
I could be going home tomorrow.
I think the conversation
between Gabby and Rachel
will be a difficult one.
- Hi.
- But I would like to think
they both want
what's best for each other,
and maybe I'm part of that.
- What is going on?
- Did you hear? Do you know?
- Yeah. Yeah.
Well, he came to talk to me.
- Okay.
I get he's following his heart,
but I'm like,
how many roses
were you gonna take
until you were, like,
gonna jump?
Like, where was like, the line?
- Yeah.
- Like, was he genuinely
trying and then, like,
decided he couldn't,
or was it like,
"I just want to see
how far I can get"?
- Yeah.
- And that's, like,
where I was at,
and now, of course,
he had to do that
before the date...
- Yeah. I know, I hate that.
That was the first thing
I thought of, too,
and I can't imagine
having those feelings,
like, before a date.
But how did you feel
when you, like, went?
- I didn't go.
- There was no date?
- No.
I, like, couldn't,
'cause I asked these guys
to give me 100%
every single time.
I can't go in there being like,
"Oh, someone else left,"
and I feel like a failure.
- Yeah.
- It's, like,
"The Bachelorette."
'Cause it's like,
Logan just came in
and dumped me
for another Bachelorette.
Like, this is humiliating.
- Yeah.
- Humiliating.
And so, like, I'm gonna try
to go tonight,
but, like,
I just still don't feel great.
- Like, I would honestly feel
the same way.
- Yeah.
But, like, what do you...
How are you feeling?
'Cause, like, I want you to get
what you need out of this,
if that's something
you want to pursue.
- I don't ever want to put you
in a place
by, like, having to see him
or, you know...
- I don't want you to be
thinking about me so much
that you, like, if there...
You genuinely think
something could be there,
that you lose it.
- Yeah.
- You know what I mean?
- I think the only reason
I would agree
is to, like, explore it more.
- Mm-hmm.
- But, like, you don't deserve
feeling like these guys
aren't here for you,
because I see the way
they look at you,
and I know how crazy
they are about you,
and like,
I want you to see that.
- Yeah.
I appreciate that
the first thing you thought of
was to come to me,
and I love you.
- I love you. Mm.
- I think Gabby
is interested in Logan.
Okay, bye.
But I just don't think
Logan is trustworthy.
He strung me along for weeks,
and I just really
don't want that
to happen to Gabby in the future
and for her to feel
as hurt as I do right now.
At the end of the day,
I'm gonna support her
no matter what,
but I really hope
Gabby sends him home.
- I was really excited to spend
some time with Rachel.
That was some place
that I really wanted
to experience with her.
- Mm-hmm.
- And I didn't get a chance
to do that.
But, you know, going in tonight,
you just gotta make up
for lost time.
- Obviously, without Logan here,
there's some unanswered
questions, right?
So, you know, hopefully
she can address those
if she's comfortable.
You know, good news is
there is a rose on the table,
so now that there's
only five of us,
I think we can all get
some quality time with her.
- What we have to do is just
be there to listen to her,
and be there to support her.
- Anyone nervous?
- Yeah.
I just don't know what,
you know, happened at all.
- I mean, everyone just
put two and two together
that something bad happened,
because she's not feeling well.
I don't know
how it's gonna turn out.
I don't imagine
it's gonna go well.
- First of all, I...
I want to really
apologize to you all.
This morning,
Logan did come to my room.
He told me that he
is interested in pursuing
a relationship with Gabby.
And this is something
that Gabby and I...
It was kind of our biggest fear.
But I thought we were farther
enough in this process
where this wasn't gonna happen.
It's just tough, like,
the constant rejection.
And I do want to, like,
open the floor...
Like, if you guys, like,
don't want to be here,
like, you do not have to be.
If anyone, you know,
has any concerns
or wants to leave just...
Obviously let me know.
I'd rather know now.
I definitely feel
very vulnerable and nervous.
When you are rejected,
it makes you question yourself.
It makes insecurity come up.
- Mind if I grab you for a sec?
- Yeah, of course.
I would be lying
if I said I didn't think
other people would walk out.
I'm just having a really
hard time moving forward.
And if this doesn't go well,
I don't know if I can,
so hopefully tonight
changes all that.
Because at this point,
I feel like
everyone's gonna walk out.
- How are you? Like...
- It just was like...
Obviously me and Gabby's,
like, biggest fear,
like, in this whole thing
is, like,
is someone gonna flip?
- I'm sorry you had
to deal with that.
- It's okay.
- Like, the fact that, like,
you hold it together
with such composure and grace.
- Thank you.
- I mean, seriously.
You don't have to apologize,
it's like...
- I do.
- I do really appreciate that.
But I mean, like,
I'm here because
I love that feeling
of seeing you smile
and making you happy.
That's who I am.
I'm wanna make you smile
and I wanna make you happy
every day.
- I love that.
Thank you
for checking up on me, truly.
- Of course, of course.
- What a day.
- Yeah, it's a tough one.
- She handled that very well.
- Absolutely.
- That's tough.
- Oh, my gosh,
are you kidding me?
Especially with Logan
getting a rose last night.
- Ah...
- Yeah, you know,
you know, I want to have
a conversation with her.
You know, to just tell her
that I am here for her,
and I'm 100% invested
in this relationship.
- I agree. Yeah.
The other guys, they're
in a different place than me.
They all have expressed
that they want
to make sure she's happy
and feels like
a million bucks tonight.
And that's all amazing, it is,
and I want to do the same,
but I want to touch
on how I feel.
- This is for us.
- Wow.
- I wanted to do
something special for you.
- I actually was pretty hurt.
You know, I see Rachel
as my future person,
and it didn't sit
the best with me.
When you're in a relationship,
a healthy relationship,
you both need to be able
to communicate your feelings.
I'm, like,
a little bit scared to have
this conversation
with Rachel, but like,
we definitely gotta have it.
Moving forward,
I want to be your person...
I mean, that's why I'm here...
And I want to be
your best friend,
and I want you to be able to
tell me literally everything.
And I'll just say, like, I'll
take any piece of you any day,
and today we lost,
like, something that, like,
I think we could have made,
like...
I mean, I know could have made,
like, an amazing memory.
But today, you know,
hurt a little bit.
- Yeah.
- Like, it made me feel
a little unseen.
Like, I don't want to make you
feel bad at all, like...
- No, I want you...
I want you to keep telling me
how you feel.
- I feel like our
relationship at this point
has gotten to the point
where, like, we can
talk about stuff like this.
- Yeah.
You have no idea.
I do see you.
- Okay.
- I literally look forward
to every single time
we get to spend together.
- I want to keep building
on what we have,
not, you know,
kind of gloss over things.
And I want to build it
the right way.
- I love that.
Believe me.
Thank you.
Tino continues to be truly
open and vulnerable with me.
And hearing him want
to be around me
even if I'm not in a good mood
or if it's just for a second,
it's a really good feeling,
especially
after all the rejection
I've been through.
It really just does
make me hopeful.
- You know, how are you?
- I'm good.
This was, like,
the last thing I needed.
- I know.
I feel like you've
been through a lot.
- And so far tonight,
everyone is checking up on me
and validating me.
- You know, we missed you today.
We were waiting for you
to, like,
eat waffles and drink beer.
- I want a Belgian beer so bad.
And although it was
definitely nerve-racking
walking in tonight,
everyone's truly been able
to make me feel so special.
- How cool is that?
- Oh, my God.
- Just for you.
I feel like I'm in the stars.
- You are the star.
- It's been so tough
to get to this point today,
but my feelings are just
growing stronger and stronger,
and it's a really great feeling.
- How are you doing today?
Do you feel like
you can, like, breathe now?
- Yeah, no, I feel better.
I wanted to, like, really
show up for everyone.
- I was pretty worried
about you.
If you were okay,
and feeling still
like, okay about everything
and all of us guys.
The connections are, you know,
getting deeper, and it's, uh...
It's not easy,
and you're handling it
absolutely like a champion.
- Thank you.
No, I appreciate you
being so honest with me,
and truly, I feel like
every time I'm with you,
my day is so much better.
- You know, sometimes
if you want to let out stress,
like, you normally would yell,
right?
Do you need to get any... do you
want to get some yelling out?
- Yeah!
- Should we get
some yelling out?
- I want to.
- And keep in mind,
like, I got a deep yell.
- Can I just scream?
- All right, let's just scream.
- Okay.
- In three, two, one.
- It's incredible yelling out
all my frustrations with Zach.
He really does make me laugh.
I feel like I genuinely
can be myself around him.
I'm really happy that the day
was able to get turned around
because at this point
in the journey,
I want every single rose to go
to someone who truly continues
to step it up with me.
Hi, guys.
And after such a great night,
I'm very confident that these
guys are all here for me.
Um...
so I know that today
wasn't ideal.
And I really do appreciate
all of you being able
to truly show up tonight,
especially
after sort of a low day for me.
But this rose can only go
to one person.
And this person continues to
be extremely vulnerable with me
and is able to open up with me,
even when it's really hard.
And so...
Tino, will you accept this rose?
- Yes, I'd love to.
- I mean, it's funny 'cause,
like, every rose I get,
I feel like is like the most
important rose I've gotten.
But this one was a special one
because it is like resemblant
of, like, hard days
in a relationship.
It's exciting to, like, see
a future with somebody again.
- Have a good night, guys.
- I mean, I'm happy for Tino,
but like, damn, you know?
Rachel's the person,
you know, that I could
be spending the rest
of my life with,
and it's becoming
very, very real.
I mean I've been giving
my heart out from day one,
so there's, like, real,
real feelings on the line,
and I don't want to be hurt.
- I feel relieved.
I've said what I feel,
I've stated who I want,
and that's Gabby.
And what happens now
is out of my hands.
Gabby's going on
a group date today,
and I'm just hoping
that I'll get an answer soon.
And hopefully Gabby
will give me a shot.
Hey!
Hi!
- Ooh, that's a far road.
- Good to see you.
- You too.
You guys are always
out of breath.
Thank you. Hi!
Oh. It's so good... I know,
this is a great seeing... hi.
How are you guys?
- Good.
- It's so nice here.
- Today we just get to explore
the city,
one of literally the cutest
and charming European cities
that I've ever seen.
So I'm so excited to just
spend the day with you
and have some quality time.
Shall we?
- Yeah!
- Okay.
- I'm following you.
- I don't honestly
have a ton of doubts
going into today.
I feel like I have an open
heart and an open mind.
Best case scenario today
is that I connect more
with these men and just have
a sense of normalcy
and enjoying kind of
everyday things.
Have you guys seen these boats?
Should we go on one?
- Gabby gave her
one-on-one date to Johnny,
so I'm disappointed
a little bit,
but looking forward
to the date today
and getting time with Gabby.
This group date could
very well be make or break
in terms of my time
to continue to explore
something with Gabby and keep
building that connection.
- How fast can this thing go?
Yeah.
- Oh, my God.
This is beautiful.
- That's beautiful.
Like the greenery. I love it.
I love the old brick.
- Low bridge, Nate.
- Protect your head.
- Duck, duck, duck!
- Gabby looks amazing today.
She was in a all-black outfit.
I couldn't keep my eyes off
her, but going on a date
with five other guys, it's...
It's pretty weird.
- Oh, my God, I smell waffles.
- Waffles!
- Hi!
- How are you?
- Good, how are you?
- Welcome at House of Waffles.
- Thank you.
We're excited.
- Would you like to try
to make one yourselves?
- Love. Yeah.
- I've been wanting
waffles since I got here.
I'm just like, "Yes."
It looks so amazing.
- Wow.
- That is really good.
- Isn't it?
Ooh.
- You're going under?
- Yeah.
- This isn't natural to hang
out with, like, six guys
and one girl, but what
resonates with her is people
are willing to put themselves
out there
and to make her feel wanted.
So that's what I'm trying to do.
And she looks amazing,
so it's like...
It's a fun day so far.
Full of surprises.
So as long as we don't have to
physically fight each other,
I'm up for any surprise
at this point.
- Okay. Yo, we better D up.
- Swing it, swing it, swing it.
- God, these kids are good.
- Ooh.
- Clear it out. Clear it.
- Come on.
- Oh!
- First time I think I've
played soccer in 15 years.
Those kids are no joke.
They're good.
They're going between my legs.
But you gotta win somehow.
All right, I'm gonna start
picking these kids up.
- It's so fun to see the guys
interact with little kids.
Nate, you can tell
is immediately
comfortable around kids,
which is no surprise,
because he's a dad.
Just score one goal.
But really, everyone
is diving right in,
and it's kind of enlightening
to take a peek into the future.
You guys did so good.
The Belgian boys won the
soccer match fair and square,
but I know my guys are
pretty competitive, so I have
another surprise for them.
Oh!
- Out of nowhere, this big
burly Belgian guy
brings out
these two buckets of fish.
- Come.
- And he's like,
"You, we're gonna play
a Belgian game."
- You know this?
Rock, paper, scissors.
- Okay.
- Okay. One...
I win.
- Wait.
- Oh, God.
- That's the Belgian game.
- I am not accustomed
to a lot of Belgium games,
but I'd like to find the person
that made this game
and give him a piece of my mind.
Rock paper, scissors, shoot.
- Oh.
- Here it goes.
Here he goes.
- This is my friend
Flipper here.
Oh, say what up, Flipper.
"What up, dawg?"
You know, I feel
like Gabby likes me.
"Yeah, she was feeling you.
"She didn't want you
to see you slapped by us,
but you know what, YOLO."
For sho, for sho.
- In America,
this is how we play.
Instead of slapping the face...
Oh!
- That was a great day, but
the highlight was the kiss.
I saw an opportunity to go for
the kiss, and I went for it.
Why not?
I don't know how they felt
when I kissed Gabby,
but I don't really care.
- Thank you for choosing
this date.
We're having a great time.
- Oh, I'm so glad.
Yeah.
No, it means so much.
And really when I say,
like, I look at you guys,
and I truly do feel like
the luckiest girl in the world,
and I can't believe that
I'm here with all of you.
- We all felt like we had
a good amount of time
with her today, myself included.
So it's... it's just refreshing
to not have to worry about drama
and only worry
about the relationship.
So excited to continue it
into the evening portion.
- Today was a testament
to, like, our group.
We really do get along,
and we're all respectful.
- Ooh, there's one rose.
- Whittling down the group to
such a small number of guys
is the best move ever.
We're all gonna get
so much time tonight,
and I'm excited
to continue to grow
Gabby and I's relationship.
- I thought that
was a really special day,
just like getting out in
like a spring day in Bruges.
Sharing that with Gabby
and you guys was really cool.
I'm looking forward
to tonight as well,
so it's just like
I think everything's
kind of going in a positive way.
So I'm excited.
- Well, since it is
a smaller group of us,
I don't think that we're gonna
have to worry about trying
to steal time or worry about
when we're gonna grab her,
so it's gonna make it easier
to focus on the conversation
that we want to have with Gabby.
- Toast to a great first day
here in Belgium,
and toast to a great night
with Gabby.
- Cheers.
- I'm still a little salty
about the kids that
whupped us in soccer,
but you know.
- I think we need a rematch
with those kids tomorrow.
- Oh, oh.
- Oh!
- The hell?
- What side of the park you on?
- What is going on?
- How's everybody?
- I'm sure you guys
are curious why I'm here.
I would be too.
I originally had
a connection with Gabby,
but I decided
I was gonna pursue Rachel
because she saw something in me,
and she told me that we
could have something special.
As time went on, I didn't
quite see the same thing.
So I met with Rachel,
and I told her
"I can no longer see you,"
and I had a conversation
with Gabby.
And I got word today
that she wants me
to have an opportunity
to pursue her.
- I'm just confused right now.
Logan is hopping over to
Team Gabby, and it's just...
It's just...
I don't... I don't get it.
I guess we were thinking
that she saw, like,
her person in the guys here,
and for someone else
to be added, I just don't
know what to think right now.
- I will be moving in
with you guys as well.
So let's have a good night.
- Hi.
- It's upsetting
that Logan is here
because Logan would not be here
if Gabby didn't want
to explore that relationship,
so it makes me question
how strong really is
my relationship with Gabby
or Gabby's relationship
with any of the other guys here.
- I just wanted to say
thank you guys
for such a good day.
I feel like I had so much fun.
And Logan is here.
Um, I'm sure you all
have spoken.
- We did.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Logan came to me yesterday,
you know,
to express his feelings, so...
yeah, here we are.
- Happy to be here.
- Thank you.
So let's make a toast
to an amazing day
and relationships flourishing
and still some to explore.
- Cheers.
I'm worried about tonight
because knowing how far I am
along with these men,
I don't ever want
to jeopardize that
by having Logan come along
this late in the game.
But I really do want to be open
to all possibilities,
and I hope that
the guys understand
where I'm coming from.
- This is a big night.
You just kind of
brought on Logan, like...
- Yeah.
- You know, when you do
introduce something like that,
like, and you already have
these established relationships,
and you don't know, like...
Logan's been
back and forth a little bit.
And I want to let you know
that I'm all in.
- Thank you.
- And I think that
you're awesome,
and I'm very much about you,
and so
I'm not anyone that would
make you question anything.
And hopefully
my words carry weight.
- Yeah.
Like, I do really care for you.
I know your heart
is in such a good place.
Like, I can tell you're ready
for a relationship.
It's never been a doubt
in my mind.
And I appreciate that about you.
- Yeah.
- I just didn't see that
coming, you know, from Logan.
I thought he was, like,
crazy about Rachel.
- Or maybe he's the most
calculated dude here.
- Yeah.
- I wonder if he gets
the group date rose.
- I kind of feel like
that's gonna happen.
- That would be so annoying.
- The addition of Logan,
it is a wake-up call,
and it has some of
the guys, including myself,
on alert to kind
of reevaluate, like,
where you stand.
I always try to be,
like, as open as possible
and just try to show you
all of me,
and it was just fun today.
Like, it just felt, like,
so natural.
- Like, we just
got to be together.
- Yeah.
- The only bloop was obviously
the new Logan addition,
but even then like...
- Yeah, how did you...
Like, how did you take it?
- So I, at first, I saw him
and I was like, "Okay,
this is what's going on."
But honestly, you should
explore every relationship.
Like, I want to be chosen.
- Yeah.
- So just know that you have
my support in all of this.
- Yeah.
- You do.
- No, thank you.
I'm really, like, so grateful
for you guys,
and just, like,
being here with you.
I know group settings
are so hard.
It kind of like...
It's hard for me, too,
to have it be hard for you.
- It's all right.
With each week, I have gotten
closer to each of the guys,
and our connections
do grow stronger
each and every time
that I see them.
So with Logan coming in late,
I think emotions are high,
but ultimately,
I hope that they just trust me.
How are you?
- I'm good. I mean...
I don't know.
I obviously, like,
have feelings for you,
and I think I'm, like, still,
like, flying
off that, like, one-on-one time
where I thought we had,
like, such this
amazing connection,
and it just felt like us.
And then this is like six guys
and you, and it just...
I don't know.
It, like, started to feel like
very real in that sense.
- Yeah.
- And I was, like,
used to being like,
stealing you away, like, for
a kiss or something like that.
And it just, like, felt,
I don't know,
it didn't feel,
like, that natural.
- Sometimes it is kind of hard
having earlier one-on-ones
because then, like, so much
progresses afterwards,
but I do think about you a lot.
And sure, I think we could
probably grow some more,
but I think there's time.
- Yeah, I'll take the kiss that
I didn't get to steal today.
- Yeah.
- Just this kiss.
- As someone that feels like
that they're fighting
for a group date rose,
to see Logan come in,
you know, naturally you're
like, "Okay, you know,
"do I have a shot tonight?
Like, have you already
made up your mind?"
- It does kind of muddy
the waters a bit.
If Logan did get the rose,
it would speak volumes
to where her intent lies.
We'll see how things shake out,
but it's a little unsettling.
- I kind of can't believe
that I'm
getting to sit here with you.
- Oh, I know.
I bet you've been going through,
like, so much
these last days or weeks.
Do you feel, like, kind of good?
- I feel great.
- Yeah.
- I mean, this is what I
wanted, to be sitting here
holding your hand, you know?
- Yeah.
- And I realized, like, what
you had to go through in order
to just, like, get me to sit
on this couch with you.
It was, like, you had to have
difficult conversations,
and like, you did that,
and let me be here,
and this is where I want to be.
Like, really.
- Yeah.
- Like, I'm very into you.
So I'm glad to be here.
- Yeah.
Yeah, me too.
I think the premise
of everything
is to listen to your heart
and try and find
a way to do it with integrity,
which you did,
so that means a lot.
- Thank you.
Yeah.
- Yeah.
- Sitting with Gabby, there
is no doubt in my mind
that I made the right choice.
It's time to pursue Gabby
in a way that is fierce
and in a way that I can
make up for lost time.
And if I got the group date
rose, I'd be pretty excited.
- I did want to thank you guys
honestly for such a great day.
Unfortunately,
I just have one rose to give.
I wish I could give you
all them today.
So...
Nate, will you accept this rose?
- Yes.
Ah, you need to go
through this sweater...
Yeah.
- Oh, I'm so happy that
I got the group date rose.
It's my first one,
so it's amazing.
We even added a guy tonight,
and I thought
that it could have been him,
but she gave it to me,
and I am so...
I am so elated.
- It sucks.
Like, I went into tonight
feeling very good
about, like, our talk,
but Nate got
the group date rose,
and we have Logan here now,
so I don't necessarily know,
like, ranking-wise,
where I stand.
But I don't need to be here
for, like, eight more weeks
just to see what happens.
Like, that's just
a waste of my time, so...
- I woke up this morning
feeling good.
Last night, I made a fantastic
reconnection with Gabby.
I think maybe there's still
a little tension
with a couple of the guys
about the fact
that I'm getting to switch over,
and that's okay with me.
I didn't think this would
be a popular decision.
I'm just trying
to follow my heart.
But I did hurt Rachel,
and I really hope
she finds what she's
looking for on this journey.
- Wow, this is adorable.
- I'm just so happy to be here
with you, truly.
- I'm so happy to be here
with you too.
Yeah, when my name was, like,
left off the group date card...
- Mm-hmm.
- I was just lit up.
I was like, "Yes, finally."
- I feel like we've always
had, like, such a solid,
like, base from the beginning.
- Mm-hmm.
- And I feel like whenever
anything happens, like,
you're the first person
I want to see.
I feel really safe with you.
- I love that.
- I do have very strong
feelings for Aven.
I have since the beginning.
But I had a rough couple days
in Belgium,
so today I just
really need to know
that it's a two-sided connection
and that we both feel that way
and it's not just coming
from me.
This is so cool.
- This is amazing.
- I'm so happy
you're here with me.
- I know.
I missed you.
- I missed you.
- I've been looking forward
to this one-on-one with Rachel,
and now that it's here,
I'm really excited.
You know,
the things that Rachel's
been through up to this point
haven't been easy.
So I can't wait
to explore the city
and just try to make today
as special as possible.
And you know, just reassure her
that I'm 100% here for her only.
- When is your birthday?
- November 6.
- What's you zodiac sign?
- Scorpio.
- I'm a Pisces.
- Oh, let's go.
- Ooh, it must be a match.
- Check.
- Right off the bat,
Aven is one of the most
handsome men I've ever seen.
And we are exploring Bruges,
which is one
of the most romantic places
I've ever been to,
and that's all I want today
is romance.
I love chocolate.
What do you think?
- I'm in.
- Do you want to go in?
- Let's do it.
- Oh, my gosh.
- Oh. Oh, my. All right.
It smells so good.
- So we're getting hefty today.
- Ready?
- Mmm.
- Aven is such a great person.
He's so funny.
He makes me laugh.
How do you do that?
- I don't know.
This is a hidden talent.
- And we've always had
a good physical connection,
but he's really stepping it up.
You know, touching me
and kissing me
and making me feel desired
and wanted.
- Hi!
- What you guys doing over here?
Sewing?
- We... no, no, no, no, no.
We are making lace.
It's a very... a tradition since
the 15th century in Belgium.
- Oh, wow.
- That's incredible.
- So if you choose him,
what will be the wedding like?
- It would be
a very big wedding.
- Big wedding.
What we do is wearing a veil.
- Wow.
- So now you have to close
your eyes.
Just pop it over.
Oh.
Now you can see
if he's good kisser.
- Ah.
- Leave it on.
Oh.
Beautiful.
- I've never kissed someone
with a veil on my head,
but it feels right.
A wedding is something
that I definitely
feel like could be
in our future.
- That looks beautiful on you.
- What do you think?
- Can we just take
this one to go?
Can we get this gift wrapped?
- Yeah.
- Aven is so romantic.
It just feels like
everything today
has just been so perfect.
I love spending
the day with him.
Oh, I think we're here.
- Oh, my God.
Look at this view.
- I already feel like we have
such a strong connection,
so tonight I can't wait
to get to know him more.
- So excited.
- I know.
- I did not expect
to come back here.
- I know.
- But I'm happy we're here.
- It's really scary to begin
to get these feelings...
- After you.
- Because I don't want
to get hurt.
And as much as I don't
think Aven would hurt me,
it is still in the back
of my mind,
because I just feel like
no one can really blame me,
that a shoe could drop.
So I hope I can
learn more about him
and feel confident
giving him that rose tonight.
I've been really looking
forward to this date with you
for a while now, and I can't
wait to get to know you more,
but I just wanted to thank
you for the best date.
- Of course, absolutely.
- Cheers.
Well, I had just an
amazing day as you did.
Definitely exceeded
well, well beyond.
- I know.
It was the best day with you.
And I would love to hear
more about you and your life
and what makes you
the way you are.
- Yeah.
Well, I think I told you
like when we first met.
Stability is a big thing for me.
Feeling secure
and that someone's
like not just gonna dip out
at any point
is, like, huge for me.
Growing up, my parents
were like never together.
You know, I lived with
my mom for a few years
and then I moved to with
my dad for, like, the rest
of my life, basically.
- And so how old was it?
- I was ten, which was tough.
I didn't want to do it.
I was like,
"I don't want to be here.
Can you send me back?"
type of thing.
And I didn't get to see Mom
that often.
You know, our relationship
to some extent
was like through a phone for
a while, you know what I mean?
Which was tough like,
in high school, and it sucked.
And honestly like, you know,
you want to have like
a stable relationship
with both your parents,
but I just really
never saw her that much.
So you know, me and my mom
got really close
when I got older,
because of all the time
that we didn't have
when I was younger.
So in regards to all that, she
kind of made something for me,
and it's kind of
like a good luck,
good energy type of thing.
So it's like this little
like, rubber bracelet thing.
- She made this?
- Yeah.
- Oh, my gosh.
- And kind of seeing
how, you know,
these last couple of weeks
have been tough for you,
I think like, if you hold
on to it for a while,
maybe it'll like turn
your experience in all this
around for a little bit,
you know, so...
- Well, you are turning this
around just starting with that.
- Yeah.
- But this is honestly
incredible.
- It's been a tough week
for Rachel, so I want to just,
like, be as open as possible
and there to be no grey area
with how I'm feeling
in this moment,
and I want to just kind
of do my best to remind her
that I'm here for her.
- I truly have had the most
incredible day with you,
and I only wish
we had more time,
because I just think we have
such an incredible connection.
- Couldn't agree more.
- So, Aven, will you accept
this rose?
- Absolutely, of course I will.
And I just wanted to say
I'm so honored
that we're on this path
together,
and I truly look forward
to the moments
that we get to spend together
moving forward.
- Asking me
for more one-on-ones?
I'm very, very, happy
about how today went.
I mean, it was an amazing night
from start to finish,
and I've never felt this,
like, strong of a connection,
or this natural of a connection,
you know, so quickly.
Oh, my God.
Every moment I spend
with Rachel, our feelings
are getting stronger
and stronger for each other,
and I really do see Rachel
as someone
who could be my future wife
and somebody that I do want
to spend
the rest of my life with.
- I feel so happy.
Tonight is the perfect night
with Aven.
He's been there to support me,
and he has chosen me
immediately,
and he's never wavered.
I could easily see myself
falling in love with Aven.
And I feel like
I'm almost there.
- What's up, Johnny?
- Johnny.
- You missed one hell of a day.
- Was it cool?
What'd you guys do?
- It was crazy.
- So we're all hanging out
around the couch area,
and someone walks up.
- Yeah.
- Logan.
No.
- Although he's
been with Rachel,
he has feelings for Gabby.
- Is he coming over?
- He's over.
- Yeah. Mm-hmm.
- How do you feel?
- I was bummed.
- Yeah.
- The fact that Logan is here,
you know, we start to question,
like, is Gabby questioning
her connections
with the rest of us?
- That's like...
That's what's kind of
going through my head, too,
as I go on this one-on-one.
It's like,
what connection do they have
that I gotta kind of step up?
- That's fair.
- Oh.
- Whoa.
- What's up, guys?
- Logan.
- Going into my date with Gabby
with Logan coming over,
it's gonna be a little weird,
but I'm gonna try to, you
know, compartmentalize that.
All right, gentlemen,
I got a date I gotta get to.
I'm out of here.
- All right, take care, Johnny.
- Peace, guys.
- Bye, Johnny.
- Me and Gabby,
right now we vibe.
We know there's a connection.
You know, we've admitted
that we're into each other.
But this is not
looking for a fling,
this is looking for
someone that is forever.
So I'm over the moon
to finally get
some one-on-one time with her.
Gabby!
- What?
- So...
- Come on.
- No. Yeah.
I got you. I got you.
Wait.
I'm excited to spend the day
with Johnny.
Johnny and I have fun.
I have a fun day planned
in the countryside of Belgium.
- Beautiful. Love it.
- He's like so macho,
and too cool for school,
which normally I'd hate,
but he pulls it off
'cause he's like kind of goofy.
But good relationships
are all about balance.
The fun side, and the emotional,
and the serious side.
With Johnny, I don't quite
know if we have a balance yet.
But today I'm excited
to see where things go.
- Welcome.
- Thank you.
- Gabby.
- This is beautiful.
We're so excited to be here.
- We started already, actually.
- Oh, you did?
Without us?
- So my name is Ann.
I'm actually sixth generation
in a family brewery,
which is called The Half Moon.
This is Vincent.
- Nice to meet you.
- The brewer of the beers.
Speaking of beer,
let's go taste it.
- Let's go.
Yeah.
He has a one track mind.
- Oh, hell yeah.
This is right up my alley.
Whoa.
- Yum.
- Gabby's, hands down,
the coolest girlfriend
I've ever had.
She brought me to Belgium,
and she took me to a beer farm.
It just made me that much
more attracted to her.
- So smell it.
- You can swirl it a little.
Get out the flavors.
- Cheers.
- Oh.
You're enjoying this, huh?
- We have an activity
for you to do together.
- Oh, cool.
- That's great.
- Yay.
Oh, my God.
I actually don't know
what this is.
- Is this a spa day?
- I think so.
A Bruges...
- So you drink this?
- Immerse your entire body
into the beer.
Oh, I bet you can...
- You could definitely
drink that.
- I love spa days,
that's where I thrive.
Did you bring your Speedo?
- Yeah, actually,
that's what I'm putting on.
- So we're gonna soak in beer,
maybe drink the beer,
have a little fun in between,
and hopefully get weird.
- Nice and hard.
- Yes.
- Love it.
Harder, harder.
- Do you like it?
- Doesn't feel great.
- Does that kind of hurt?
- No. Your turn.
- Try me.
- No free rides.
- No!
- I would never act like this
on a first date.
- You hit me in my face.
- Try it one more time.
No free rides.
Usually, I'm more laid back
and not so assertive.
- But Gabby is definitely
pulling it out of me.
Wow, that feels amazing.
- Does it?
- That's sandpaper.
Oh, no.
Watching Johnny
be so comfortable
and kind of leaning into
the craziness is so special.
- That's beer.
- Is it beer?
- This is the kind of person
I would want
to do these things with,
and this is the kind of person
I can see myself with.
- You drink it?
I didn't drink it.
I spit it out.
Don't do that.
That's bad for you.
- But Johnny and I
haven't had really
intense conversations
yet and have kind of
remained surface level.
Oh, my God.
- Oh, my God.
- This is beautiful.
And I need someone who can be
there for me and be vulnerable,
and vice versa.
So I am excited to see if
Johnny can go there tonight.
- Like, today, honestly,
was so strange for me
because I never act like that.
But I do, like when I'm
by myself in my room.
No, I feel like, yeah,
it's just like super hard
to get out of my comfort zone
like that, but...
- Yeah.
- Clearly, today I was like,
"Let's get in that tub."
- Yeah.
- Right?
- No, I loved it.
You're, like, funnier
than I thought.
- I was, like, super nervous
going into it,
I'm not gonna lie.
- Oh, you didn't seem like it.
Do you feel like you're
just, like, kind of guarded,
or it takes you a while
just as a person to be weird?
- I'm a freak.
- Yeah, I know.
- No, I think it's both.
I think, like,
I'm super guarded at first,
and then it just
takes a while too.
I think it's just because
like past relationships,
and I feel like once I got
to that point of, like,
being, like, myself,
it just like ended.
- You had said you were in one
kind of recently, no?
- Yeah, but then I, like,
started to be myself
and she like just
disappeared on me.
I think that was
like really hard.
- Yeah.
- And that was
like the last time
I really, like,
let my guard down.
- Yeah.
It's so hard with
relationships because I think
it's impossible
to not take it personally.
- Yeah, and I think when you...
I exude confidence...
- Yeah.
- I'm, like, no, that's not me.
I don't... I'm, like, the least
confident person ever,
which is crazy, but...
- Yeah.
I think you have a lot
to be confident about.
I even see it really, like,
with you and the guys.
I feel like people like being
around you for who you are.
- I don't see it, but like,
I'm like so hard on myself,
I feel like.
- Yeah.
- I think I seriously lack,
like, some serious confidence
to where like I should
probably, like, you know, talk
to people about it,
or whatever but...
I definitely struggle with it.
Like, just depression
and like, really
feeling bad about yourself.
And I feel like I have felt
like at an all-time low
all the time
for like no reason too.
- Mm-hmm. Yeah.
No, I can definitely...
I feel like I relate.
I've struggled a lot
with anxiety and depression
in my life, and I've had
to relearn so many things
that I didn't get to learn
as a kid.
And as an adult it hits you,
and you just think,
I'm kind of...
- Exactly.
- Yeah, like I'm broken
and nobody else understands.
But I think we just have to be,
like, easier on ourself
a little bit.
Tonight, Johnny is saying
things to me that I don't know
if he's really said
to anyone recently,
but I think that's
such an important part
of a relationship is the
willingness to be vulnerable,
and he's shown that
in so many ways today.
- I had a lot of fun today.
- Me too.
- Like, a lot of fun.
- I did not want that to end.
- Yeah.
- Can we do it again, please?
- Yes.
- Um...
But just like you said,
that I bring out a side in you,
I feel like you do the same
with me.
Like, I never have to be
reserved around you, you know.
So, Johnny...
- Yes?
- Will you accept this rose?
- Of course.
- I'm so happy right now.
This rose means pretty much
everything in the world.
From the beginning, this
whole thing has been natural
with her,
and I think if something's
meant to be, it comes natural.
I can run faster
than you than you think!
Ah!
I really do believe
that what Johnny
and I have is really special.
I love the inside of Johnny.
All the things I think that
he's maybe scared to put forth
are the things
that I love the most.
Oh, my God.
Johnny,
he doesn't know how romantic
or how sweet
or how special he is,
but I am really grateful for him
and just so excited
to see where things go.
I know it's just
the beginning for us.
- Going into tonight,
this is an interesting
Rose Ceremony,
because we have Logan here now.
That kind of adds like
a weird dynamic to this group
that like we have somebody new.
I know some people aren't
feeling 100% comfortable.
I mean,
I don't feel comfortable.
I can't imagine how they feel.
It's just starting to get
more real, so I think
tonight, I'm curious to see
who goes home.
- Anticipation is a little bit...
I'm like, who's walking in here?
Is Logan walking in here?
- I know.
I want them to come down so bad.
- Tonight is gonna be
a bit of a curve ball,
I think, with the Gabby side,
with Logan moving over
to their side.
I'm sure that stirred the pot
quite a bit.
- Gentlemen.
- Going into the cocktail party,
I just feel discouraged that we
got Logan from Rachel's side.
What has he done to this point
to be worthy
of coming into the journey?
I don't know, so I'm nervous
going into tonight.
- How's the week been
for you guys?
I mean...
- So the group date
was canceled.
You know, Rachel
wasn't feeling ready for it.
There was a lot going on
that day.
- To hear that, you know, those
events had also carried over
and affected Rachel
to the point of changing
the group date
is really concerning,
and I'm sorry about that.
I think you guys understand
my intentions.
- Uh, you know, there's
always concern, you know,
when you think about
number of roses.
Now there's
a little more concern,
because there's same number
of roses, more guys.
I haven't had
that real time with her yet
and may not get that time,
so hopefully the connection
is strong enough.
- It's been a long journey
to sit next to Gabby,
and it hasn't been an easy one.
- I'm sorry.
- Oh, ..
- But when I'm with her,
I'm breathing fast,
I'm feeling butterflies.
I want to keep this.
But you know what, I never
asked Gabby for a guarantee,
I just asked her for a chance,
and she gave me that chance.
And tonight I really want
to capitalize on that chance,
and I'm hoping
that I'm rewarded with a rose.
- Hi, guys.
Thanks for being here.
First and foremost,
I want to apologize
to everyone who lost time
this week,
but I'm so excited to have
another night with all of you,
and I am so hopeful
for what's to come.
- Yeah.
Coming into tonight,
I have these
overwhelming feelings
of this all becoming so real.
I see these relationships
flourishing
and also getting really hard,
but with great risk
comes great reward.
So cheers to a great night
and let's have some fun.
- Cheers to that.
- Logan is the big question mark
that we're all wondering how
much Gabby really sees in him.
His connection may be stronger
than we assume.
Just because I have a rose
doesn't mean that I feel
secure in our relationship.
I do feel good about it,
but you never know.
I love your laugh.
- Well, I do have
something for you.
- You do?
- Yeah.
It's a little gift.
I don't know if you've been
souvenir shopping in Belgium,
but open it.
There's...
It's Belgian chocolate,
for your daughter.
I know you really miss her.
- Thank you so much.
- Mm-hmm. Of course.
- Okay.
- I'm nervous.
My fate tonight
is completely unknown.
Gabby either
has to give me a rose,
who's been in the house
for two days,
and turn away
one of these other guys,
who have been like solid
for her.
- Does that count?
That counts.
- All right, that counts.
Which is not fair, because
you wore this dress here,
and I was distracted.
- A lot of these guys are
going in with weeks and weeks
with Gabby.
- You look amazing.
- Thank you.
You do too.
This was my first impression
suit, so you know...
- Ooh!
- I thought I, you know,
let me go ahead.
- Time to tell her who they are
and learn about who she is.
- You like to pick on people,
in like a good way.
- In a good way.
But you've earned my sweet side,
you've been so sweet to me.
- Oh. Thank you.
- Knowing that makes my odds
seem pretty slim.
- You impress me.
- No, you impress me.
You have a very
like individualized way
of making me feel special.
- It would be astronomical for
her to pick me over someone
who has been unwavering.
- I feel like we hit it off
from the beginning,
and like, every time we talk,
I want you to know
that, you know, it's just us.
- Yeah.
- But I don't want to lose this.
The only way I can get
to a level with Gabby
that other people have
had the chance to
is by being myself.
I wasn't able to be part
of the last group date.
- You want to get slapped
by a fish?
- You guessed it.
- First we have to play
rock, paper, scissors.
- Kay.
- And then you let me win.
- Okay.
- Rock, paper, scissors, shoot.
No, we're on the same cadence.
Okay.
Thank God.
- Okay.
Which side do you want?
Good side, bad side?
- Obviously... what's
your good side?
- Um...
Oh!
- Wow, that's it?
In the throat?
Went to my neck.
- Okay.
- I can smell the fish.
- Does it smell bad?
- Now that Logan's here,
it's just sucks,
especially for people who are,
you know, gonna get sent home.
Like, I would totally feel
some type of way
putting in all this work
and then Logan
stepped in and just...
- Gets traded to the Kings,
drops 40 game one.
Like, yeah, that's tough.
- Can't win.
- It was already game seven
for some of us,
and now it's overtime, like...
- I'm pretty nervous going
into tonight's Rose Ceremony.
I think Gabby brought
Logan here for a reason.
You know, does she see
something in Logan that
she doesn't see
in the rest of us?
So it's, you know...
Kind of makes all of us,
but especially me, kind of
doubt where we are with Gabby.
- Gentlemen, sorry to interrupt.
The cocktail party is now over.
So we do have to get ready
for the Rose Ceremony.
- I think Logan coming over
is gonna push someone out
who may have not
been getting pushed out.
- I think my chance of
getting a rose tonight
are actually low, but you know,
Logan just came back
into the equation.
He hasn't had
much time with her,
so anything can happen.
- You know, I've been
in the Gabby trenches
since the initial onset.
Hopefully she sees that.
So I hope Logan doesn't get
a rose and is sent home.
- Going into tonight's
Rose Ceremony,
I'm anxious, nervous, obviously.
If I don't get a rose tonight
because of Logan,
I just will be, you know,
extremely upset.
- Logan getting a rose
makes me nervous
because that's one less rose
to go, to not just myself,
but also the guys
that have been with me
in the dating Gabby trenches.
So I hope Logan doesn't get
a rose, but I have no clue.
- I might be shocked
if Logan comes down.
He's had the least
amount of time of anyone.
- And if she does pick him,
then it's, like, you know,
it's very telling.
- Yeah.
- I know I'd be nervous as hell.
- I'm feeling a little uneasy
about tonight's Rose Ceremony,
because Logan moving over
to the Gabby side
really hurt Rachel.
It's on everyone's mind
where her head's at.
- I feel like I'm definitely
on the chopping block tonight,
and the only person
that I have to blame is Logan.
Hopefully, I get a rose,
but I don't know.
It could be any one of us
going home tonight.
- I feel like
we're gonna be shocked
at the first person
who walks in.
- The real question is, do we
think Logan gets one or no?
- I think he does.
- I think he does too.
And it's gonna cause some.
- A stir.
- I just wanted to say,
first of all,
I truly am lucky to know
each and every one of you.
Of course,
going into every week,
there are challenges.
Just know that if you do not
receive a rose tonight,
ultimately, I just
have to follow my instinct,
and I truly appreciate
each and every one of you.
- Yeah, this week
has been incredible.
I think each week
keeps surpassing the last
in so many ways,
so thank you so much
from the bottom of my heart.
- Curious to see who comes down.
- I am too.
I think the first guy
is gonna be,
um, Erich, for sure.
- Yeah.
- Jason.
Jason, will you
accept this rose?
- Of course. I'd love to.
- Damn, boy.
What's up, J?
- With the number one.
- How's it going, man?
- Number one.
- You made it.
- You guys are one and two.
- How many roses
were on the table?
- We had four.
- Oh.
- And Rachel had three.
- Wait, Rachel had three?
- If it's not Ty first,
Ty is second.
- There's no way it's Zach.
It's gotta be Tyler.
- I can see Zach
coming in last, actually.
- Zach.
Zach, will you accept this rose?
- 100%
- On paper, the odds
are not in my favor tonight.
- Spencer.
- I'm going up against guys
who have gotten to know Gabby
for five weeks.
Would have been much easier
to continue on
and commit to Rachel
without a problem,
but it wouldn't have been right.
- Tyler.
- Because I've had another week
to figure things out.
My feelings have been sorted.
I know what I want,
and I've put it out there.
Now a rose means
that's either accepted
or turned away.
- Erich.
- And it's intense.
- Erich, will you accept
this rose?
- Yes, of course.
- Because I am not sure at all
that Gabby feels
the same way I do.
- Gabby, Rachel, gentlemen.
It's the final rose tonight.
When you're ready.
- There's only one rose left.
I'm scared, you know?
There's a chance that this
is the last time I see Rachel.
- Ethan.
- I love you, bro.
Ethan, will you accept
this rose?
- Absolutely.
- It's down to me,
Mario, and Mike,
so it's now or never.
- Until Logan walks down,
I'm still, like,
not even, like,
considering that as an option.
- I think
it's gonna be Michael, but...
- I think it's Mario.
- I think Mario
comes down those stairs.
- I think it's Mario.
- I think it's Logan.
- Logan.
Logan, will you accept
this rose?
- Yes.
- She gave me a rose.
She stamped it,
made it official.
I feel great.
I feel incredible.
- Gentlemen, I'm sorry.
Please take a moment
and say your goodbyes.
- I mean, three guys up there,
I've had the least
amount of time.
One of them's had
five weeks with Gabby.
- Michael.
- Gabby.
- Thank you for everything.
- Yeah. Likewise.
- One of them got
the First Impression Rose.
- It's been a fun ride.
- Thank you for everything.
- No problem.
- And yet she chose me
to get the rose.
- Ah.
- Wow.
- Logan's coming down.
- Plot twist of the evening.
What's up?
- Hello, gentlemen.
- What's up, man?
Congrats.
- Thank you.
- Congrats.
I wasn't sure that Logan
was gonna show,
but now I know that,
you know, he's here.
And he is vying for Gabby's
affection and love,
so welcome to the squad,
I guess.
So Michael and Mario
are going, huh?
- Yeah.
- Wow.
- I would respect it
if it was Mario,
because he's
been putting in work.
But to each his own.
In all honesty,
it was tough to see,
but weak links are gone.
- Thank you.
Hi.
- Hey, Gabby.
And is getting real.
- Hello.
- How're you doing?
- Good.
- Everyone's a hitter.
- We are setting sail to a place
where it's very romantic.
Shocker.
- It's an even playing field
now,
and it's anyone's game,
so might as well be my game.
- Somewhere that's known
for its landscapes.
- There's no point
in stopping now.
Full speed ahead.
Me and Gabby.
- We're going to Amsterdam.
- Still to come this season
on "The Bachelorette"...
- I can say now with confidence,
I am falling in love with you.
- I truly feel like
I'm on cloud nine right now.
Everything I ask for,
you really embody it.
I really can't imagine
my life without you.
This is the best day ever.
- I've always wanted
to be with someone like you,
but just never knew
if it was possible.
He has, like, really shown me
what it's like to feel loved.
I feel like all my dreams
are, like, coming true.
Sometimes if things
are too good to be true,
that is exactly what they are,
too good to be true.
- There has been
a situation with Logan.
She was in tears.
- I feel awful.
- You gotta pack your bags.
- Watching her kiss
somebody else
is absolutely sickening.
This is a joke.
- Tino is acting like
a real baby back bitch.
- I'm terrified of
not just being a mom,
but being, like, bad at it.
I don't know what to do.
- I'm just so conflicted now.
I just don't understand.
I feel so blindsided by you.
- I don't want to be with a boy.
I want to be with a man.
- After overnights,
you change your mind?
You told me things,
and then you went
back against what you said.
I'm so sick of this.
I don't want to do this anymore.
He never loved me.
How do you move forward?
You can't.
Like, you can't do that.
I would, like, literally
rather be alone.
- He said he can't love me.
It's like, am I too broken
for anyone to love?
Rock, paper, scissors, shoot.
- Oh.
- You guys are sick.
You like it...
- Oh!
- This is the Belgium game.
- Here we go. On shoot.
Rock paper, scissors, shoot.
Oh!
- Oh.
- Oh!
- I'm actually not...
Ah!
You ain't around.
- You good, you good...
- Ahh!
- Wait.
I want to play with you.
- Got to do it in America
also, like this.
- Yeah.
- With fish sticks.
- Oh.
- Okay.
- Me?
- Mm-hmm.
- Ooh.
- All right, I'm out.
- Oh, la, la.
- If you don't let me win,
I swear to God.
- Two and done.
- One, two, then shoot. Okay.
- Okay. One. Two. Rock.
- Oh.
- I won.
- No.
- Yes, I won.
- I won.
- No.
You can kiss me.
- You want to kiss with me?
Whoa!
- I love it.
- I'm like, "You guys go.
Let's run away together."
- Let's go.
>>>>oakislandtk
www.opensubtitles.org