- Tonight
on "The Bachelorette"...
- Ahh!
- Your smile melts my heart.
- Oh.
- It just feels
like a really beautiful start
to something really amazing.
- I do just want
to get on your lap,
'cause I feel like
I can get closer to you.
Right now I feel so loved
and seen.
- We're in a football field
right now.
- It was so special.
I feel like I'm gonna remember
this for the rest of my life.
- Even if you were
the only person here,
I don't think I could have
the heart to continue...
- "I don't want
a woman like you."
It hurts to hear.
- Like, because there's
two of us
they think they can act
that way.
- I don't know if I have
the capacity
to keep doing this, like,
week after week.
- Dude, the girls
just walked out.
- Damn, my brain is spinning
right now.
- How many people left?
Four left?
I'm leaving.
I'm literally quitting.
- It all starts right now.
- We survived the night.
- Yeah, man.
- Yeah, it was pretty tight
in that room
with that last rose.
- We have 21 guys now,
and I think we're
definitely at a point
where people are starting
to lean in directions.
People are like,
"I want to spend
more time with Rachel."
Couple guys want to spend
more time with Gabby.
And then there's
a decent amount...
They still want to explore
both relationships.
But my goal is just, like,
spend more time with Gabby.
Spend more time with Gabby.
Figure out how I can do that.
- Wait, who gave you
your rose again?
Was it Rachel or Gabby?
- Rachel,
but that don't mean nothing.
- I feel like I already know,
something is there
with me and Gabby,
but I do have to explore
Rachel and I's connection first
before I can, you know,
choose a lane here.
- Did you guys talk
to both ladies last night
or was it just one?
- I got to talk to both of them.
I'm not leaning towards
one or the other right now.
So just kind of, like,
taking it day by day.
Okay.
- You know, I'm very interested
in both, you know,
Gabby and Rachel.
I haven't quite made
the decision
of which one I want to spend
all my time and energy with.
So, you know, right now,
I'm just happy to develop
those relationships
with both of them.
- Last night was really great.
And I think already there's men
that are clearly here for Rachel
and men who might be
more interested in me.
But there are a couple of men
more in the middle ground
that I think this week
will help us figure out
who we should pursue
relationships with
and who we're not meant
to be with.
Hi!
- Right now I'm afraid
of a couple things.
I'm afraid
that I'll kind of be let down.
And I'm afraid to make
the wrong decision.
- Obviously this
is a fresh new week.
- Yeah.
- And we're gonna be going
on dates this week.
- Mm-hmm.
- But at what point do you think
we need to, like, figure out
where everyone stands?
'Cause I feel
like that would give me
so much more clarity.
- Yeah.
- And it would feel
so much better moving forward
if I knew
where the guys were at.
- Yeah.
I want these guys
to be assertive
and make that decision fast.
I feel like they have spent
enough time with us.
So I think now the one's that
are lingering in the middle,
it's kind of sketch.
- No, I could not agree more.
- Yeah.
- It's disheartening, for sure.
- Mm-hmm.
I don't know.
Maybe this week
will help us figure it out.
I feel like we somehow need
to communicate that with them.
- I feel like
we could just tell them.
I mean, it's our journey.
- Yeah.
- Of course it's
up to them as well
who they want to explore,
but if at the end of the day...
- Mm-hmm.
- We make a decision...
- Yeah.
- It's kind of up to them
to reciprocate it
or decide not to continue,
I guess.
- Yeah, so true.
I feel like this is gonna be
a big week for us.
- I could not agree more.
And I think
they don't realize, really,
how much is on the line
this week.
- Yeah.
- Boys, how we doing?
What's going on?
Jesse!
What's up?
- All right, well, guys...
Well, if you can't tell by now,
Gabby and Rachel,
they're not messing around.
They're not looking for a fling.
They're looking
for their husbands.
Nate, what was it like for you
getting to spend
that entire day with Gabby?
- You know,
it felt like a lifetime.
I was fighting for
a lot of time during the week,
but to get that intimate time,
I got to cover
a lot of important topics
that I wanted to share with her.
And I did come home with a rose,
so I feel like our relationship
definitely progressed this week.
So I'm happy about that.
- That's fantastic.
You guys want to talk
about this week?
Yeah.
- It's a big one.
There will be two incredibly
romantic one-on-one dates.
There's gonna be one
with Rachel.
There's gonna be one with Gabby.
And there's gonna be
a rose on the line
at each of those dates.
- Whoo.
- Wow.
Let's go.
- There is also going to be
a massive group date.
Yeah.
- Prepare for anything
to happen this week.
Everything can change...
Like that.
For the first date,
got it right here.
This one's from Rachel.
Yeah!
- Have an amazing week.
Wish you all the best of luck.
And I hope to see you all
at the next Rose Ceremony.
Later, fellas.
- Thanks, Jesse.
- See you.
- I already know there's
an amazing connection
with Rachel.
I want to keep, like,
developing that relationship.
So I'm hoping for a one-on-one.
- All right, fellas.
- I am all-in on Rachel.
There's no question about it.
So I really want
this one-on-one,
like, more than anything.
- "Zach...
"Today is the beginning
of our love story.
Love, Rachel."
- Attaboy.
- My boy!
Whoo!
- I see you, man.
- How you feeling, man?
- I'm feeling great.
Like, pretty speechless, man.
Pretty speechless. Yeah.
- Yeah, she's one for one
for kicking people out, so...
Ooh. Ooh.
- You definitely want to hear
your name on that card
for the person that you're
kind of focused on.
So, yeah, I was hoping
it was gonna be me.
Unfortunately, it wasn't.
- I think it's about time
to get ready for that date.
- These one-on-one dates,
I think there's
definitely a new amount
of pressure.
I thought Jordan V.
Was coming back
after that first
one-on-one date.
He did not.
So you never know
what could happen.
So, you know,
you gotta be on you're A game.
- If Zach doesn't come back,
I think every single
one-on-one date card
we're gonna be praying
that it's not our name.
- Zach has a great connection
with Rachel.
- Oh, my God.
- Let's go.
- But at the same time, like,
she had a connection
with Jordan the first night.
And then bam, he's going home.
She might be using
these one-on-ones
as, like,
"I need to know right now
If I'm gonna like him
or he's going home."
- Today, I am really excited
for my date with Zach.
The first time we talked,
we had immediate chemistry.
But I don't really know
that much about him.
So today I really want to see
if Zach is here for me.
There is a rose
on the line tonight,
and I think
the stakes are pretty high.
- Oh, my God.
- Hello.
How are you doing?
We have
a really fun day planned.
Are you ready to head in?
- I'm excited.
- All right.
- Let's do it.
- But I actually don't know
what's happening.
I have enlisted the help
of someone very special today.
- Hey!
- Hello.
- Ooh.
- Hi, how are you doing?
Zach, this is Karamo.
- How are you doing?
- Hello.
Pleasure to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
- He is one
of my favorite TV stars.
You might know him
from "Queer Eye,"
but he's also an author,
a relationship expert...
- Oh, babe, you don't gotta go
through the résumé.
- And a culture expert.
- Listen, this night
is for you two.
I had to make sure
that I come here
to support her.
To make sure
that your relationship
jumpstarts on the right foot.
Listen, let's pop
some champagne, though.
You know what I mean? Come on.
- Please.
- I've been rooting for Rachel
from the first time I saw her
on the last season,
because she deserves love.
I mean, this is the first test
of a gentlemen.
Can you pop the champagne?
- Oh. Let's see.
- Okay.
- Okay, man.
No, I love Rachel so much.
So the fact that I get to set up
a date for her tonight
that I know is gonna be magical
and that's gonna surprise her
feels really good to me.
All right, so let me tell y'all
what I have planned.
So in my eyes,
you are a starlet.
Beautiful, gorgeous,
everything that we know
about old Hollywood.
That woman that we all admire.
So I actually have figured out
a way to get you all
into a very exclusive
movie premiere tonight.
I'm giving y'all that full,
Hollywood red carpet treatment.
- Amazing.
- Oh, my God.
- Yeah? Like a good date?
- I've never done it!
I've never been...
- Never been
to a movie premiere?
No, I'm so excited.
- I feel so good.
The best part is having Zach
by my side.
- Here you go, my love.
- Thank you.
This is a great date so far.
I'm excited.
- Today, the guys
are just at home,
so to be able to strengthen
these connections,
I would like more time
with them.
Hi.
- We know her.
Oh!
- Whoa.
- Hi!
- Yo.
- How is...
Oh, my God, you guys
just do this all day?
So cas.
What's so scary
about falling in love
is that you are making yourself
so vulnerable.
Surprise.
I don't want to date someone
who's not sure about me.
Hi.
So I'm really excited to see
who shows effort
and who's showing
they are here for me.
I know this can work.
I'm so excited for it to work.
Oh, my God, surprise.
- What's up?
- Nothing.
It seems like you're
enjoying yourself.
This is nice.
What do you do all day?
- This.
- Yeah?
- We eat food, work out.
- We, like, throw the football.
Tan.
- Like, this is most...
- Not throw the football.
- Yo, Ethan, throw the football!
- Ooh.
- Whoa.
- Oh!
- Fumble.
I know what that means.
- Every time you miss the ball,
it's a shot.
- Uh-oh.
- Hold up, this went crazy.
- Oh, God.
- I don't...
- Oh!
- That looked
like it was actually
coming in hot.
- Oh.
- Meatball.
- Oh, yeah.
- Oh, there it is.
That was a nice redemption.
I don't want to play anymore.
I didn't want to play to start.
It's kind of frustrating
the men aren't being
super forward with me.
- Good guy.
- That's pretty nice.
- Oh, you like it?
Bro, I got this
from Mexico, bro,
when I went on a wedding trip.
- Um, so...
There's some guys who
are just kind of proceeding,
like, blasé.
"Whatever, I get to date
two girls."
That's not what this is about.
And the lack of effort
is a decision at this point.
Like, it just doesn't show
initiative.
It doesn't show
that you're ready.
Oh, thank you.
- You have a great day.
I feel like
I'm giving so much to them,
and, like, they're not giving
everything back.
My expectations are so high
that I'm terrified
to be let down.
- Okay, I'm gonna be
real with you.
So there are two women
in the house now.
Like, there is Gabby as well.
How do you know if you have
feelings for her?
Like, is she completely
off the table for you?
It was crazy because I had
this feeling with you
almost right out the gate.
I felt that there was sparks,
or chemistry,
or whatever you want to call it.
And I just knew in that moment
it didn't matter that
there were two Bachelorettes.
Like, I...
I felt something with you.
And, um...
- Good answer.
- Girlfriend, if this
is not the one...
Like, literally, I'm happy
that I'm sending you
on this date.
This is gonna be good.
Thank God.
'Cause I was like,
who else we gonna get out here
if you fail?
So this is great
that you are doing so well.
- Oh, my...
- Exactly.
- This is a great day.
Rachel is beautiful and amazing.
This whole experience has been
something I couldn't
even have imagined.
There's a lot of emotion
and a lot of feelings
and new experiences.
- Come on out.
Ow!
All right.
- We kind of match.
- Roar.
- Ooh.
- It's not easy to open up,
and she's made it,
you know, so much easier
for me as I'm doing stuff
that's out of my comfort zone.
- Oh, my...
- Yes!
- Let me see.
- Look at you.
I think everything we've done
so far today
has made me feel
really confident
about moving forward with Rachel
and really exploring each other.
- Oh, yes.
- Oh, my God.
Tonight is a big, special,
VIP movie night for them.
I cannot wait to see them
strut their stuff
on the red carpet.
Three, two, one.
Come on out.
- Oh.
- Oh, my...
- You look good.
- Look at you.
- You like it?
- Oh, my... no, I love it.
Ooh, I love?
He loves it.
You look great.
You look very handsome.
- You look like a movie star.
- Thank you.
- Seriously.
- I think this might be it.
- I think this is it.
- This is it?
- This is it, yeah.
Wow.
- I have to say,
you both look gorgeous.
This is what I wanted.
These two look
really good together.
If all it takes
is for you to look good
to say it's a match,
my baby, this is a match.
- Right now,
I'm just kind of in my head.
Going to the house today
was kind of weird.
Nobody really showed initiative,
and I was hurt.
I was.
I deserve to be loved,
but do I deserve to be loved
by the person
I want to be loved by?
'Cause it seems like the people
that I wanted to love me didn't.
And I don't want to, like,
give my whole heart
to someone just to have it,
like, broken again.
But I know that it's, like,
with great risk
comes great reward.
- Someone at the door.
- I think because of everything
that I've been through,
I just feel my feelings
so deeply.
And it truly is
a blessing and a curse,
'cause I think
it hurts way more.
- Ah, there's the card.
- Oh, damn.
- Ooh.
- It's scary doing this,
like, week after week.
I don't know if I have
the capacity
to either keep breaking
people's hearts
or to potentially
have mine broken.
- "Erich..."
"Who said three's a crowd?
Love, Gabby."
- I'm ecstatic.
And I'm not gonna sleep tonight.
I'm super pumped.
- I think it does take
kind of the right person
to know how to love me.
We're in a limo,
drinking champagne.
- Only fitting to go
to a movie premiere
in Hollywood.
- Whoo.
Oh, my...
- "Me and You"?
- No.
- Wait...
- Oh, my God.
- Let's go.
- What?
- Rachel, Zach, look here.
- Let's go.
Let's go.
- Rachel, over here!
- Oh, my damn.
- Yeah.
- Oh, my God.
- Wow.
- Look here, Rachel.
Look here.
- Rachel!
- Hey, Zach.
- This is so incredible.
Having Zach by my side
is so perfect.
And he's just making me
feel comfortable
in a situation
I've never been in before.
- Kisses? Mm.
Oh, my gosh.
- I mean, it felt
like we were movie stars.
It was so fun.
Little twirl?
Ooh.
- Whoo.
- She was looking stunning,
as usual.
This all feels like a dream,
to be honest.
- Oh, my God.
- Oh, my gosh.
What's going on?
- I don't know.
- It's so quiet.
- Wait, are we sitting there?
Oh!
- Oh, my goodness.
What?
- "I hope this is the beginning
of your love story.
Enjoy the movie.
Karamo."
- Wow.
I can't wait.
- Oh, my gosh.
- This is crazy.
This is...
- We have
our own private viewing.
- Wow.
Oh, my God.
- Rachel!
- I'm speechless.
- I... I don't even know
what to say.
Watching the videos
of Rachel growing up,
was completely shocked.
Like, that's the last thing
that I expected.
- Say, "Congratulations,
Auntie Mary and Uncle John."
- Congratulations.
Oh, that...
- Oh, my God.
- That moment we shared
was something special.
And I got to see, you know,
what her life was back then.
And that's something
that not everyone gets to see.
And I didn't expect
anything like that.
Zach, man.
Zachary. Zach.
It's your first Halloween!
What do you think, Zach?
You having fun?
Hi, Zach,
just letting you know
that we love and miss you.
And we're so excited for you.
And you're really just looking
to find your true forever love.
But I hope you find someone
that loves you unconditionally
and is also your best friend.
Take chances,
but stay true to yourself.
And Twix and Bella miss you too.
Love you. Bye.
- When I see Zach's reaction
to his mom,
I'm, like, trying so hard
not to cry
because it's, like,
so beautiful.
Watching him as a child
and hearing his mom talk
about him,
I really just feel so much,
like, closer to him.
It's really special.
- My baby girl,
I barely got you back again,
and you're already gone.
But I know this time
you're gonna find the man
who's gonna capture your heart.
And when I see you next,
you're gonna have
the biggest smile
on your face
with a fiancé on the way.
And all I can do
is wish you the best,
all the happiness in the world.
So, baby, just live it,
love it, and have fun.
I love you.
Oh, my gosh.
- I'm, like, trying to not cry.
Like...
Wow.
You were a cute kid.
How did it feel, seeing that?
- Oh.
Obviously it stirred up
a lot of emotions.
Yeah.
I'm, like, the luckiest son
in the world, so...
That's so awesome.
- So I saw your mom.
Are you close with your dad
as well?
- Yeah, so I'm...
I'm very close, you know,
with my dad.
And, you know, one crazy thing
about this whole, you know,
journey is, you know,
he... he was an aspiring pilot.
He wanted to become
a military pilot.
He loves planes so much so
that when we were kids,
he would just drive us
to any airport...
- Stop.
- And we would sit...
- Are you ser...
- In the park... like,
a parking lot of an airport,
and he... we would just watch
planes take off and land.
And he would name
every single one of them.
- I did that with my dad.
- You're kidding me.
- No, I'm literally, like,
tearing right now.
- You actually did that?
- Like... yes.
That's...
I've never heard or met anyone
that's done the same thing.
That's...
- This is literally...
This is wild.
- Oh, my gosh,
this is just so crazy.
I feel like I kn...
Like, have spent
weeks with you already.
- Yeah?
- This has been so incredible.
- This has been absolutely
one of the best nights
of my life.
- Same.
- Tonight was incredible.
I really do believe
that we really did start
the beginning of our love story.
And...
I think Rachel could be
my future wife.
- I have a surprise.
- More surprises?
- Yeah.
Do you want to dance?
- This is crazy to say out loud
and actually think about,
considering how early it is,
but it's very real.
What's going on, it's very real.
I'm falling for her.
I'm falling for her,
really, really hard.
Um... yeah.
- Zach, will you accept
this rose?
- Absolutely.
- Okay, good.
Thank God.
- Absolutely.
I'm so relieved.
Coming into tonight, was seeing
if Zach and I could connect
emotionally.
And to see him get emotional
seeing his family,
I definitely think we have
an emotional connection,
a physical connection.
To be able to be blessed
to be in this position,
to find love again,
and to be experiencing it
with, like... like,
unconditional love
with someone like Zach
next to me is just
truly, like, so special.
This is all about finding love.
And it just feels like
a really, like, beautiful start
to, like, what could be
something really amazing.
- My journey thus far,
it hasn't been easy.
Going to the house yesterday
obviously backfired.
I left feeling upset and sad,
wondering if these guys
are truly interested in me.
But today,
I'm just looking forward
to spending time with Erich.
We always have
a good time together.
- This is a big day.
This is, like,
the make or break.
- I'm really excited,
but also a little apprehensive.
Will he be able to accept me
for me?
Hi!
- Hey, Gabby. Hey.
- How are you?
- Good.
- You look good today.
- It's good to see you.
Thank you. You do too.
Hi.
I feel like I live here.
- Erich's date card said
"Three's a crowd."
So who's the third, you know?
- Yeah. Yeah.
- I'm, like, getting
kind of nervous now.
Yeah, you should be.
The legend.
- Oh, hey, kid.
How you doing?
- You guys, I think you know
who this is.
This is my grandpa.
America's grandpa.
- Who are all these guys?
- Grandpa?
They're all my boyfriends.
- I was shocked.
I was like,
"No. There's just no way."
Have you got a date for me?
- , come on.
- This is about me.
- Oh, wait a minute.
- It's really about to be
a two-on-one
with, like, a family member.
This early.
Like, it's unprecedented.
- Yeah, all right, shall we?
Bye.
- Bye-bye.
- So you know what we're doing
buy I don't.
- I do know.
- I don't think that's fair.
- I know it's early,
but I think it'll be nice
to be able to see
how Erich interacts
with my family.
Let's hit it.
- Bye!
This is really beautiful
country, I've gotta admit.
- I know, it's so green here.
Grandpa John is really great
in so many ways.
He's been married
for 50 plus years.
So he's a great guy
to have around.
And he really loves me.
I really appreciate that.
- So my grandpa's approval
on Erich
will mean the world to me.
- So now you're living
here in California?
- Yeah, I just moved.
You should come hang out
with me in Santa Monica.
- What's in Santa Monica?
- Beaches.
- Good-looking chicks?
- Grandpa.
You are a pervert.
- I've never been
on a first date
where somebody's grandpa's
been there.
So it's definitely not natural.
But he's a really funny,
charismatic guy.
It is special that he's here.
Where do you think we are?
- I have no freaking idea
where we are.
Oh, what is this?
- Welcome.
- Thank you.
- My name is Kirsha.
I'm gonna be
your sound ceremony host today.
Before we get started,
I'm gonna do
an energetic clearing on you,
which just helps to release
any negative energy's
auric field.
- One of my favorite things
is a sound bath,
'cause it's very grounding.
- I'd like to invite you
to turn around.
- It's just what I need
to have a reset
to get myself out of my head.
I think I've personally been
a little overwhelmed
these last couple days.
- We're gonna start
with an intention-setting
ceremony.
- I can go first.
Okay.
Um, I would like to set
an intention of moving forward
in this journey with confidence
despite any fears I may have.
Because I truly believe
that the risk
is worth the reward.
Being the Bachelorette,
I've had so many doubts.
I've been scared as hell,
feeling that I'm not good enough
to be in this role.
- My intentions is presence.
Just being here in the moment.
- Being in love is so scary
because you're trusting someone
with your whole heart.
- So trusting myself
and my heart with Erich,
I think, is a big step for me.
- John, you're welcome
to rejoin us
whenever you feel ready.
- "Rejoin us" how?
Oh, jeez.
- What on Earth?
Interesting.
That was an interesting
experience, yeah.
- I thank you
for placing trust in me
to guide you
through this ceremony.
- I mean, at my age,
any new experience
is a good experience.
Not something
that I'd necessarily
ever have to duplicate again.
Okay, where's my beer?
- Wow.
Grandpa, I think
maybe we should do teams.
Let's see.
Hi.
Do you want to bowl
with my grandpa and I
- and my date?
- Sure.
Are you me?
- This is Julie.
- Julie?
- Hi, Julie. How are you?
I'm Grandpa.
- I'm Grandma.
- So I got a date. Ooh.
- That's right.
- We got this.
- Okay, here we go.
- Don't get any ideas.
Are you me?
I'm too old to have ideas.
- So far, today has been great.
And it really feels
like a normal family day.
Erich is rising to the occasion.
Oh!
He seems like he's into me.
Oh, my God!
It didn't feel
like a normal first date
where I felt
like I had to impress him.
It seemed like he was
really down with everything.
Just really easy to be around.
- This day has been, like,
a lot of fun.
It's been, like,
senior citizens bowling tour,
literally.
Yeah.
I think we have to have a moment
away from whatever that is.
I agree.
There's nothing like making out
in a bowling alley.
- With a bunch of teenagers
and old people.
All right, we'll keep it PG.
- It does make you feel
like a teenager.
It's kind of fun.
- I was lucky that we just,
like, have this connection,
we hit it off,
because I don't know
if I've had that with Rachel.
- Today with Erich
was definitely as good
as I hoped.
He did great with my grandpa.
You've got it.
- I'm, like... I come out of this
and I have a new grandma.
- He's like,
"I got a hotel room."
Right!
This week has been hard.
- Oh, my God.
- I know. Isn't this crazy?
- This is unbelievable.
- I've been in my head,
questioning everything.
- Is there another table
that Grandpa John's
gonna pull up with?
Yeah.
But I'm feeling, like,
overall good.
I know I do really have
a connection with Erich.
And I might not be
perfect tonight,
but hopefully he's patient
with me,
'cause that's the only thing
I can really ask for.
I had an amazing day.
- Me too.
- Cheers.
- Some parts were interesting
for me.
Yeah, same.
- Like, you really do make this
so easy.
And, like, I really just want
to value the time
that... that we have to see
if... if there is,
you know, a deeper connection,
if that is a possibility.
- Yeah, yeah.
- And, like, I know...
I feel like we're kind of
on the same page
where it's, like...
- Yeah.
- It might take a minute
to get there, but...
- Right.
- To know
the possibility's there,
like, that's what's exciting
to me.
- Yeah, totally.
A lot of relationships
is effort,
which people take for granted.
- Yeah.
- But...
- It's easy to give up.
- Yeah.
- And just to...
To just not, like, fight
through it.
And growing up, you know,
you see your parents...
- Yeah.
- And that was one thing
my mom said, she's like,
"I'll always fight for him
no matter what."
And, I mean, that...
- Have... do they, like,
ever not get along?
- Obviously, yeah.
- Have you... yeah.
- They fought all the time.
- Well, I don't know, like,
how much they, like, show you.
- So, like, my... my dad is
this, like, larger-than-life,
big personality.
Like, the most stubborn
son of a bitch
you'll ever meet.
- And my mom is this, like...
The hardest-working person
I've ever met
in my entire life.
- Mm.
- And they have this, like,
deep love.
I mean, they are
absolutely soul mates.
They're just, like,
the best team.
- Yeah.
- That I've ever seen. And...
- I know it's a lot to ask for,
but it's... that's, like...
That's what I want.
- Yeah.
I think it's important too,
'cause I think I still have,
like, fears built-in
that I constantly have
to, like, sit down,
assess, and fight.
And I'm reserved
to share that with people,
because I've been hurt
so many times,
like, by a parent.
- Yeah.
- And I think, like, that's
kind of the hardest love
to not ever have received.
- Yeah.
Growing up, my mom kind of...
We're estranged.
I don't have a relationship
with her.
- I'm sorry.
- She, like... no, that's okay.
Um, she definitely did
the best she could.
But the second I moved
out of the house,
she, like, wiped her hands,
like, clean.
So it... I mean, it is...
Like, I obviously get emotional
talking about it.
- Yeah.
- But it...
I'll, like, maybe never know
what it's like to, like,
have a mother's love.
And it's something, like,
that's hard and I'll miss.
Just give me a second.
- I'm overwhelmed.
What if I can't do it?
Like, people, like want
to see the Rachels
'cause she's easier.
I'm too complicated.
It's like, I'm messy.
I think, tonight,
the pressure of being
the Bachelorette just...
It really hit me.
Like, what did I get
myself into?
Can I do it?
Is it too much?
Can I truly find love?
It is, like, so hard for me.
I feel like I'm
incredibly different
than other women
who've walked in my shoes.
I don't always want to explain
my situation to people.
It's really, really hard.
And I can see myself
still having guards
and walls up,
because, um, I'm afraid of him
and what we might have.
But I think being able
to recognize it is...
Is the first step,
and then hopefully I can
move forward knowing that.
Thank you for everything
and being here.
There's, like, a big part of me
that worries
and is really scared
that, like, people aren't gonna
be able to resonate with me.
And when we sat down initially,
like, and talked,
I was really just, like,
so scared.
- Yeah.
- This is a huge honor,
and I don't want to it up.
And I'm not polished.
I'm not like anyone
they've seen in the past.
I'm not like Rachel.
Not that I'm comparing
myself to her,
'cause I think we're both,
like, very different.
But...
I didn't ever think
that this would really get
to me.
And then, I think this week,
like...
it's all landed so heavy.
Like...
Am I the right person,
basically, for this?
- Yeah.
- And I think there's
still lots of, like, navigating.
And I'm sure I'll, like,
ebb and flow,
but the last thing I want
to do is not be who I am.
- It sounds like,
from your situation, that you...
Like, you've become, like,
really in tune
with your emotions.
And, you know, you've had
a much different upbringing.
And I think it's shaped you
as a really unique person.
- Yeah.
I think it has truly made me,
like, the woman I am today,
which I'm really proud of.
- Yeah.
- But I do have
such a severely emotional side.
Like, maybe... I don't know,
even with my friends.
Like, with Rachel...
Like, when I love people,
I love them to a point
where it, like, literally hurts.
- Yeah.
- You know? But I think
I'm lucky
that because of my past
I have that capacity...
- Yeah.
- To be able to love
that deeply.
And, like, believe me,
I just want to have fun.
- I know.
- Like, you know,
forever and ever,
but, like, there's...
To you too, like, there's
so many different sides
that you just, like...
- I know.
- Want your partner to know.
- No, trust me. I know.
And I will be as open
and honest with you.
And I want you to do the same.
- Yeah.
- Because, like, I only have
so much time with you here.
And I... I really like you.
And I will not hold
anything back.
And as much as you want
out of me, I'm willing to give.
And I'm... I'm...
I'm here to see where this goes.
And I don't... I don't have
any expectations
or anything of you,
but I want you to be honest.
I think that's
why we're both here.
- Yeah, yeah.
- I'm trying to get
comfortable with it.
But seriously...
- Thank you for everything
and being here.
We can go get warm.
I'd love... love to.
I think tonight was, like,
a huge turning point in growth.
And, like, having...
Taking a break,
regrouping, and coming back,
we connected like I never,
ever, ever would have asked.
I didn't expect things
to be this hard this soon.
I really didn't.
But, ultimately,
I think it's left us
in, like, a way better place.
- Yeah.
So...
With that being said,
Erich,
will you accept this rose?
- I would love to accept
this rose.
- Today with Erich
was one of the best days
I've had so far.
My feelings for him get deeper
and deeper and deeper
every time.
And it's scary as hell.
Who knows what's to come?
I do just want to get
on your lap,
'cause I feel like
I can get closer to you.
Is that close enough?
- I'm the imperfect
Bachelorette,
but I think
in some people's eyes
it'll mean perfect.
And Erich, tonight,
really, really, really
really, really, let me
lean into that,
and understand it,
and be myself.
'Cause I would give anything
to be loved
by someone like Erich.
- Oh, my God!
- Hello.
- You guys look amazing.
- Thank you.
- So beautiful.
- Today's the 19-on-2 date,
the biggest in Bachelor history,
which is crazy.
- Today, no one is a bridesmaid.
Everyone is a bride.
- I think this week has
brought me so much clarity.
I am a little timid
about being the Bachelorette.
I have my own fears,
but I've been proven
with Nate and with Erich,
that one conversation,
one day can really change
your whole experience.
- Perfect.
- So today,
I'm hoping to see
these guys' personality
and to see how much effort
they're truly willing to show,
not just in the activity,
but towards Rachel and I.
- Whoa.
- Whoa, do you see that?
- Let's go!
- Oh, my God.
When I say Gabby
in a wedding dress,
my heart's, like,
beating out of my chest.
Like, it felt like
I was getting ready
to go into shock.
Oh! Oh, hi.
Wow.
- Hi!
- You look like
a Disney princess.
- Oh, my goodness.
- The date card said,
"Who do you picture
yourself with?"
- Hi.
- But they're both
great women,
and I'm like, it's completely
up in the air right now.
Ohh!
- I think everyone just saw
their wife for the first time,
so if anyone's confused,
they're a hundred times
more confused now,
'cause they look
absolutely beautiful.
Yeah.
- Yeah, we're so excited
for a fun day.
I think, as you guys know,
Rachel and I take this
very seriously,
so we're hoping today we can
see who we can
picture ourselves with,
and what better way than
a classic Bachelor photo shoot?
- Oh.
- We have a Bachelor legend,
icon and artist,
Franco Lacosta, to help us out.
- Well, I mean, first of all,
I'm here to help you
to really decide, who do
you picture your future with?
So this is gonna be
a lot of fun for me,
for them, for all of us.
And now it's time to play.
Yes.
- So go and grab your costumes
and get ready,
and give me some good stuff.
Hurry up.
Come on.
- I'm excited, 'cause I haven't
been on a date yet.
I haven't been on a group date,
haven't been on a one-on-one,
so this is game day.
Gotta be ready for anything.
- I'm... I'm right here. Damn,
bro, I got the short-shorts?
I've seen Franco from past
seasons of "The Bachelor,"
and so I think we're gonna be
pushed out of our comfort zone.
- No way.
- Bro, this looks crazy.
- Oh, my God.
- I just have this?
Guys, I got a leaf.
That's it?
- What?
- That's it?
- I think that in a group
setting, I do best.
What am I supposed
to do with this?
I mean, I got two switches,
on and more on.
- Franco had some
inspiration here.
I mean, I'm, uh,
dressed up
as a little kid today.
- Yeah, I'm a baby
for some reason.
I gotta put this on.
- Meatball was looking
like a big, hairy baby.
I never... I've never seen
a baby come out
with a beard and chest hair.
- There you go.
- We got Kirk, uh,
looks like he just got hit
by a semi truck.
We got some, you know,
some male cowboys,
"Magic Mike" looking,
but not so magic.
- It's a little breezy
back here.
I don't know if I'm a sexy
patient or a crazy patient.
All I know
is my ass cheeks are out.
I don't know what I'm
getting into, but I'ma own it.
I'ma own it.
I'ma make sure
I come out with a rose today,
for sure.
- You guys look amazing.
- They look incredible.
- I don't...
I feel like there's not...
- You guys look great.
- Enough to the imagination.
- No, no, no.
Of course, but I did want
you guys to look delicious,
and you look all yummy!
The first photo we're gonna do
is gonna be the car wash.
- A Daisy Duke car wash.
- And be sexy, eh?
Come on, get on each other.
Oh, I love that.
Oh, my God.
- Gabby, these boys are dirty,
dirty, dirty.
Clean them up.
- The car wash is hilarious.
I feel like the guys
are really embracing it.
- Oh, yeah, sexy.
Yes, oh!
Wash their scrotum.
Keep doing it.
It's beautiful.
- It definitely put the guys
outside of their comfort zone.
- It's okay.
- Aah!
Am I dilated?
- Do you see the baby?
- Oh, my God.
- Baby coming out.
- Oh, no, it's coming!
- It's coming? Oh, my gosh.
Rachel's the father.
First time in human history,
so exciting stuff.
I'm cramped... cramping.
- Ohh!
- It's kicking.
- Oh, no!
- We're delivering now.
Come on, baby Meatball.
Wah, wah, wah!
- I could see myself
having a child with Aven,
and I hope it looks
like Meatball.
- Guys, this is all
about the family, you guys.
Yeah, Power Rangers!
Yeah, this is beautiful
for Grandma.
- That's a beautiful family.
Aww.
- I'm team Gabby all the way.
She looks...
She looks really good,
and I'm just happy to see
that she's smiling
and having a good time
with the group date.
- Rachel is a badass pilot.
- Buckle up, everybody.
- Spencer,
grab her... ach... eat her face.
- I feel like I'm in
the Bermuda Triangle right now
because I was kind of leaning
towards Gabby, right,
but I... I think Rachel might
have been flirting with me,
and I don't think they know
who I'm flirting with
because I'm trying
to flirt with both still.
It's kind of a mess.
- I have three patients?
- Can you help me out please?
I picture myself with Gabby,
getting married at the end
of all of this,
so I think I need Gabby
to check my vitals.
- Oh, my God.
We have a rogue patient!
- The photo shoot
is so much fun.
These guys are really
putting themselves out there
and revealing so much.
- Hey, Jacob.
- I'm ready for my close-up.
- Wow.
- Whoa. Are you Adam?
- Amazing.
- Are you Eve?
- Yeah.
- Ohh.
- Amazing.
Just don't get excited.
We don't want this leaf
to fly away.
- So I got some forbidden fruit
that the ladies can have.
- Okay, you guys, look at me.
- I don't know if they're
gonna want it this early,
but it is tasty.
- Oh, exactly. So beautiful.
- Ah, there it is.
Ohh.
- I've seen Jacob's situation
multiple times today.
And it scares me...
- Whoo.
- Because I just can't
stop looking.
- Delicious.
It is the time
for the final shoot,
for the proposal.
Tino, come here.
Whoo!
- Logan!
- I'm sure Rachel
could be the one,
and I don't care if anybody's
looking, anybody's watching,
I'm going for it.
Rachel, the way I feel
with you I want forever.
Oh, my God.
- Amazing.
Okay, Logan.
- Rachel?
- Yes?
Are you gonna ask me something?
- Will you marry me? Yeah.
- My heart.
- That was beautiful, you guys.
Tyler and Nate.
- Yeah!
- Coming from a one-on-one
to being in a group environment
is a little bit more difficult,
but Gabby looks
absolutely radiant,
and I do miss her.
I think about her a lot,
just because
our first date was so good.
- Tyler, really just be
in the moment.
Take the time.
This is the picture.
- What?
- Oh, my gosh.
You look amazing, and, you know,
I've been waiting for this
moment my entire life.
- But as long as Gabby's
having fun, I really don't,
like, get jealous
because I know that, like,
we still have
our own connection.
- Nate, come on.
- And to me,
Gabby is like
a beautiful ray of sunshine.
- This is your time.
This is your moment.
This is the precedent
for the rest of your lives.
Let's do this.
- Aww.
- I am a thousand
plus a thousand
times a million percent
in on Gabby right now.
So just trying
to keep the spark going.
Your... your smile melts my heart.
- Aw.
- It really does.
Whenever you enter a room,
the world melts away.
The second I laid eyes on you,
I felt like I was meeting
my best friend,
and forever
could never be long enough
to just realize how beautiful
you are inside and out.
- Oh, thank you.
Oh, my God.
I feel a beautiful
connection here.
- Nate makes me feel special
in a way
that nobody else has here,
and right now I feel
so loved and seen.
I did it.
- So just having him
next to me today
honestly gives me a sense
of such solid ground.
Its' really such a good feeling.
- You guys so beautiful.
- And other men really
just are showing initiative,
which gives me so much hope.
- Have a wonderful time.
Enjoy the after-party.
- So I can't wait for tonight.
I know it's gonna be
really incredible.
Bye, you guys.
- Whoo!
- See you soon.
- Wow.
- Oh, my God.
- We're at SoFi Stadium,
where the LA Rams
and the LA Chargers play.
The newest, nicest, you know,
insane NFL stadium there is.
- Wow.
- And it's like, the lights,
two gorgeous women, 19 guys.
- Let's go!
- Every guy was feeling
that tonight may be
the biggest night
in Bachelor Nation history.
- Hi.
- Here we go.
- You know,
being here for a date
isn't something you get
to do every day.
- Hi, how's it going?
- But the one thing I want
tonight is a rose from Gabby.
That's all that's on my mind.
- Let's go.
- The group date today really
was so great and so special
because it showed me
that I'm building
really strong connections
with these men,
so I know tonight is going
to be so amazing,
and it'll be nice
to strengthen the connections
that I think I have
and maybe discover ones
that I didn't know I had.
- You guys truly did
show up today for us,
and you continue
to put yourself out there,
and it really doesn't
go unnoticed.
So cheers to you guys.
Cheers.
- I'm super excited
about tonight.
Gabby and I discussed this week
that we would really like
to start forming
some really strong connections.
Look at that.
Look where we get to talk.
- And today I was very
impressed by a couple of them,
and I'm excited to see how
they take that into tonight.
- Yeah, today was fun.
I, um...
I feel like today, like... like,
I saw a different side of,
like, how we can be, like,
be funny and be silly.
- I know, and I, like,
need that.
- Yes. Like, I saw
the romance part in this.
Like, that is, like,
without a doubt,
but today I was like,
wow, I can, like,
really see you, like,
as a best friend too,
and, like, that's,
like, so important to me,
to have both,
you know what I mean?
- Me too.
- So I'm happy that...
We got to do that.
This is so, like,
high school movie.
Like, we're on a football
field right now.
I feel like, like,
the star quarterback.
- Do you want to teach me
how to play football?
- Okay, we can... yeah.
I'll teach you
whatever you want.
Where am I going?
- Let's see how far I can throw.
Ready?
- Yeah.
Oh, my.
Good toss.
- I'm pretty good.
- I'll hike it to you.
- All right.
- Hopefully my pants don't rip,
'cause they're kind of tight.
- Good?
- Yeah.
- Blue 42?
- Oh, you're running?
- My time with Aven,
running around SoFi Stadium,
it really feels
like a crazy experience,
and I just feel like
our connection gets
better and better.
And to lay down in the endzone
with him, making out,
it's just a...
It's really amazing,
and I'm ha... I'm having
such a great time.
- I kind of missed you.
Oh, my goodness.
- I don't know if it was that...
I mean, I kind of
told you last week.
- Mm-hmm.
- I was like, I'm here for you.
So there's something
I've been wanting to do.
Sometimes you got
to create a moment, right?
- Yeah.
- So...
- So far there are guys
stepping up tonight,
and I am so blown out of the
water by some of these guys.
- I have a secret.
- Okay, I wanna hear.
- I'm a hundred percent certain
I'm only pursuing you.
- Tonight is, like,
out of a story book.
I feel so lucky to have
the connections that I do.
I haven't seen her in a while,
but I hope Gabby's doing well.
I know she was really excited
for tonight,
and I'm hoping she's making
as many connections
with some of these guys
and really starting
to feel really strong feelings.
- So how are you doing?
- I'm good.
How are you?
- I'm really good.
- Mm-hmm.
- Um, I kind of, like, wanted
to talk to you about today.
It was obviously
an odd situation
because Rachel was there
and everything.
- Yeah.
- And, uh, you know, I...
I just felt, like, a really
good connection with Rachel.
Like, amazing one,
and, you know,
I... I really do want
to pursue that.
- Yes.
- And I want to be straight up
with you, and I wanted
to tell you that...
- I really appreciate it.
- 'Cause I respect you so much.
- Yeah. No.
- And you're on your journey
and everything.
- Yeah. Yeah.
For sure.
You should tell Rachel.
- Yeah, no, absolutely...
- Did you already? Yeah.
- I... I didn't get a chance
to talk to her yet.
- Yeah.
- But I really wanted
to tell you first.
- No, thank you.
Naturally,
there are gonna be men
that gravitate more
towards Rachel.
Tyler is really sweet.
He comes from such
a genuine place,
and he's very respectful,
and I truly just think
he's being honest,
and I appreciate it.
How are you?
- I'm good.
Honestly, today was a blast.
- Mm.
- You know, I-it's funny,
'cause obviously,
I'm not a model.
Right, I'm not...
- I don't do funny.
- You have a great bod.
- I appreciate you.
I really do.
You know, and obviously
I wanted this time to, like,
talk to you and kind of...
Kind of, like, give you
a little bit more insight
on my intentions
and things like that.
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Today gave me
a lot of clarity.
- Mm-hmm. Oh, good.
- Okay,
and, you know,
I... I looked at that today
and my own life and, like,
what my values line up with,
and, you know,
I do have my intentions
fully for Rachel.
- Yeah.
- And I think you have
the bubbly aspect to you,
the... the goofy aspect,
and you're a little bit
more, like...
I don't want to say
rough around the edges,
but y'all want people
to be very direct with y'all,
and so obviously
I wanted to make sure
that I expressed that to you.
- Yeah, totally.
- You're the best.
- Oh, you are.
Lo and behold, I've been
freaking out all week
that I'm not good enough
to be the Bachelorette.
- Appreciate you.
You do look great tonight.
- Thank you.
And then Hayden tells me
he feels his morals
more align with Rachel,
and being called
"rough around the edges,"
like, definitely hurts.
That's my fear.
- Um, I really wanted
to talk to you because,
like, I think we can, like,
joke around and just be, like,
funny and... and just
cause a ton of laughter,
but I don't know if maybe
we've had the connection
that I think I wanted to have...
- Yeah.
- With you from the...
From the get-go.
- Mm-hmm.
- Like, I think, like, even if...
Like, say if you were
the only person here,
I don't think I could have
the heart to continue,
because at the end of the day,
we're trying to find somebody
for the rest of our lives.
- Yeah, absolutely.
- You know what I'm saying?
- Mm-hmm.
- But obviously, like,
you're smokin'.
Yeah.
Well, shoot.
I... I'm happy that...
- Yeah.
- I'm happy we got
to have this talk though.
- Me too.
Yeah
- Bye, Gabby.
- Okay.
- All right.
Well, hey, cheers?
- Yes, of course.
- To finding our future person.
- Of course.
Yeah.
- All right. Cool.
Let's get back in there
and have some fun.
Yeah.
- I think these guys
coming to me saying that,
because I'm different, they
don't want to be with me is...
Like, validating that
I'm maybe too much for people.
- Is this where we're sitting?
Do you know?
- Yeah, is that... yeah.
- Ultimately, like,
yeah, it hurts to hear,
but, like,
I'm sure Rachel is going
through something similar.
- I'm here for you, and, like...
- Thank you.
- I think you're beautiful
and...
- I do feel like
we have a connection.
- That makes me feel amazing.
I'm so glad you said that.
- You know, I'm...
I'm so different
than another Bachelorette,
so my biggest fear was being
too rough around the edges,
and now I am that for people.
- I think Gabby's amazing,
but you're definitely
more my type.
- Well...
- Like,
when it comes down to it,
like, I want to be
rough around the edges.
'cause I know who I am
on the inside,
and I'm proud of it.
- Hello.
- Whoa.
Hello.
- Hi, guys.
Tonight was really, really good.
A lot of guys have let me know
where they stand tonight,
which is a really good feeling.
And I'm so excited
to hand out a rose.
- Yo, where's
your partner in crime?
- I don't know.
Where is she?
You guys do something?
- Oh, there she comes.
- This is a very
dramatic entrance.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
- How are you?
- Hi. Good.
How are you?
- Good.
Well, thank you guys
for such an incredible day
and an even better night.
I had so many amazing
conversations tonight,
but unfortunately,
this can only go to one person.
This person continues to make
me feel really seen and safe.
Aven, will you accept this rose?
- Of course I will.
- Whoa.
- Today, the photo shoot
with Gabby was magical
and kind of reaffirmed
my feelings and emotions.
I already know
I see a future with her.
So I definitely have my eye
on the Group Date Rose.
- Um, I think you guys are
getting a feel of who I am,
and I... I think I've
been open with some of you
about how I've had, um,
kind of a difficult week
coming into myself in this role,
and tonight has kind of
been hard for me in ways.
So I feel like I can't
give a rose tonight.
So I think we can say goodbye.
Hi.
- What's wrong?
- A couple guys just had
some choice words
that didn't sit right
with me tonight.
- What do you mean?
- Like, Hayden told me
that I was rough
around the edges.
What the?
- And Jacob straight up told me
that if I was here by myself,
then he would leave.
- What the?
- Are you kidding me?
- No.
And, like, I was hurt.
- So, like,
did you talk to Jason?
- No. I just had a breakdown.
- Oh, my God.
Gabby, come here.
- Yeah, I feel good,
but obviously that was tough
to see Gabby not hand out
a rose to anyone here, so...
- For sure.
- Did, uh... did, uh, you talk
to both tonight?
- Uh, I did.
- Wow.
- I did. I did.
- Hayden, could you please
explain your conversation?
Like, I want to know
what the hell happened.
- Yeah, I just told Gabby
that, um,
respectfully, my intentions
were to pursue Rachel.
- What did she say?
- She respected that,
so in... in my eyes, this
was a positive step forward.
- Honestly, you can't...
What do they think,
insulting one of us is...
Is gonna make
the other li... like...
- Mm-hmm.
- Like, because there's
two of us, they think
they can act that way?
- Yeah.
- Do you wanna address it?
- No.
- Like, do you want me
to address it?
- No.
- Okay.
Whatever you need.
- Yeah.
- And we'll talk tomorrow.
- I love you.
- All right, I love you.
- I'm here to find
a lifelong partner.
I'm not here to teach dudes
how to act.
- I'm gonna kill 'em.
- I know that they know
that something's up.
I think that they'll have time
to reflect on their
and figure out what happened.
But for me, I kind of don't
know how to proceed
or if it's gonna be okay,
so something has to change.
- How are you feeling
after everything?
- You know, the big thing
that happened last night
that kind of shook me
a little bit,
and I'm sure
would have shook you,
was how the night ended
with Gabby.
As I was walking out,
I actually passed Gabby,
and she... it looked
like she was crying to me.
- Bro, her not giving
a rose out,
like, that was tough to watch.
She's clearly feeling
some type of way
or upset about something, so...
- Jacob's like,
"Yeah, me and Gabby
ended our relationship."
- Jumped ship, yeah.
- And then Hayden was like,
"Well, yeah, I talked to Gabby,
and told her
that I'm going for Rachel."
- You know, that could, like,
mentally
mess with you a little bit.
- It's just upsetting
to see someone who seems
so comfortable and strong
to be in a place like that.
- To go into that night
thinking that, you know,
I've got another rose,
there's another potential...
- Yeah.
- To find someone you want
to spend time with
and leave that upset,
is... like, that's horrible, so...
- Yeah, and it probably is...
Goes a lot deeper than...
Than we even know.
- Yeah.
- Last night,
when Hayden came up to me,
and when I heard, you know,
"You're rough around the edges,
and I... I want to be
with someone different,"
it just, like,
struck the deepest chord,
and I literally didn't know
if I could continue doing this.
- Yeah.
I am so sorry
that you even had
to feel that way last night.
I'm so proud of you
for even coming out
and just saying you weren't
gonna give the rose.
- I think what happened
last night,
you know, with Hayden and Jacob,
is that they like the feeling
of being able to,
in a sense, reject one of us.
- Mm-hmm.
- And it is a way
of self-preservation, um,
for them to be like,
"I... I have another option."
- Frankly, it doesn't matter
at this point
really what they think...
- Yeah.
- Because it is our journey.
- Of course no one has
put me in the position
that you were in,
and I can't even compare it,
but I definitely agree
that we wanted to feel chosen,
and we wanted
to kind of let them...
- Mm-hmm.
- Lean either way,
but it turned
into something ugly.
It is just so messy.
- Yeah.
- And we can't move forward.
If we don't make a change
right now,
I think it could really end
in a disaster.
- Yeah.
- Last night gave me a lot of
clarity with everything,
as far as, um,
who I'm pursuing...
Obviously, which is Rachel,
but obviously tonight's
a big night for everyone.
There's a Rose Ceremony.
- Right.
- And, uh,
my head's in a good spot.
- Yeah, for me personally,
I'm just a little disappointed
that I wasn't able to get time,
and so, you know,
I'm looking forward
to kind of getting time
with both of them tonight.
Tonight's a big night.
It's huge.
And for my personally,
I'm looking just for,
you know, more one-on-one time
with Gabby and Rachel.
You know, I still haven't
decided which one I want to,
you know, spend all my time
and energy with,
but, you know, hopefully
I can get some clarity tonight.
- Tonight is absolutely
going to be monumental,
in that I think they're looking
to kind of set in stone
who they want
to pursue relations with.
I just hope that Gabby
and Rachel get that clarity
and can move forward with this
without having to worry
about who's there for them,
who's not there for them.
That's just where I am.
- I mean, we all know
roses are on the line,
so I think this is
your last chance, you know,
obviously to make an impression
on one of these women.
I'm really pumped up,
to be honest,
and I can't wait
to get this going.
- Gentlemen, how we doing?
Everybody doing okay?
Um, I know I am not
who you were expecting to see,
but I do have some news for you.
I know you all were really
excited to see Gabby and Rachel
tonight at the cocktail party...
but that's not gonna happen...
Because the cocktail party
is officially canceled.
So you all will be moving
directly
on to the Rose Ceremony.
- Now what?
- Are you kidding me?
- That really isn't the only
thing I want to tell you all.
Rachel and Gabby have realized
that this whole thing
is just not working for them,
and to be honest, if this thing
continues to go down this path,
they're not gonna find love.
So at the end of the day,
that journey...
is over.
But that doesn't mean they're
just willing to give up.
This is how it's gonna work,
Gabby and Rachel have decided
that the best way
moving forward is to continue
on their journeys separately.
If you accept a rose tonight,
that means you are committing
to dating one woman,
that woman that offers you
the rose that you accept,
and not the other.
There will be one group
of men for Gabby,
and there will be another group
that is pursuing
and committed to Rachel.
Fellas, look,
this really could be
the biggest decision
of your lives.
I'll see all of you
at the Rose Ceremony.
Good luck.
- Well, that was a big shock.
Holy.
- Cocktail party is canceled.
I did not see this coming.
This was time that I needed
so I can speak
to both Gabby and Rachel
and kind of get, you know,
that clarity from them as well.
So I don't know what to think.
- It just goes to show you,
you should act on something
when you feel it.
I'm gonna follow my heart
the best I can, and, uh,
if I'm lucky enough
to receive a rose,
I'll act according
to what my conscience tells me.
- I think the guys tonight
that are on the fence,
the... the pressure's
gonna be put on them.
Obviously, these guys
are really gonna have to
figure out, you know,
who they want to pursue.
- At this point,
I've committed to Rachel.
Hopefully Rachel feels
the same way I do.
- We do owe it to the ladies
and to ourselves
to kind of make that decision.
You know, if this helps prevent
another night like last night,
like, you know, I'm all for it.
- They have their mind made up.
So if you haven't done
what you needed to,
you're gonna go home.
- Guys are losing their marbles,
and we're gonna see
how this night's about to go,
but I can tell you right now,
this will be
the craziest night
in Bachelor Nation history.
- Tonight is a Rose Ceremony,
and Rachel and I decided
that we are giving out
our own roses
to the individual men
who will agree to come
on our journey separately.
We overcame so much
on our previous journey with
Clayton in our last experience,
but I think we have
to kind of be brave enough
and separate at some point,
and this Rose Ceremony
is the beginning of that.
- You weren't there last night.
I'm... all right,
so this what happened.
- Tell me the vibes, bro.
- Yo, it was so bad.
Like, she's probably
so upset right now.
Myself and Zach are in
the winner's circle for Rachel,
and Erich's in the winner's
circle for Gabby,
so we're kind of just
sitting around waiting
to see who comes out
for each side
and kind of take it from there.
This is probably gonna be
a pretty stressful, uh...
Stressful Rose Ceremony.
- This is what I'm worried
about is,
people will be, like, you know,
"If I get a rose from
this person, I'll say yes."
When the time comes to it,
when you're standing up
in front of that, you know,
woman that maybe you didn't
exactly expect,
will they stick to their word?
I don't know. That's tough.
- I know.
- And I hope they do,
because you're playing
with their heart.
- Gentlemen, welcome
to your second Rose Ceremony.
I know it's not
what you expected.
I'm sure by now you've noticed,
there are two pedestals
with roses.
Rachel and Gabby have each
individually decided
which men they want
to continue dating.
I really hope that each of you
has given strong consideration
with respect
to where your feelings lie.
Do you see a future with Gabby?
Or is it with Rachel?
I wish you all luck.
- I am excited to finally
go on my own journey
and for Gabby to go on hers.
I feel confident in the group
of guys that I want to pursue,
but I'm really nervous
for Gabby,
because I definitely didn't see
what happened
last night happening.
I know that I would be
so shocked
and so hurt
if that happened to me,
and if someone were
to reject her rose tonight,
this could end in disaster.
- Thank you guys all
for being here.
I know it's been a crazy week.
I think having
two Bachelorettes has
provided struggle
that nobody could prepare for.
Personally for me,
some conversations last night
were hurtful
and the impetus that we needed
to move forward
in our two separate journeys.
- So with that, we can begin.
Tino.
Tino, will you accept this rose?
- Absolutely.
I knew it.
- Hey, shh, shh.
Hey, calm down.
- Nate.
Nate, will you accept this rose?
- Absolutely.
What's up, E-Money?
- Nate.
It's Nate.
- It's Nate.
- I'm excited
to get a rose from Gabby.
I feel good with our connection
right now,
but, um, I hope Rachel gets to,
you know, choose the people
for her as well.
- Logan.
Logan, will you accept
this rose?
- Yes.
- Welcome to the club.
- I'm curious to see
if anyone says, like, no.
- Yeah.
- Johnny.
Johnny, will you accept
this rose?
- Of course I will.
- So far tonight has been
going really well.
I think this is a great thing
that Gabby and I are getting
our actual own love stories.
- Oh, here comes somebody.
- Johnny, for sure.
- Good.
This is... this makes sense.
- This journey, it's...
It's not the beginning anymore,
and I really hope we can start
getting to that point
and really getting more clarity
on who our husband is.
Termayne.
Termayne, will you accept
this rose?
- Look, I don't want
to be the guy
to first decline the rose
of the night,
but I am gonna have to decline
the rose.
I feel like we could
be great friends
outside of this, obviously,
but I feel like I have
a deeper connection with Gabby.
- I am gonna have to decline
the rose.
- Gentlemen, ladies,
all right,
just want to clarify here,
'cause obviously
this is all new,
you declined Rachel's rose.
- Yes.
- All right.
Because you're holding out
for Gabby?
- Mm-hmm.
- All right,
I think what we need to do
is put Termayne back in line
and then find out if Gabby's
gonna offer you a rose.
- Okay.
- It looked like Termayne
got up and then came back.
Yeah?
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Did he turn down a rose?
- Oh.
- People might have
turned down a rose..
- Now Rachel, I'm so sorry,
but because Termayne rejected
your rose,
you can no longer offer
that rose tonight.
Now, Termayne, you've made
your intentions very clear.
You wish to pursue Gabby.
But Termayne,
if you do not receive a rose,
you will be leaving us tonight.
Thank you all.
- Termayne rejecting my rose
was so embarrassing
because it was
in front of everyone.
It was not only embarrassing,
but just really surprising
because I didn't think
him and Gabby
had that strong of a connection.
- Spencer.
Spencer, will you accept
this rose?
- Yes, ma'am.
- Getting rejected,
it's humiliating.
But I feel like I owe it
to myself to prove to myself
I can be strong enough
to hold it together
for the rest
of the Rose Ceremony.
Alec.
Alec, will you accept this rose?
- Um...
unfortunately,
I don't think I can.
Uh, I just don't think
I'm the right one for you.
- That's okay. Thank you.
- Thank you, Rachel.
Pleasure to meet you.
- No one else has came out here.
- Are you catching that...
- Jesse just walked in.
Jesse just walked in.
- Are you hearing that?
- Rachel, I'm sorry again,
but I do have to take your rose.
- What?
This is weird.
- I think, you know,
looking around,
everyone just kind of had
this feeling of, like,
oh, my gosh, what is happening?
Like, you know,
just because it's awkward.
- Jason.
Jason, will you accept
this rose?
- I would love
to accept this rose.
Get closer.
Thank you.
- Tyler.
Tyler, will you accept
this rose?
- Absolutely.
- When I first found out
I was the Bachelorette,
the first thing
my parents said to me was,
"Can you handle this
emotionally?"
- Mario.
- When they said that,
I was like, I'm so strong.
I can do this, of course,
but what if I'm really not
strong enough to do it?
Like, maybe they were right,
maybe I can't do this.
Maybe I shouldn't have done it.
Ethan, will you accept
this rose?
- Absolutely.
- I feel terrible for Rachel
because I know what it's like
getting rejected by these men.
Kirk, will you accept
this rose...
- Yes, absolutely.
- Last night, I did allow
some of these men
to make me feel terrible
about myself.
- Jordan, will you accept
this rose?
- Always.
- I know what it's like
to wonder,
what's wrong with me?
Can I actually do this?
What if it happens again?
Quincey, will you accept
this rose?
- Of course.
- I think that has to be
what's going on
in Rachel's mind right now.
- Meatball.
Meatball, will you accept
this rose?
- I'm sorry, um, I cannot.
I'm here for Gabby.
Um, I just have to go
with my heart.
- Okay. I appreciate it.
- I'm sorry.
- No, thank you.
- Did somebody else say no?
- Meatball just rejected Rachel.
- All right, boys,
what is going on right now?
- My brain is spinning
right now.
- Dude, the girls
just walked out.
The girls just walked out.
Like, it's...
- But that doesn't...
I can't. Like...
To hear three people,
one after another,
stop me and say,
"I can't accept this rose,"
it was so humiliating.
It was the hardest moment
I've had
as the Bachelorette, truly.
Yeah, it just is hard
because the whole time,
I just thought, like, you know,
it didn't work out
with Clayton, and I didn't
ever expect to be Bachelorette.
I didn't.
- Rachel, Gabby,
it's the final rose tonight.
When you're both ready.
- And so it's just hard
to, like,
really feel like I deserve it,
'cause I never feel like I did.
And then to be rejected again
multiple times
after you already feel
like you don't deserve it,
is hard.
I feel so lucky to be here.
Like, I'm lucky
to be standing next to Gabby,
and I still feel that way, I do,
because she deserves it.
- Michael.
Michael, will you accept
this rose?
- Yes, I will.
- To find love
is what I'm here for,
but if I get rejected
one more time,
I am ready to walk out
and leave.
I'm ready to be done,
go home to Florida.
I'm... why am I here?
Hayden.
Hayden, will you accept
this rose?
- Absolutely.
- Gentlemen, I'm sorry.
Please take a moment
and say your goodbyes.
- Thank you.
- Thank you so much, Termayne.
I really respect you.
Tonight was a little awkward
at times,
a little rocky at times,
but I think for kind of the
first time in this journey,
I feel like I am in control.
We made it...
Barely.
Walking in and seeing
my nine guys waiting for me,
I just feel elated.
I feel like good things
can come out of it,
and just so excited
for what's to come.
Here's to love.
To love.
- To love.
- Coming up next week
on "The Bachelorette"...
Ohh!
- Paris is romantic.
There's something in the air.
- Paris just does something
to you.
- There's gonna be two
separate groups now.
We're on two separate journeys.
- Love to you is just
the ultimate thing,
and that's exactly how I am.
- I never thought I would
be able to find someone,
and, like, now it's right
in front of my face.
- Every time I'm in the same
room as Gabby and Rachel,
I realize my feelings
toward Gabby.
- He made a vulgar comparison,
something about,
"I don't trust these bitches."
- I've tried hard
to put my feelings aside,
but the heart wants
what it wants.
- Every single day's
like a roller coaster.
- Why does she look pissed off?
- Do you know why I'm talking
to you right now?
- The shock on their faces,
no one even knew
what I was coming from.
- Tonight, Rachel was given
some information
about some things said
that was really disturbing.
- I hate every single day
having to get
to the point
of wanting to leave.
I'm just so over this.
I'm so done.
- When Rachel offered me a rose,
I just think I...
made a decision, you know,
in the moment,
and immediately when
I said it, I regretted it.
I think I did make a mistake.
Hey, Rachel?
Could I talk to you
for a second?
I just feel like there might
be something there.
I just...
you know, I spent more time
with Gabby...
- Mm-hmm.
- So I think there was, like,
an immediate kind of
connection there,
and we just didn't get
that one-on-one time.
You know, I was trying to get
to talk to you, but...
I feel like we just never got
that opportunity.
- Yeah.
- But I... you know,
I... I really wanna, you know,
get to know you.
- Yeah.
- I think there are feelings
that I have for you.
- Yeah.
- I don't know how you feel
about me.
- I gave you the rose.
I know.
We haven't really had
that much time to talk.
- Mm-hmm.
- Um,
I think you're
incredibly beautiful.
- Thank you.
- I love your personality.
- And I'd love to just kind of
give it another shot.
What... what do you think?
>>>>oakislandtk
www.opensubtitles.org