Tonight
on "The Bachelorette"...
Oh, my God!
I am so excited
to meet families
and deepen our connections.
- I'm happy you're here.
- Me too.
It really feels like
a taste of the future.
This is the best day ever.
I'm in love with you,
Rachel, so...
I have been
falling in love with you.
I feel so happy.
I just feel sorry
for those other fellas.
That's all I can say.
[laughter]
It's scary to, like,
open up and to show somebody
my entire world.
I'm terrified because I know
how much I have to lose.
Just trying to stay true
to myself.
It's important
to keep in mind,
what would it be like
without her?
It makes me cry.
I just want to know that
he found what he's looking for.
When you know, you know.
We're gonna have to have
a talk.
You're living like
a fairy tale right now.
I mean, you're saying
all the right things,
but I want to see him fall
for the right person.
I don't know how I made it
out of that house alive.
I almost cried.
I feel bad not saying
all this to you earlier.
I care about him so much,
and then I hear that.
I feel like
my heart is breaking.
[♪ ♪]
♪THE BACHELORETTE♪
Season 19 Episode 07
Episode Title: "Week 07"
Aired on: August 22, 2022.
[upbeat music]
[♪ ♪]
The past couple weeks,
Gabby and I have been
traveling around Europe,
sailing on this ship.
It was just, truly,
the most romantic thing
I've ever experienced.
And now we are going
to be separating,
and I couldn't be more excited
for Hometowns.
I'm gonna be visiting Zach,
Tyler,
Tino,
and Aven.
This is
the most excited I've been
on this journey, definitely.
I know how much family means.
I'm only visiting three men:
Jason,
Johnny,
and Erich.
I'm sure
meeting their families
will bring out
different sides of them
that I can't wait to see.
It should really strengthen my
connection with each of them.
What are you hoping
to find out
as you meet all these families?
I truly just can't wait
to see where
all these guys have come from
and meet the people that are
most important to them.
Meeting families is huge
because when you marry someone,
you marry their family.
And if a family just
doesn't like you,
doesn't give you a chance,
or you don't see yourself
fitting in,
it's definitely gonna
make you wonder,
like, how is this
gonna work in the future?
- How are you feeling?
- I'm nervous.
Meeting parents always
scares the [bleep] out of me.
It always has, always will.
[both laughing]
Should we get you
off the ship?
- Yeah.
- America is calling.
Meeting the family is
pressure on any relationship.
These families know
that I'm still
actively dating other men.
But I'm hoping
that they at least
keep their hearts and their
minds open in meeting me
so I can make a decision
if I'm able to be engaged
by the end of this,
which I hope I am.
I am so excited
for my first Hometown.
And I get to spend it
with Jason.
[jazzy piano music]
[trolley bell rings]
[♪ ♪]
I'm so excited.
It's my first time
in New Orleans.
Vibes?
Ten out of ten.
I always knew there was
something special about Jason.
We both feel our emotions
very deeply,
which is why
I'm so attracted to him.
But there is a large part
of this process
that's making him
uncomfortable.
He is more reserved.
I don't think
it's a bad thing...
[laughing] Hi.
'Cause I do see a future
with him.
[both laughing]
Honestly, I'm just excited
to see different sides of him
and to meet the people
who love him so much.
How are you?
So much better
now that you're here.
- Welcome to New Orleans.
- Thank you!
- Amazing. Like...
- Yeah.
- Have you been here?
- No.
- No?
- I'm so excited.
- It's not Paris, but...
- Yeah, but it's close.
- There's French influence.
- It's the French Quarter.
Yeah.
My family's gonna love you.
Are they? I'm nervous.
I'm so excited
to spend all day with Gabby.
I'll take you
to Bourbon Street.
Have some drinks.
Show you the ropes.
It's been
the craziest journey,
and here we are
in New Orleans,
and, like, it finally just
feels like home.
[jazz band playing]
[♪ ♪]
Yeah.
[laughing]
- Come on, you're the dancer...
- No!
You gotta show me
how it's done.
- You're showing me up.
- No, you're a great dancer.
New Orleans, it's a place
that I've just fallen
in love with,
and it just makes me
feel happy
to share that with Gabby.
When I think about Gabby,
I get really excited
and there's just, like,
a true spark between us.
I just feel like
when we're together,
we just have an amazing time.
We gotta tip these guys.
[percussive big band music]
[♪ ♪]
- You need some beads.
- I know.
Why is there so many penises?
- 'Cause you're in New Orleans.
- [both laughing]
You want some beads?
- Yeah!
- Oh!
- Oh, that was a good one.
- You caught it.
Whoo-hoo!
I want to get an old man
to show me his [bleep].
Oh, this guy...
You want some beads?
You have to flash me!
Why not?
I'm so happy to be here.
100%, yeah.
It's so weird 'cause I was
actually gonna leave.
And then...
When?
Like, in the very beginning.
And then I was like,
I want to stay for you.
Oh. Thank you.
[soft music]
I know Jason is so sweet
and so sensitive,
so I imagine he learned that
from his family.
He is, you know,
a little more quiet,
so I don't know if they're
gonna be more quiet,
or if it's just specific
to him as a person.
My parents are separated,
so you'll be meeting
my dad today.
He's so important in my life,
and I'm excited for you
to meet him, for sure.
Me too.
So I'm just excited
to learn more about him
and finally meet his family.
It's really special to me.
Ah, I don't know
whether to laugh or cry.
[laughs]
- Hey, man.
- Hey.
- I love you.
- Love you.
Gabby... you don't get
the attention.
She does. That's for you.
It's so nice to meet you.
I'm so glad to see you.
Oh,
you're making me emotional.
You're so sweet.
Having my dad here today,
meeting Gabby, is so exciting.
You know, his opinion
means everything to me,
and it's gonna be
a really special day.
I haven't talked to you
or seen you
for six, seven weeks.
Tell me... tell me
the exciting adventures.
This has been
the craziest, most...
Really? Just because of
the environment and isolation?
It's just... I can't describe
how crazy it is.
Jason's character
shone through right away.
He has stood out
in such a special way.
I know he feels so much.
- Wow.
- Yeah.
You know, some people need
to wear their logo
and their brand on the outside.
Jason wears it on the inside.
[sniffles]
He's a good kid.
Good man.
- Yeah.
- I missed him.
Our family has always been
a very emotional family.
And Gabby said such
positive things about Jason.
Should we go chat
over there for a little bit?
Okay.
But I'm only hoping
for my son's happiness.
I think he's on
a very good path
if he continues
to grow like this.
So it's been
a great experience?
[laughs]
I mean, yeah, it's been
a crazy experience.
[both laughing]
But yeah.
Gabby definitely makes it
worth it.
Meeting my family
is a huge deal, and...
Yeah, that is.
That's a huge deal for you,
I know.
Yeah, and she's,
yeah, one of the funniest,
but, like, most genuine people
I've ever met.
And I feel like we,
this whole time,
have had this, like,
energetic connection
that, like, sometimes you don't
even need to say something.
- You just can feel it.
- I felt it.
I mean, when I got halfway
to seeing y'all at the table,
I got a little emotional
just thinking
this could be
my daughter-in-law, you know?
Well, we'll see.
I mean, Gabby seemed
very mature,
and I could feel her warmth,
her easiness,
and she's beautiful,
and you're projecting
happiness and calmness
and ease with it, I can see.
You've been nonstop smiling,
and I'm so happy
that I could be a part of it.
And no matter what,
I'll always support you 100%.
If it's the real deal,
I want to be the best man
at your wedding.
All right. [Chuckles]
My dad's reassurance
that he supports me
in whatever decision I make
means everything to me.
It's a special moment
that I'll never forget.
Not to let a good beignet
go to waste.
[laughs]
And tonight,
I can't wait for Gabby
to meet the rest of my family.
May the best days
of your past
be the worst days
of your future.
- Cheers.
♪ Hey! ♪
[blues music]
[bicycle bells dinging]
[♪ ♪]
I'm so excited
you're gonna meet
my mom, Karen,
my sister, Kelsey,
my sister's boyfriend, Brendan.
I feel like it's gonna be
a good night.
- Me too.
- I can't wait to meet 'em.
Best-case scenario,
Jason finds
the love of his life
and she walks through the door
with him tonight.
All right, shall we?
Going in to meet
Jason's family,
I know that Jason's
different than me.
But we do have something,
like, so unique
and so special.
- Ladies first.
- No, you first.
- It's your house.
No, this time,
you first, I swear.
Okay.
So of course I'm nervous,
because there's pressure
to get a family's approval.
- Yo!
- Oh, my gosh!
[sobbing]
- Oh!
- Jason!
[sobbing]
[soft music]
- All right, let me in.
- [laughter]
I'm excited for tonight
and also terrified.
You are so gorgeous.
'Cause at this point,
I know how much I have to lose.
I can't even describe
what we have gone through.
- Jason's been great. Yeah.
- Where have you been?
- He's been in a simulation.
- What?
Yeah, so, the first...
I mean, like,
the first two weeks,
like, I was so overwhelmed,
and, like, honestly,
- like, I was about to leave.
- Yeah?
And then
we genuinely connected.
Oh, my God.
So then Jesse came in
and was like,
"Hey, two of you guys
are going to Paris."
Just the two of you?
- Like, just a...
- Like a one-on-one date.
Wait, on a one-on-one date,
you went to Paris?
- Champagne tasting, berets.
- Yeah.
- Okay, so you say...
- You caught him
right before he was about
to leave.
- Yeah.
- She's amazing.
- Aww.
- [laughs]
- You're beaming.
- Sounds like it.
So actually,
Gabby, you wanna go chat?
Yes.
Jason's family is so sweet,
and I know how close he is
to his mom and his sister.
I know that he's reserved.
We've both recognized that.
So, you know,
I just wanted to know,
is he always like this?
Is it the environment?
Is it the scenario?
Just like, painting
a better picture
of who he is as a person.
All right, well, what dirt
do you want on Jason?
[both laughing]
- I'm just kidding.
- Everything.
I really don't
actually have anything.
- He just behaved and, like...
- You just giggled.
You know,
did everything right,
and I was like, "[bleep]."
[both laughing]
Um, but he really is
just the greatest person ever.
- [laughing]
- Aww.
- He really is.
- Yeah.
Do you think he's, like, ready
for a long-term relationship
and whatever that
might look like?
I think that, 100%,
I could see him
being ready for, like,
something serious like that
and, like, taking
the next step.
I just think he hadn't met
the right person yet.
- Yeah.
- So...
We both know we're kind of
different from each other,
but do you think,
like, he could be
with someone like me?
- Oh, 100%.
- [both laughing]
Sorry, maybe describe more
what you mean,
'cause I, like, think
you're great.
- Yeah.
- [both laughing]
Gabby is great.
I could definitely
see her, like,
being part of our family.
- It's like he's, like, glowing.
- Yeah.
It's weird, but it doesn't
feel that far-fetched to think
Jason might be ready
to propose
and that Gabby could be,
like, my future sister.
I think Jason and I
connect in the way
that we both feel
our emotions so deeply.
So deep.
And I hear
you're the same way, kind of.
- Yes.
- Yeah.
So I think that's what
led us to each other.
- Yeah.
- But I know we're different,
and that was
the most scary thing
about coming here today,
is that I didn't know
if you guys would think
we were okay for each other.
- What were you worried about?
- Like...
Like, I know he's a little
more reserved and stuff,
and I'm not,
so I don't know if you guys
think that is something
that he needs in somebody.
To me, I would see it
as a good balance.
Yeah.
You know,
the whole thing was such a...
It's so outside
of his comfort zone.
He was like,
"Mom, what if I found my wife?
What if I really found
my wife there?"
[both laughing]
I'm like, "It really...
"I mean, maybe?
- That'd be really good."
- Yeah.
When I saw you two together
I'm like, okay.
There's something...
I can... I feel something
really good between you,
I don't know.
It was really cute.
I mean,
it's really, really cute.
[both laughing]
I know I keep saying that,
but I mean it.
No, you're so sweet.
But I just want you guys
to have fun and be happy,
and I hope it grows
and I hope it keeps growing.
- Mm-hmm.
- And, of course,
I'm hoping for the best,
I'm hoping it turns out
the way I would love
for it to go.
- I really do.
- Thank you so much.
It means so much being here.
I got a really good feeling
from Gabby.
She was so warm and friendly
and I love the way
she was into Jason.
Best-case scenario would be,
he is truly in love with Gabby
and Gabby is truly
in love with Jason,
and they live
happily ever after.
Tell me everything.
Tell me what's going on.
I still can't process
what has happened.
I really can't,
but something about her
just, like, puts me at ease
in a weird way.
We, like, definitely connect
on, like, a deeper level,
like, and, like,
she just gets it.
Yeah, it's hard to believe,
- you know?
- It's weird.
- Like, how did...
- How could this happen?
Yeah.
But it seems like
it's happening.
I know. I don't get it.
[both laughing]
But, like, I'm trying
to stay true to myself
and, like, taking it
one day at a time
and not, like, rushing.
And I could never see myself
getting engaged.
It's just not realistic to me.
As much as you, like, you know,
have feelings for somebody
or whatever, like,
that's just not something
I can see myself doing
at this point.
Like, maybe it'll change in,
you know, the next two weeks,
but I need space to process
everything that's happened
- and, like...
- Right.
Right now, that's how I feel.
And it's scary.
Yeah.
So it's not...
- It's not her.
- It's not her. It's...
It just wouldn't feel right
to me, you know?
So you have or have not had
this conversation, you said?
No, not yet, but I will.
Okay.
So how would you feel
without her?
- I'd be really upset.
- Like, I'd be sad.
Okay.
So that's important
to keep that feeling in mind.
What would it be like
without her?
It makes me cry.
[sobbing]
Sorry.
[dramatic music]
I just don't want you
to lose something.
Like, you're so,
like, distracted
by everything around you
that you lose something that...
You lose something
because of the distraction.
Yeah.
I get overwhelmed
thinking about Jason
because I just want to know
that he's really happy.
I just want to know that
he found what he's looking for
and he feels
really good about it.
I love you.
I love you too.
But I hope
that they go down that path
and come out together.
Yeah, so we gotta
get out of here.
- Aww.
- But...
I loved having you both.
Yeah.
- Thank you.
- I'm so glad to meet you.
- Thank you for having me.
- I love you so much.
And I look forward
to seeing you again.
I'm really happy.
After today, I do feel like
I learned so much about Jason.
Seeing him with his family
made my heart grow so much,
and to know
that they do accept me
just, like, means
the whole world.
Love you.
My feelings for Jason get
deeper and deeper every time,
and I am head over heels
for him.
[♪ ♪]
I can see myself
with him forever
and excited for the future.
I'll miss you.
I'll miss you too.
We had an amazing time
together.
I am falling in love with him.
- Bye.
I've never felt
this way before,
and it feels like
I'm in a dream.
[soft music]
[♪ ♪]
Hello.
Hi!
Oh, my gosh. You're here!
It's so good to see you.
I feel amazing.
Rachel's gonna meet
the family tonight.
Oh, my gosh,
so good to see you.
Rachel meeting my family
is going to be
a huge and instrumental part
for her to understand who I am.
- [gasps] Stop it.
- [laughs]
On bikes again?
We're not
in Amsterdam anymore.
The last time I saw Rachel,
I told her
I was falling in love with her.
And this date
is incredibly pivotal.
I love this!
I could be getting on a knee
in a few weeks from now.
And I want my parents to be
just as ecstatic and happy
as I am.
- Where are we going?
- You'll see.
Rachel's been taking me
on all these incredible dates,
and now it's my turn.
I'm taking Rachel
on the most incredible
Hometown one-on-one date
that she's ever gonna have.
- Okay. So we're gonna stop here.
- Okay.
And we're gonna do
a little bit of trespassing.
Okay.
We're climbing up
this ladder right here.
[gasps] Stop.
[dramatic music]
[♪ ♪]
[laughing]
Oh, my God!
[jet engines roaring]
[sweeping music]
Oh, my gosh.
[laughing]
This is so surreal.
Oh, my God!
Zach and I have talked
about this memory
that we both shared
with our dads,
watching airplanes fly.
I'm so happy.
- You like it?
- Yes!
That's the plane I fly.
It's a moment
we both grew up with
and something we hold
really dear,
so to share that together
before I meet his family,
it's really special.
- I'm nervous, but I'm excited.
- I'm so excited.
Like, with tonight, you know,
meeting the family,
they're gonna have
a lot of questions.
- For sure.
- I mean, you know, they know
that... you know, what's later
down the road after this.
Mm-hmm.
I am gonna tell them
that I'm very much so
still and am, you know,
falling in love with you.
Because this means a lot
and you mean a lot to me.
- Yeah.
- So I'm nervous.
Don't be nervous.
But I'm so excited.
I'm so excited too.
It's incredible to hear
how Zach feels.
We have such a deep connection.
Tonight is a huge night.
Family is just so important
to both of us,
and, of course, I'm so nervous,
but I'm just really hoping
my relationship with Zach
can take off to new heights.
[jet engine roaring]
Home sweet home.
Oh, my God.
This is a potential family
she's marrying into.
Is she going to fit in?
We can be overwhelming.
Once she sees you,
she's gonna be terrified.
[laughter]
But they'll warm up, you know.
Yeah.
- Oh.
- Hi.
Both: Oh!
[laughter]
Hi, everyone.
I'm so excited.
Rachel is gonna be
meeting my mom, my dad,
my sister, my Aunt Nanette,
and Uncle Pat.
I mean, he's just as funny
as he is
in his shows and movies.
This is very important to me,
and I want their full support
and trust moving forward.
So how has it been?
I mean, wow, like,
in the first three minutes
or two minutes maybe,
there was immediately just...
- Wow.
- Really?
Like, crazy connection,
- and we had a one-on-one date.
- Yeah.
A big surprise
movie premiere.
But the movie premiere
was our childhood videos...
- Mm-hmm.
- A message from both...
- You were in it. Yes.
- Aww.
- We were both just crying.
- Emotional wreck.
It was, like... it was a lot,
and I can't wait for you
to get to know her.
Obviously see something in her,
and she is pretty incredible.
You look very,
very happy together.
Yeah.
I just feel sorry
for those other fellas.
That's all I can say.
[laughter]
I see him walking in,
hand in hand,
as if they had been together
for quite some time.
Rachel, how about you and I
go have a little talk?
Absolutely.
But I am concerned
that he will be brokenhearted
if it doesn't continue.
And I want to hear what her
expectation is of my son,
and I also want to hear
what my son's expectation is.
Oh, I'm so excited
to talk to you.
And I don't know
anything about you,
but I know my son
just is enamored with you.
Yeah.
But he's also got
an emotional side.
Yeah.
And so
I'm concerned about him.
Because all
the awesome experiences...
I mean, you go to the most
romantic places on Earth,
and you'll fall in love
with a monkey.
Yeah.
What attracts you to him?
I think immediately,
kind of like he said,
we did just have a connection
right off the bat.
Being able to watch that video,
we immediately started off
our relationship
talking about all of you
and talking about family,
and he got emotional.
And I feel like
that really was what solidified
just how great he is for me,
on top of everything
I already was learning
that day.
He's looking
for the soul mate.
Absolutely.
Let's get this life going.
Yeah, he was talking a lot
about you and your wife,
how you guys are still
very much in love, so...
Oh, yeah.
I know that he looks up
to you guys a lot.
I married my best friend.
She happened to marry
her best friend.
And that is what he's
looking for, and me too, so...
You know, you've had
an incredible marriage
for all these years.
Yours, dad's,
the family's approval,
that does matter,
and I do want you to always
be, like, upfront and honest.
I just knew
when I looked at your face,
I would know
how you were doing.
I just wanted to know
that you were okay.
I would see it, whether you
really were falling in love
or not, because I know you.
But we don't know her.
I've actually told her
I'm falling in love with her.
- You have?
- I have.
Oh, my gosh.
I can actually see
a future with her and...
I'm so happy for you.
- Oh, boy.
- So...
- I see it.
- I mean, I see it in your face.
I see... I see the love.
Are you ready?
- I think I'm ready.
- Yeah?
- You're gonna make me cry.
- I knew I was gonna cry.
- Sorry.
- You're gonna make me cry.
- It just...
- I think my biggest concern
is that there are other...
Other guys in the mix, so...
I could see it in his eyes.
I saw nothing but true love
and happiness,
and I've never seen him
like that.
- I love you, babe.
- I love you too, Mom.
- I missed you.
My biggest concern
is how fast
and how hard he is falling.
Knowing that he is
falling in love with you,
is that someone that you could
see spending forever with?
- Yeah, I truly would...
- This is so incredible...
I know it's a tough question
because I know
you have other dates,
but, you know, as a mom...
Believe me, I'm honestly...
Love him,
and I'm just worried.
- Yes.
- I'm so glad you're asking this,
because there are still
obviously other relationships,
but there are,
you know, things that he has
that truly no one else has,
and our relationship
is different.
I don't want
his heart broken, you know?
And no one ever wants that
to happen to your child.
Absolutely, yeah.
He's genuine,
and when he's sharing with you
and sharing his heart,
it is for real.
- What I love...
- Or when I'm with that person
that I want to spend
the rest of my life with,
I'm going all in.
That does leave you
susceptible to heartbreak
if the other person's
not, you know, the same way.
I'm aware you're in
a very strange position
and your heart might be broken,
but it might be filled
with awesome Rachel love
forever and ever.
You don't know how good
that makes me feel,
you know, hearing that.
I am very proud of you, son.
- She's incredible.
- Yeah.
- He just...
- He's just a great person, so...
And I want him to find that
from a person in love,
and the way I see him
talk about you,
I really believe he is
falling in love with you,
and for him to feel
that confident
in what both of you have,
we're gonna be
right there with him
and embrace you as part
of the family as well.
- That's so good to hear.
- Thank you.
And we're kind of
what you see is what you get.
- You know, not...
- I love it.
I think I have
the stamp of approval
from Zach's family tonight,
and his family
is so incredible,
and I could see myself
fitting in.
The opportunity to see him
in a new light
and through other people's
eyes is really beautiful.
[uplifting music]
- Hey! [Laughs]
- Aww.
Zach, will you accept
this rose?
I'm already crying. [Laughs]
Oh, my God.
Tonight,
I got to see my kid,
but more importantly, I think
I probably met his future wife.
I'm falling in love
with you.
I can't imagine going another
direction than with my son.
They just fit.
It was perfect.
Oh, my God. [Laughs]
You know you're not
married yet, right?
[laughter]
Tonight could not
have gone any better.
Everyone loved her
and she loved them.
- That was awesome.
- That was good.
[clapping]
Best-case happened tonight.
I've received the blessing
from my family,
and Rachel's the one.
It was unanimous.
They loved you,
and that meant a lot to me,
just hearing all the positive
things they said about you.
I mean, that was just
what I needed to hear.
And I can tell you that I am...
I'm in love with you,
Rachel, so...
Oh, my gosh.
[soft romantic music]
[♪ ♪]
I feel so incredibly happy.
- This is crazy.
Zach continues to say
every single thing
I've ever wanted to hear.
I can't believe
that he feels that way.
It just means everything to me.
I feel like this journey
is working for me.
- See you soon.
- I'll see you soon.
Bye.
Zach makes me so happy.
My feelings have
definitely grown for him.
I am falling in love
with Zach.
He is so perfect.
[upbeat music]
[♪ ♪]
[laughs]
Why are you laughing?
We're here
in Palm Beach, Florida.
And I'm about to meet
my man, Johnny.
Welcome to Florida.
This is the most
I've worked out...
- Wow.
- Since I've been here!
- [both laughing]
- Ahh!
Johnny's super hot.
He knows it, I know it,
you know it.
He makes me feel
so, so special.
- It's so good to see you.
- What's up?
- How are you?
- I missed you.
Johnny and I did have
a slower start,
but we do have this
really strong connection.
I think speaking with his
family will just give me
a better grasp of him
as a person and kind of where
he's at in his life right now.
What are we doing?
So I cannot wait
to show you my town.
But I miss my family and I feel
like it's been forever.
I think we should
see them first.
Oh, okay.
- Nervous?
- A little bit.
I don't know
what I'm walking into.
- Don't. You're gonna be...
- Your family?
- You're gonna love them.
- I feel amazing right now.
Here at Hometowns bringing
Gabby home, it's big,
and I'm nervous,
and it's my family.
This is the first time for me.
I've never sat down
and gone through questions
like this with my family,
so today's huge.
I think today's probably
the biggest date I've ever had.
Johnny doesn't give
his heart to just anybody.
No, he doesn't.
Bringing her back here and all
is gonna be a big thing.
- Yep.
- [door squeaks]
- Yo.
- Oh...
Oh, I knew it was gonna be...
[clapping and cheering]
- Sup, man?
- Everyone.
- How you doing?
- Welcome home.
Hi.
Today Gabby is gonna meet
my mom, Elizabeth,
- my dad, John...
- Nice to meet you.
Best friend, Perry,
my brother, Robert,
and his girlfriend, Jillian.
He's looking great.
Best-case scenario,
we have an amazing time.
My family loves her.
Getting on a knee
is a huge thing,
and so I need everything
to come together today.
What did you think night one?
- Night one?
- [laughter]
- Yes.
- Wait, I rapped.
I, like, put, like,
a couple words together,
and, uh...
[laughter]
No, no,
but it was really smooth.
It sounded better.
- So...
- I was gonna call it a poem,
but that would almost be worse.
It had rhythm.
- And you kept him.
- No, I did. Yeah!
- Unbelievable.
- He had confidence, rhythm.
The best girlfriend ever.
- Aww.
- That's what he always says.
It's so cute.
Meeting Johnny's family,
we start
telling stories right away.
I watch Johnny light up,
and he gets so excited.
I felt like I had
known them for years.
Gabby, would you like
to have a talk?
I'd love to.
This is how I am
with my family,
and it is comforting
and it's fun.
I noticed
when you guys are together,
it's pretty amazing for
such a short period of time,
the chemistry you guys have.
Yeah, no, he is one
who I've always known
I could be myself around.
He's always been
really sweet with me
and really opened up to me,
and we got so much closer.
I think it was
what we needed to know
that we could see a future,
I guess.
So I'm glad you said that
'cause my question to you is,
where do you see yourself
with Johnny?
Yeah.
If he got down on one knee,
I know the whole...
It is something that
we would have to talk about,
you know, which we haven't yet.
Of course.
But knowing that Johnny
and I have your support
- means a lot to me.
- Absolutely.
I know it means so much
to him.
I think you're great.
Hell, you know, we're all in!
- Yeah.
- [both laughing]
Gabby's great. She really is.
I think they would be
perfect together,
the way they play
off each other,
and I was really happy
to see my son happy.
And I hope this
is the love he finds.
I remember him
coming out of the limo,
and I was like, "Oh, my God."
- Really?
- "That's my type." Yeah!
And then he has this charisma
about him,
his blue eyes
and his eyelashes.
Right.
I don't think
you can really get...
- Resist?
- Yeah.
The connection with you
and Johnny seems very organic.
- Yeah.
- Whether it's for now or ever,
I think
it's really, really cool.
Yeah. Do you think
that he is, like, ready
to be in a long-term
relationship?
Well, the thing
about Johnny is,
he doesn't give his heart
to anybody.
Yeah.
And if Johnny were to say,
"This is it,"
you're in
for a different Johnny
and very fortunate
because he's extremely loyal.
You know,
he has so much to give
and has such a big heart,
so obviously I think
he saw something
in you and he felt safe.
- Right.
- I'm glad.
We're along for the ride,
whatever it is.
- You guys are amazing.
- Thank you.
So yeah.
I was very excited
to see Johnny,
but I was really anxious.
And as soon as I spoke
with her,
I was instantly relieved.
You know, he loves
to be in love,
and I could definitely see that
with those two.
How do we feel about this girl?
Oh, she's amazing.
- Yeah.
- Can you tell?
Oh, my gosh. Yeah.
We literally
don't stop laughing.
- That's the craziest part.
- Yeah, she has... yeah.
I can see
how it's a lot of fun.
I definitely see myself
falling for this girl.
- Yeah.
- I mean, she's amazing.
- She's perfect.
But my whole thing is just
not being fully there yet.
Mm-hmm.
To just drop and get married,
that's, like,
a huge step for me,
and I don't know
if I'm ready for that.
But it's something I haven't
talked about with her yet,
and I know that's something
she wants, so...
- Yeah.
- You know...
Make sure that whatever you do,
it's coming from your heart
and that it's...
It's a commitment.
It's a big commitment.
- It's a huge commitment.
- Yeah.
And you don't
take it haphazardly.
I know you'll decide
if now is the time,
and we'll support you
in whatever decision you make.
- Big decisions.
- Mm-hmm.
Talking to my mom
is amazing.
She was being honest
and upfront with me,
and there's a lot
going through my head.
I love you too.
It kind of just makes
everything harder
when you do see yourself
with this person,
but you don't know
if you're there in life,
so it's a bunch of emotions.
It's like juggling
everything at once.
That's a big thing,
to get on a knee for someone.
Yeah.
She's an amazing person,
but the only thing
that's kind of stopping me
right now is...
- Stopping you from what?
- What's stopping you?
- Just engagement at the end.
- Mm-hmm. That's scary.
I wanted her to meet you guys
and see how you guys felt
about her
and try to just make
the next step forward.
- I mean, that's a...
- It's a big commitment.
Big commitment.
That's something
you gotta think about.
But, the way you guys walked in
and interacted with each other,
it's like,
I just saw the chemistry.
And I said to myself,
"She could be the one."
That's a scary thing
to say itself.
One of the things you say to
me is, like, "I'm not ready."
Well, how?
Emotionally?
I think you're ready
emotionally.
Financially?
You go down the road together.
- And that's kind of important.
- Yeah.
- Go with your heart.
- I appreciate that.
I mean, we met her,
we think she's very lovely,
and you have my blessing.
[soft music]
Come here. I love you.
My dad, you know,
gave me great advice.
He was more on the side
of going for it.
Yeah!
It was really
a pleasure meeting you.
It was so great meeting you.
Today went amazing.
She fit right in.
You know, it gave me more
affirmation that, you know,
she could potentially
be the one.
I think me and you are
gonna do a little cruise.
[gasps]
Show you how I live.
I am falling for this girl,
but it's tough for me
to picture myself
getting on a knee
right now
with where I'm at in life
and it's confusing
in the best way possible.
[♪ ♪]
Johnny has this wonderful,
beautiful life at home
with his friends
and his family.
I can definitely see myself
falling in love with him.
Every time we spend
more time together,
it gets deeper and deeper
and I get
these huge glimpses of what
my life would be like with him.
- Thank you for having me.
- Of course.
I'm glad they liked you too.
They really like you.
It feels so good and so easy
being with somebody who I know
is ready for the next step.
The future is really
unwritten for us.
[soft uplifting music]
[♪ ♪]
I'm here
in Wildwood, New Jersey,
for Tyler's Hometown.
Hometowns, for me,
is the biggest week
because when you bring
families into a relationship,
it does change things.
Yesterday, Zach told me
he's in love with me,
and today, I am really excited
to see where Tyler comes from
and see where this can go.
- Oh, my God.
- Oh, my gosh.
The Jersey Shore!
I know, the Jersey Shore.
Tyler always makes me laugh
and we connect emotionally.
[laughs]
We definitely are
the most far behind,
but I am excited to see
if we can get there today.
- Hi.
- Hey, how are you?
We're here.
We're here
in Wildwood, New Jersey.
Today, we're gonna eat
some food, go on some rides,
play some games, and then,
obviously, with the family,
like, there's nobody else
I'd rather introduce to them.
- I'm ready.
- You're ready?
- Mm-hmm.
- All right.
The Jersey Shore.
Wildwood, New Jersey, baby.
I'm in my hometown,
showing the most amazing woman,
you know, the place I grew up.
I told you,
I come from a very small town.
To me, Rachel is the one.
This could be my future wife.
Like, this could be
the future mom to my kids.
I am falling for her
like crazy,
and like, I get to show her
everything.
This is gonna be
the best date of my life.
[bright music]
Yes! I'm so excited!
- Oh, my gosh!
- Yeah.
Games and everything.
- [bell rings]
- This is the best day.
I need a corn dog.
- It's so good.
- Mm-hmm.
We will take your finest
funnel cake, please.
The fact that we got
the whole boardwalk
to ourselves is nuts.
I'll show you the game.
Basically like two kids
just having the most fun.
You got it.
Here it is.
Gonna be green.
Blue?
Yellow?
- Is there any green over here?
- Yeah, there's one.
- [gasps]
- No way!
- [screams, laughs]
- [bell ringing]
The chances of that happening
are so slim.
- You're the one that wanted it.
- I got it!
- You got it.
- Both: Thank you.
[bell rings]
Ooh!
[both laughing]
Just go in the opposite way!
Any time I have with Rachel,
it's just like, "Wow,
like, this is incredible."
- Oh!
- [laughs]
[screams]
I'm strapped in. I can't fall.
That's why they got
the seat belts.
If you see your life
with somebody,
you gotta be 100% in
and you gotta give
your whole self.
It's not easy to open up
with somebody,
but I'm not afraid
to show my emotions.
- [balloon pops]
- Oh!
I always wanted somebody
that can be emotional.
That's why I'm so
comfortable with her,
because I know that the way
that I perceive love,
she's the same exact way.
Wow.
So my house is, like,
right over the bridge,
and then my apartment
like, during the summer
when I worked up here...
- Yeah.
- Oh, you get an apartment?
I have an apartment
attached, like, with my game,
- That's amazing.
- Which is, like, so cool.
There's no other way this day
could have gone any better.
Like, showing her my world
and, like, her saying
how beautiful it is.
And I just want to be like,
"It's even more beautiful
with you here."
[tender music]
We've had such a great day.
It's been such a good day.
Such a great date.
I'm literally having
the time of my life.
But this is getting
so serious.
- How are you doing?
- Hi.
Rachel, this is Joe,
by the way.
- Joe, this is Rachel.
- Nice to meet you. I'm Rachel.
How are you?
Right over here,
you know my best friend Sal?
Yeah!
This is his dad
right over here.
- Oh, hi! I'm good.
- This is Katie.
- Hi, Katie.
- I've heard so much about you.
This is Lizzie
and Katie's sister, Lauren.
Oh, my goodness.
And then this is my cousin
right over here.
Oh, my gosh,
she's your cousin?
Hi, Lauren. I'm Rachel.
It was great meeting
his friends and seeing them,
but I am feeling a little bit
more apprehensive
about everything just because
there is something bigger
happening tonight.
- You're gonna get bombarded.
- Mm-hmm.
You're getting
the whole tour.
- How are you, buddy?
- [laughter]
How are you?
Meeting family and friends,
it's so overwhelming.
Sal, I want
to introduce someone...
I definitely feel like
we have a strong connection.
But I definitely feel
like my last Hometown
had a different feel
going into the night
than I feel today.
- See you. Love you guys.
- Bye!
- Nice meeting you.
- Yeah, yeah.
I realized my relationship
with him
is a little bit farther behind
than what I would have liked
to feel at this point.
You just met a lot of people.
I know.
And now it just feels like
I'm having a bit of a struggle
because meeting his family,
tonight is looming
a little bit.
Because you're meeting
the fam,
if my mom asks you
any date that we had,
I want to know
which is the best moment
you've had with me.
[sniffles]
I care about Tyler so much.
You ready?
- No.
- No?
But it really kind of hit me
today that things are getting
extremely close to the end.
And I just definitely feel
like I have other connections
that are stronger.
I've had so much fun
with you, you know.
- I do have to close up, though.
- Okay.
And then we'll go down
to the other pier.
Okay.
I can't believe
this is all happening.
I can't believe today is real.
Tonight, she's meeting
the whole fam,
and they're gonna love her.
I already know it.
I'm just so excited.
I'm just so happy.
[♪ ♪]
- No, I just feel like...
- [sighs]
I feel like a horrible person.
It just isn't enough time.
Like, I don't feel
like I'm ready.
[somber music]
I don't know what to do.
[♪ ♪]
I just feel so bad
because he's such a good guy.
I can't even look at him.
Like, I'm, like, gonna,
like, break down.
He thinks
we're about to sit down
and talk about his family.
And that's the thing...
It's like,
when families get involved,
it's huge.
Even just meeting his friends,
I'm like, "Oh, my God.
Oh, my God."
[sighs]
I feel like
I'm gonna throw up.
[♪ ♪]
I'm freaking out.
[somber music]
[♪ ♪]
I feel so much pressure
right now.
Tyler has been here for me
since the beginning,
shown me nothing but kindness
and vulnerability
and being open,
but it's hard because
where I was emotionally
at my last Hometown
is not where I am right now,
and that's why I feel guilty.
[sighs]
It's like... I feel like I'm
disappointing him and everyone
and not giving anyone
a fair chance.
[♪ ♪]
[sighs]
Today has just
been incredible.
Yeah.
Like, I would not have this
go, like, any other way.
And it's... like, playing
the games and then...
- Yeah.
- I did not expect, like, everyone
to be over at the hotspot
when we went there.
Yeah.
And just, like, seeing you
in that setting
- was just incredible.
- I know.
You just taking over, like,
lighting up the room,
like, that's what you do
every single time.
Yeah.
It's been better
than I could ever imagine.
Yeah, I had
such an incredible day.
Um... oh.
- Come here.
- [chuckles]
Um...
I guess...[sighs]
I feel like you're just the...
You're the most
incredible person.
You truly...
I...
[laughs nervously]
I feel so lucky to know you.
Oh, you have no... like,
since the day that I met you...
And, you know, I know your past
and, like, you know mine,
and, you know, during my, like,
darkest, like, times, you know,
we know how hard that is,
and you, like, just say
to yourself,
and I used to say to myself
all the time, like,
"There's a reason for all this.
Like, just wait for it."
Like, wait for that,
like, reason,"
and, like, when I met you,
like, that was my reason.
Like, that's just...
Every single time
that I spend with you just
is better and better each time,
and I'm just so happy,
and, you know,
I said to you, like, before,
like, how important it was
for you to meet my family
and, like, them telling me,
"Next person you bring here,
make sure it's someone
"really special to you
and someone
you see your entire life with."
And, you know,
at this point, you know,
I'm not falling in love
with you,
I am so in love with you.
And it has just
been incredible.
And I would not change a thing,
and I'm just so happy
that you're here
and that I've had a chance
to experience this with you.
'Cause this means so much.
It really does.
And you are literally
the most amazing person...
- Wait, wait, wait.
- I've ever met.
[breathes deeply]
I'm just...
[♪ ♪]
This is family, you know?
- This is a big deal.
- Mm-hmm.
And right now,
I think I'm just struggling
because I just feel like...
Tonight, we're bringing
other people into this.
Absolutely. Yeah.
And... I just want you
to know that
I've never met anyone like you,
who just loves so openly
and who just isn't afraid
of anything,
of being hurt.
And...
[♪ ♪]
I just feel like...
We've had
the most incredible day,
but I'm still feeling, like,
not 100% confident.
Mm-hmm.
And...
I don't know if...
I'm ready to meet
your family...
Mm-hmm.
When I still have
this bit of reservation
and I don't know
where it's coming from.
I just feel like
there is something missing,
and I don't know if it's time
or what it is,
but I just... I don't know
if I'm gonna be able
to get there with you,
and hearing you say
all those incredible things...
[crying] I'm so sorry.
- No, it's okay.
- It really is.
Because I care
about you so much.
[sobbing]
This is so hard.
I just... I don't want
to get to the point
where your family is involved
if I don't know
I can ultimately
get there with you
because I do care about you.
Yeah.
That means a lot to me.
'Cause you know how much
my family means to me.
I know.
I wouldn't want to put them
in that position.
You know?
It's not this...
I mean, this is like...
- I know. I'm sorry.
- It's tough. No, no, no. No.
It's tough, but, like,
being with you,
you make it easy.
You've always made it easy.
And the fact
that you were able to, like,
let me, you know, love again,
like, that means so much
to me, and...
Listen.
And I really do mean this,
'cause I know you feel
the same way.
Like, that love,
that's forever.
It's real. It's 100% real.
And I believe in it
every single day,
and just looking at you,
I know you're gonna have that,
and, like, I want that too...
- I'm so sorry.
- And yeah.
I don't know.
I wish I could get there. I do.
No. It's okay.
I understand.
[♪ ♪]
You're gonna find
everything you deserve.
I truly... I know it.
- Goodbye.
- Goodbye, Rachel.
[♪ ♪]
I feel horrible.
He told me
he was in love with me.
Like, I didn't even know
what to say to him
because he's so incredible
and I feel like
he was, like, comforting me.
It was already hard as it is
knowing that he's expecting
to go meet family after this.
Who thinks
that they're gonna know
when Tyler walks in the door,
whether he's smitten or not?
- Right away.
- You'll know right away.
I can't stand this waiting.
I just have this feeling
that he's gonna walk in
with a smile
from one ear to the other.
I just felt so bad.
Someone like that,
they're so incredible,
and I feel like, why can't
I fall in love with him?
He's probably head
over heels for her,
so excited to show her off
to us.
Knowing what he said
before he left, remember?
"I'll see yo use
in a couple months
with my soon-to-be wife,
Rachel."
- Oh, my God.
Why can't I feel that
for him?
This is the hardest thing
I've had to do.
Because I feel like
my heart is breaking.
Today up on the boardwalk,
just me and, like, Rachel.
- Rachel, let's go!
- [all cheering]
We've all been waiting.
We were saying how you talked
about that before you left.
Yeah.
I know I couldn't get there
with him,
but he's so incredible,
and he just doesn't
deserve this.
Um, she's not here.
She's not here? Why?
I told her how I felt
and everything,
and she told me
that she wasn't there yet
and wasn't ready
to meet the fam.
- Oh, are you all right?
- It's okay.
- Yeah, no, it's tough.
- It's tough. It's tough.
I wanted you guys to see
just how happy I was.
I loved her.
And I still do.
And all I've ever wanted
is somebody that, you know,
would feel the same towards me.
[birds chirping]
[peaceful music]
[♪ ♪]
I had a great week
at Hometowns
with Jason and Johnny.
I think this week,
I've been able
to see these men
and who they are in ways
that I haven't been able
to see them before,
and ultimately, family is
a huge part of that.
Today is my last Hometown.
I'm in New Jersey
and I cannot wait to see Erich.
[laughs]
Ah! Oh, that was good.
So good to see you.
The last time I saw Erich,
he told me
how much he cares for me
and that he's falling for me.
And honestly, I can see myself
falling in love with him.
It's been a long
couple of days.
Yeah. Yeah.
I do...
well, I do want
to see my family.
I want to see
if we could do that first.
Yeah.
Let's do that.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
I hope today goes well
and I'm nervous
because on our one-on-one date
weeks ago,
Erich did open up to me
about his dad battling cancer
for the last three years,
and it sounds like
it hasn't been easy for him.
I do want to give you, like,
a heads up about
my dad's situation
and everything.
Yeah.
He was legitimately supposed
to die, like, three times.
And that was, like,
really, really hard
to come to terms with,
and I actually came here
with him
when he was talking
about, like, how long...
He thought he had a year.
And he was like, "I want you
to take care of your mother,"
and that was the first time
that I, like, really cried
from all that.
- It's been a journey.
- Yeah.
But the only thing
that's really, like...
That's keeping me going
is how, like, loyal my mom was
to that relationship
and to him,
and at no point
was she giving up.
It's a bond that they have
that, you know,
I think it's really rare
to come by.
Yeah.
I need you to meet them
and I need them
to meet you in order, like,
to move forward with this.
I'm grateful that we get to
spend today with your family,
especially given
the circumstances.
I hope they know
that I do care for them
because they're part of you
and, like, I really care
for you.
[soft music]
It's been a long time
since I've seen my dad,
and he has, like,
a very advanced cancer
and it's terminal.
We just don't know
how much time there is,
and it's really,
really, really sad.
So do you know everybody?
Donna, Allan, Elise,
Grandma, Grandpa.
Yes.
I think this is
a very important day
for me and for us.
Okay.
I know she's the one
that I want to bring home
and, like,
she's the one that, like,
I want to be here.
And I'm excited for her
to meet my family,
especially my dad.
All: Hi!
Hi, Mom.
I'm Gabby. Nice to meet you.
Hi, I'm Elise.
Gabby. Nice to meet you.
I watched y'all
on "The Bachelor" show.
Oh, you did?
- I was wondering...
- I know Gabby.
You do.
Yeah, sure.
Sit down.
- Oh, thank you.
- Sit down, Grandpa.
- It's been crazy.
- It is really good
to be back at home.
How have you been?
I have good days
and bad days.
- Yeah.
- So...
I mean, I kind of
filled her in on everything.
She was an ICU nurse.
I did hear that.
This is
the in-home nurse here.
Labor of love.
Everything that you guys
are going through,
it really means the world,
honestly,
for you to allow us in.
[soft music]
My dad is...
He's struggling for sure
to be there to meet Gabby,
and for it to be,
like, a family thing.
All right, Grandpa, you can
go enjoy the outside now.
I have to, like, show my dad
how much he means to me
because it's really important.
I missed the hell
out of you, man.
I really did.
How are you doing? Okay?
Oh, wow.
So yeah, I had some
pretty serious operations.
- Yeah.
- But I'm still here,
and I'm happy, I'm positive,
- you know, so that's good.
- Mm-hmm.
But I really admired...
The ICU nurses.
They're so sharp, right?
We get really close
to our patients, which...
- Yes, you do.
- Yeah.
I got a weird form
of cancer called...
- Appendiceal, right?
- Appendiceal cancer.
- That's where it started.
- The last CAT scan showed
that the cancer came back.
You know, it's being
a little more aggressive.
But I already went
through three rounds of chemo.
The first two did nothing,
and the third one
almost killed me.
Mm-hmm.
Your mother's really
hanging in there.
- She really is.
- Yeah.
- She's gotten sweeter.
- Aww.
It's hard
taking care of somebody.
I'm sure it has been hard
with Erich being gone.
I've really never met
anyone like him.
- He is a little special.
- Yeah.
I seriously like her,
and I think it's kind of...
- [whispering]
- He wouldn't say that otherwise.
[both laughing]
I wouldn't be here
and I wouldn't tell you that
if I didn't think that her
and I had a true connection.
Our first date,
he really just spoke
to what a great relationship
that you and Donna have
and how it's been so amazing
to look up to.
And, like, that's the kind
of love that he wants.
- And we've been lucky.
- Yeah.
Watching now how hard
Mom fights for you guys
and how hard
you've been fighting,
it's really inspirational.
My dad really liked Gabby.
Which is a huge sign
for me too.
But my mom,
I always want her approval
and I always need it, so...
I need her to know how much
I care about it Gabby.
You know, I wouldn't have
brought her here
if I didn't have feelings
for her.
And I would not have put
you guys through this.
I want you to know that, like,
you know,
I'm constantly thinking
about you and Dad, and...
Has he been doing,
like, similar or...
- Mm...
- Worse?
Little bit.
- Yeah.
But I keep watering
that flower,
it keeps coming back.
- Yeah.
Just seeing how,
like, undyingly you love him
and everything you've done
for him up to this point,
it's like, I've kind of modeled
what I want after the bond
that you and Dad have.
It's important to have
that feeling,
like, you couldn't live
without them.
Yeah.
And we...
we marry for life.
Yeah.
You don't take it lightly.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
I know.
It's an important decision.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
[crying softly]
I know how hard it is
for my family to open up
and to let people in
because we're very protective
of each other.
But my mom, she can see
Gabby does mean the world
to me now.
So for me, it was, like, huge.
Erich, he talks so highly
of you and Allan and Elise.
I mean, just so amazing.
And the way he loves
you guys is like,
that is what I look for
in a partner.
- Yeah, family means a lot.
- Yeah.
We just keep trying
to move to the future.
Yeah, yeah, absolutely. Yeah.
And Allan, seeing him today,
he looks so great,
and it is such a testament
to the way
that he's being
taken care of now.
Yeah, he has an incredible
will to live.
Yeah, he has
a lot to live for.
Yeah, 'cause we all love him.
You can't not love Allan.
Yeah.
He's a great guy.
So I just want to make sure
that you guys...
If you decide anything,
that commitment to my family
is really important.
Yeah.
We don't give up
on each other ever.
- Yeah.
- You can't quit.
- Ever, for anything.
You know, we've been...
Allan and I have through...
We'll be married 35 years,
and we've been through a lot.
You always have to...
stay together
and be together, always.
Yeah.
I hope you know how much
I care about Erich,
and even coming here now,
everything makes so much sense.
You can tell how much love
you have for each other.
And I just feel lucky
to be here, you know, today.
Erich's mom being
vulnerable with me,
knowing what she's
going through,
really meant the world.
Thank you.
Today really was so special.
[indistinct chatter]
What an amazing example
of love
his parents have been able
to show.
I felt so close to them.
Today with Erich was one of
the best dates I've had so far.
Thank you for coming today.
Seeing him with his family,
that really just made
my feelings
so much deeper for him,
and, like, I can't wait
to tell Erich
how I feel tonight.
[laughing]
What do you think about
Bedminster, New Jersey?
[both laughing]
Way better
than I expected, honestly.
Erich, seeing him
with his family today
and seeing
his family's commitment
to be together,
it's so beautiful.
Thank you.
Today really solidified
and clarified
my feelings for Erich,
and there's no denying
that I do have
these great, great,
great feelings for him.
I'll never forget today.
Today just, like,
was very real.
Yeah.
And very real
and very important to me.
It's, like, a huge deal for me
to bring someone home even,
- and even this context.
- Yeah.
Like, my dad isn't
doing well.
Like, that's the reality
of the situation.
And you can see how hard it is
for me not to be there
and, like, not even be
in contact with him.
So I think, like,
ultimately, like, they were
really, I think, surprised
to see how, like, much
I like you
and how much I wanted you there
because, like, that's all
they want too,
is for me to be happy
and for me to be with
somebody like you, so...
I am like, really grateful that
you were there today, honestly.
I have risked a lot to be here,
and it's all for you,
and, like, I'm, like,
genuinely happy about it,
and I know they are too.
I think being here today
really shows,
like, the sacrifice
you are making,
and I really can't imagine
how hard it is, truly.
I didn't have any doubt of,
like, why I wanted you there
and you being there.
I came to see you, like,
in Amsterdam on the boat.
And I was like, you know...
I told you
that I'm falling for you,
and... I think, like, words carry
a heavy weight.
But I'm really falling
for you, Gabby.
I think maybe now, I might even
be falling in love with you.
And I think
that's kind of scary.
But I really freaking am, and...
[soft music]
[♪ ♪]
You literally are so amazing.
[laughs]
I think I've been,
like, thinking it,
but obviously, like,
words do carry a lot of weight,
especially here.
And today was really telling,
and seeing you
with your family
and all the things
that they had to say about you
that you've never said
about yourself,
they raised, like,
a really good man.
It is telling to, like,
how much you put them first
and I think
I've, like, always wanted
to be with someone like you
but just never knew
if it was possible.
But, like, after today,
I do finally feel comfortable
in saying
that I am falling in love
with you.
[♪ ♪]
I feel so much for her,
and, like, I am falling in love
with her,
and, like, I told her that,
and to have her
say that back to me
was, like,
the most beautiful ending
of, like, the most perfect day.
And I really mean
what I said.
[♪ ♪]
I am most definitely
falling in love with Erich,
and that means
the whole world to me.
Saying goodbye
was so, so, so hard.
You're amazing.
I'm gonna miss you a lot.
Like, a lot, a lot.
I'll miss you.
I can picture us
so easy together.
And today, I think, is a day
that I'll really never, ever,
ever forget.
- Okay, bye-bye.
- Okay.
After today,
I think Erich's Hometown,
it could have changed
the rest of my life.
[horn honking]
Hi.
What's up, babe?
- [laughing]
- I'm so excited to see you.
Today, I'm in
Santa Clarita, California,
and I'm seeing Tino
and meeting his family.
Nice ride.
I'm so excited for today,
but my last Hometown
was really hard.
I wasn't ready
to meet Tyler's family.
What's up?
- Missed you.
[light music]
[♪ ♪]
It puts pressure on today
just because I do see a future
with Tino.
It's really a big deal for me
that his parents are
accepting of me.
If they don't approve of me
and like me,
then how am I supposed
to move forward?
You excited for tonight?
- I'm so excited.
- I'm very nervous.
You know, the approval tonight,
what if, like, I don't get it?
Like, how...
- Well, you're going to.
- I'm just saying.
But I just want you to be
confident when you head over,
and you'll nail it.
But I am nervous.
This is a big, huge deal.
I want them to feel like
I could fit in
because I'm really serious,
so it's really important to me
that they at least
give me a chance.
I'm so serious about you
and I'm so serious
about telling you,
you have nothing
to worry about.
- Okay.
- I promise you.
I am so excited too.
A lot at stake.
A lot at stake,
but you're gonna crush it.
- Is it real?
- Right.
Because there's
four other guys here.
She could like any one of them
as much as she likes him.
But what if Tino's not the one
she likes the best?
- Right.
- And how does he know that?
I don't know
how Tino deals with that.
[bright music]
- [gasps]
- Hi, guys.
- I get to go first.
- I planned this.
You look so tanned.
- Hi, baby.
- Guys...
- Hi, everyone.
- How's it going?
- Hi.
- I'm Rachel.
- Rachel? I'm Sandy.
- Nice to meet you
- Nice to meet you.
Rachel tonight is meeting
my mom, Sandy, my dad, Joe,
and my little brother, Mateo.
This is Mateo,
my little brother.
- Thanks for coming out.
- Mateo. Nice to meet you.
I think
it's tremendously important
that tonight goes well
because I really want
their approval,
like, so very badly.
I'm so excited to be here.
I haven't told Rachel
that I'm falling for her yet
because I think I've just been
waiting for the right moment.
And I think once she knocks it
out of the park
with my parents,
it'll be like, the table's set.
Like, just right out
of the gate, it was, like,
so electric talking to her that
where maybe it was difficult
or other people had to, like,
you know, look into things,
I was like...
I was pretty darn sure, yeah.
And she, I guess, felt the same
'cause the first rose
of the season went to me,
so yeah, that was pretty cool.
And it really just is better
every single time
we're together...
I don't know how.
Since then, like,
I mean, as, like, cheesy
as it's gonna sound,
like, everything disappears
like, when we're together,
so it's like,
when we started talking,
- it was like it just flowed...
- Aww, that's nice.
Yeah, but how much time
do you guys get together?
Each cocktail party, we found
plenty of time together.
Yeah, there's never been
a time we haven't talked.
Yeah, but aren't there other
guys trying to talking to you?
Aren't they all doing
the same thing?
I mean, how... are they...
They're striking out.
[laughter]
Yeah, no,
I mean, it's definitely...
It is different.
So you guys have
a couple more weeks.
- So what do you guys think...
- What do you do next?
The next two weeks
are gonna be like?
I mean, what are you guys
hoping to find out?
She'll send
the rest of guys home
and I'll propose to her
in a couple weeks.
[laughs]
What are you talking about?
After... after two months?
Yeah. 100%.
When you know, you know.
[tense music]
We're gonna have to have
a talk.
- Okay.
- Man to man.
I was not expecting my dad
to be really stringent
with his questions.
Clearly, he's really
skeptical about the situation.
I'm gonna take you outside
and we're gonna have a talk.
- Shall we?
- Yeah, let's do it.
I want Rachel to be able
to see herself in this family.
But I'm, like,
to some degree afraid
because I do want
that stamp of approval.
I got a lot of questions.
- First question is,
- Lay 'em on me.
It's been
a very short period of time.
Mm-hmm.
Do you really think
this is where you want to be?
- Yeah. Without a doubt.
- Really? Why?
I mean, how... how,
in just five weeks...
do you know enough about her?
I know the important stuff.
We talked about stuff
that we want for the future
and stuff we're insecure about,
and every reassurance
that I've felt like I needed,
I'm getting out of her.
You feel like you've had
that much time to connect,
- like, at different levels?
- Yeah.
I just have a hard time
believing that what you can do
on a whirlwind fairy tale trip
is really gonna prepare you
for marriage.
And I just want to make sure
your head's in the right place.
And this whole fairy tale thing
and everything
has us more...
Probably more nervous
than you are, you know?
Because we're like,
this is, you know, our kid,
and we want to see you be
happy the rest of your life.
It's just been an honor
to get to know him.
I really just feel like
I've never met anyone like him,
so I thank you for sharing him.
So what do you think
Tino's best traits are?
He is seriously so positive,
and his outlook on life
is truly something
I've never seen anyone have.
He was like,
"Yeah, you know, I give...
I give blood all the time."
And I was like, "Well, why?"
He's like,
"Well, there's a shortage."
And I remember just being like,
"Oh, my gosh.
Like, he just cares so much.
He's so giving."
If you think you met him
outside of...
So this is not real.
- This is not real.
- Well, it is.
Well, but it's not, like,
how you normally meet people
- and how you normally do things.
- Of course. Of course.
- You're in this insulated...
- Mm-hmm.
- I guess, bubble.
- Yeah.
So you have a huge decision
coming up.
Mm-hmm. Exactly.
So I've gotta figure out,
in a week or two,
if I'm mending a broken heart
or planning a wedding.
Yeah.
- And I guess you do too.
- Yeah.
Talking to Tino's mom,
I feel like
she's just skeptical
about the whole thing.
How much time do you get
to figure this out, though?
This is a big decision for you.
Right now,
it's about two weeks left.
- Wow.
- She grilled my ass.
And now I'm, like, scared
to talk to his dad.
This has hit me,
like, really hard.
Okay.
I guess my first question
would be is,
how can you make a connection
that quickly?
You gotta appreciate
the skepticism.
Oh, no, completely.
It is extremely expedited,
but I think we are able to talk
about really serious things
really quickly and see
if we want similar things,
if we line up with our morals.
I have trouble wrapping
my head around the fact
that this could happen
that quickly.
And so tell me,
what's Tino like?
Convince me that you know him,
the real Tino.
I think it's just the way
he looks at life
and his positive outlook.
I feel like I have
so much to learn from him
and he's so humble and caring
and people just gravitate
towards him.
[sighs]
Don't take this the wrong way.
It just sounds...
I mean, you're saying
all the right things,
and it's like,
that's all great,
but at least in our mind...
From 20,000 feet away,
we see it as, like,
this fairy tale thing.
Like I said,
I'm looking out for him.
- Yeah.
- It's nothing against you.
I'm just making sure
that he's making
the right choice
and that it's the right match.
Yeah.
Like, I genuinely almost cried
because I thought it was
going that bad with his dad
and I didn't know
how to answer his questions.
How can you talk
about Tino this way,
but there's still other people,
you're obviously exploring
those potential relationships?
I literally was like, "Okay,
this is actually about to end."
And I want to see him
fall for the right person.
So how far have you and Tino
talked about, like...
let's say he's there
at the end of this.
I mean, are you expecting
an engagement?
What's the plan?
Yeah, no,
I'm looking for an engagement.
And he, I mean, has told me
that that's something
he's ready for.
He definitely, I think,
is a little bit slower
with... his feelings
and he definitely
holds back a little bit more.
So I'm definitely
kind of just waiting
to see where he's at
with all this, but yeah,
that's definitely something
I'm looking for.
- No, I mean...
- [sighs]
I don't want to beat
a dead horse.
The hardest part
about all this is just...
This is your second go-around,
and...
I was asking Tino, I was like,
"Well, you know, is this person
just looking to get married,
or does this person,
you know, really like you?"
I wouldn't put him
in this position
just so I could get married.
I'm not that type of person.
I really want to meet someone
that is gonna be my partner
for life.
Like I say, you're looking
for an engagement,
so you've got your mind set,
and, you know,
when he talks about
that this could go further,
I'm just like,
"Tino, are you ready?
And, you know, are you sure?"
Both of you should be
honest with each other
and make sure it's right.
Yeah.
Well, I appreciate it.
Thanks for chatting with me.
No problem.
[tense music]
And thanks
for having us over.
This has been so great.
[♪ ♪]
I just feel like
he just didn't like me
and just was like,
"I hate you."
I'm like, "Okay."
To be, like, almost expecting
to be engaged,
like, right then, it's like,
you still don't know enough.
Would you want to be
engaged with someone
you don't know
enough about yet?
I feel like
I need to breathe.
I just feel like
I don't even know...
It's like, okay,
everyone hated me,
so where do we...
I just feel shook up by them.
Shook up.
Like, I feel like
I could do no right.
I feel like I could be
the most perfect person,
they wouldn't have liked me.
You know, hopefully
over the next two weeks,
from what I heard,
you know, you guys have
a lot more to learn
about each other and make sure
that whatever happens next
is, you know, the right thing.
Yeah.
And just be open and honest.
Yeah, I really appreciate
you guys welcoming me in
and I really do appreciate
all the hard-hitting questions.
I really...
No, I do respect it so much
because it really shows me
how serious you all take it
on top of how serious
we take it, so...
That's good.
It has been incredible
to see...
We all should.
- Where you come from.
- Yes, absolutely.
- So thank you so much.
- We all should. Yeah.
All right, well,
we're gonna head out, so...
- Okay.
- All right.
It's time for us
to say goodbye.
I have stressed
the importance of Hometowns
and the importance of them
at least giving me
a chance to see
if I could fit in,
and I don't even
feel like they...
Like, I feel like
his dad is like,
"I hope you do not
come back here."
[♪ ♪]
Like, I don't know
how I made it
out of that house alive,
if we're being honest.
I almost cried.
We'd have to really sit down
and talk about, like,
is he gonna be okay
moving forward
when his parents
just aren't gonna be happy?
Oh, my God, what a night.
I felt like I just...
I really wanted this
to go well for you.
Yeah. Yeah.
They did adore you,
I promise you.
I don't think they...
I'm gonna be honest,
I do not think they like me.
They definitely adore you.
- Tino...
- They do.
I'm not too confident.
Your dad wasn't even
giving me a chance.
Tino, they were tough on me.
Yeah, they were
hard on me too,
but of course, they asked,
like, "Are you sure?
Are you sure?"
And this is where, like,
I feel bad, like,
not saying all this
to you earlier.
Like, Rachel,
I'm so sure about you.
You always make me
feel appreciated
and valued and loved, like,
every time we're together.
And, I mean, that's why, like,
I'm proud and, you know,
excited to tell you
that, like, I am falling
in love with you.
And I don't want
a future without you.
[tender music]
I should have told you
weeks ago,
and I'm so sorry about that.
With you being honest,
I think I should be honest too.
And I think
I also feel like I have been
falling in love with you
for a while.
And that's honestly how I feel.
That's actually
the most incredible thing
I think I could have
ever expected
out of this conversation.
[♪ ♪]
I feel a lot better
knowing how Tino feels.
I feel really happy.
Like, more than happy.
I am trying to just
enjoy this moment,
but it still is difficult
to think about.
His parents saying the things
that they were saying,
their opinions hold weight,
and I'm very, very scared
with how that went.
Let's head out.
And what does it mean
with him,
and if I don't have
the approval,
can we go forward?
Good night. Bye.
And so as good as it feels
to hear him say those words,
it's really hard for me
to think about an engagement
when I know
that I don't have any support
from Tino's parents.
[♪ ♪]
Coming up next week
on "The Bachelorette"...
I gotta tell you
about my famous love spell.
I could do it for you,
if you like.
Rachel visits
Aven's hometown,
where they feel the magic.
- Ooh!
- Oh!
[glass shatters]
Is that bad luck?
And then...
Welcome to what promises to be
a dramatic and shocking
Men Tell All.
All of your favorite men
from this season are back.
You had your chance.
Have some respect for the guys
that were there.
And they're ready
to talk smack...
You did me wrong.
All of that
is, like, [bleep].
I guess I like girls that
are rough around the edges.
I... I love Gabby.
And...
Meatball, our savior!
If you think you know
what happens...
[dramatic music]
Guess again.
This news is about to change
your lives forever.
[♪ ♪]
Get ready.
[cheers and applause]
To new adventures!
And then, in two weeks...
Bienvenidos!
Gabby and Rachel take
their journey for love
to Mexico.
I am in love,
and I've never been
this happy.
This is the moment
during Clayton's season
where everything went haywire.
Everything went off the wall.
The last thing your dad said
to me, like, was,
they don't like me.
I'm scared to move forward
because of what happened
at Hometowns.
After Fantasy Suite,
everything took, like, a 180.
That was the last thing
I could've ever expected.
I'm picturing the girl
that, like, I'm in love with
doing that with somebody else.
It, like, crushes me.
He said he can't love me.
It's like, am I too broken
for anyone to love?
Gabby will not
be joining you.
You're gonna be
the only Bachelorette here.
I'm struggling,
because I want this to work,
so it's hard
when I've given him
nothing but the best.
It's all coming up
on "The Bachelorette."
[♪ ♪]
Is your father a pilot,
or did you...
No, my dad's actually
an engineer.
He always kind of has been
interested in aviation,
- but yeah.
- Right.
We always have been
in our family.
When did you start flying?
When I was 17.
Do you have
your pilot's license?
No. I could've gotten it,
- if I was more dedicated.
- Yeah.
Look, I failed
out of junior college.
And, um,
I wasn't even on drugs.
- [quirky music]
- [laughs softly]
I'm just not good
at studying.
See, the more I talk,
I feel like Zach
just brought me home
so everyone could get
their pilot's license.
That's right.
[laughing]
He's got quite a presence,
doesn't he?
- He does.
- He's got a big heart.
You know, he comes
from a great family.
Mm-hmm.
- [giggles]
- Yeah.
And, of course,
someone had to say it:
He's the right one.
[laughing]
Look, everybody knows it.
I do need one thing from you.
- Mm-hmm.
- I need a high five.
Oh, of course. High five.
[laughs]