TONIGHT...
THE SHOCKING
DRAMA BEGINS...
LIVE.
I DON'T WANT TO DO THIS
ANYMORE.
GABBY.
I WANT TO LEAVE HERE.
GET READY FOR THE DRAMATIC
SEASON FINALE OF
"THE BACHELORETTE."
FOUR MEN.
I WANT TO BE WITH RACHEL AT
THE END OF THIS.
LIKE, I WANT TO
HAVE A LIFE WITH
HER.
TWO WOMEN.
WE ARE LITERALLY
ABOUT TO BE
ENGAGED.
I FEEL LIKE ALL MY DREAMS
ARE, LIKE, COMING TRUE.
AND ONE DRAMATIC FINAL DAY.
YOU SHOULDN'T
HAVE HAD TO GO
THROUGH THAT, AND IT'S REALLY
NOT OKAY.
THIS IS MY DAUGHTER.
NOBODY'S GOING
TO TAKE HER AWAY
FROM ME WITHOUT A FIGHT.
HOW WILL IT ALL END?
I'VE ALWAYS
BEEN HONEST WITH
YOU.
WHY, ZACH?
OH, MY GOD
TEARS OF JOY.
I JUST LOVE HER.
I WANT THE BEST FOR HER.
OR TEARS OF
UTTER HEARTBREAK?
I FEEL SO
BLINDSIDED BY YOU.
WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO DO,
WALK AWAY BECAUSE
HE'S NOT READY
TO PROPOSE?
AND JUST WHEN
YOU THINK IT'S
ALL OVER...
YOU'RE LYING STRAIGHT TO MY
FACE.
LOOK ME IN THE EYES AND LIE TO
ME AGAIN.
THE CRAZY DRAMA CONTINUES.
I WANT AN
ANSWER FOR WHY YOU
DID WHAT YOU DID.
I'M SORRY.
THIS IS ACTUALLY CRAZY.
THE TELEVISION EVENT OF THE
SUMMER IS FINALLY HERE.
IT'S LIVE, AND IT ALL STARTS
RIGHT NOW.
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
THANKS FOR COMING.
THANK YOU.
GOOD EVENING,
BACHELOR NATION!
I AM JESSE PALMER
AND WELCOME TO
THE LIVE TO COWRITE SEASON
FINALE THAT I
GUARANTEE WILL BE
SO EMOTIONAL, SO DRAMATIC, AND
SO CONTROVERSIAL,
IT WILL HAVE ALL OF AMERICA
STUNNED.
OUR TWO BACHELORETTES,
GABBY AND RACHEL,
ARE NEARING THE END OF THEIR
JOURNEY TO FIND LOVE.
SO WILL THERE BE ONE PROPOSAL
OR MAYBE TWO?
I THINK WE ARE
ALL HOPING TO SEE
BOTH OF THESE
AMAZING WOMEN FIND
THE LOVE THAT THEY SO DESERVE.
NOW, GABBY AND RACHEL ARE HERE
TONIGHT TO BE A PART OF
AMERICA'S LARGEST
VIEWING PARTY
AND MAYBE THEY CAN HELP SHED
SOME LIGHT ON WHAT WILL SURELY
BE THE MOST TALKED
ABOUT FINALE
WE'VE EVER SEEN.
SO WHAT DO YOU THINK?
SHOULD WE BRING THEM OUT?
ALL RIGHT,
PLEASE WELCOME YOUR
BACHELORETTES,
GABBY AND RACHEL!
HI.
HOW ARE YOU?
HAVE A SEAT.
IT'S SO GOOD TO SEE YOU BOTH
AGAIN.
THANK YOU FOR BEING WITH US
TONIGHT.
YOU BOTH LOOK FANTASTIC PER
USUAL.
THANK YOU.
LIGHTING AND MAKEUP.
WE HAVE GOT SO
MUCH WE ARE GOING
TO GET INTO.
RACHEL, LIVE STUDIO AUDIENCE,
LIVE TELEVISION, NO BIG DEAL.
WE ARE ALL GOING TO WATCH THE
DRAMATIC CONCLUSIONS
TO BOTH OF
YOUR JOURNEYS TO FIND LOVE.
HOW ARE YOU FEELING?
DEFINITELY NERVOUS.
IT'S HARD TO RELIVE EVERYTHING
THAT WE ARE EXCITED I THINK.
I'VE BEEN IN THAT SEAT SO I
KNOW EXACTLY HOW YOU FEEL.
I CAN RELATE.
IT'S BEEN A MINUTE.
GABY, IT'S BEEN
A COUPLE MONTHS
SINCE WE GOT DONE FILMING IN
MEXICO.
I DIDN'T HAVE EXPECTATIONS
GOING IN SO I THINK WITH THAT
MIND-SET, IT'S BIGGER AND MORE
LIFE-CHANGING
THAN I EVER COULD
HAVE IMAGINED.
WE ARE JUST SCRATCHING THE
SURFACE.
WE HAVE GOT SO
MUCH TO GET INTO.
I THINK WE NEED
TO PICK UP WHERE
WE LEFT OFF, RACHEL, WITH YOU
AND ZACH AT THE ROSE CEREMONY.
ARE YOU READY?
OKAY, BACHELOR NATION,
HERE WE GO.
THE MOST DRAMATIC FINALE IN
BACHELORETTE HISTORY
AND IT STARTS RIGHT NOW.
RACHEL, CAN WE SPEAK?
YEAH.
WHY, ZACH?
OH, MY GOD.
UM, I THINK IT'S...
I'M SURE YOU FEEL THAT THE
FANTASY SUITE
FELT A LITTLE OFF.
YEAH.
WITH US.
AND YOU KNOW, SINCE DAY ONE,
I'VE ALWAYS BEEN HONEST
WITH YOU...
YEAH.
AND UPFRONT ABOUT MY
FEELINGS.
AND TO BE HONEST,
I THOUGHT WHAT
I WAS SEEING WASN'T THE REAL
RACHEL.
I FELT LIKE I WAS SEEING
BACHELORETTE RACHEL, NOT THE
REAL RACHEL THAT I'D COME TO
KNOW AND LOVE.
OKAY.
HIS LOOK WHEN
HE ASKED HER TO
WALK OUT, HE JUST
LOOKED, LIKE,
PRETTY...
UPSET.
YEAH.
INTERESTING.
I GUESS HE KIND OF SAW IT AS A
NOW OR NEVER.
YOU KNOW, AT
THIS POINT LATE
IN THE STAGE WHERE I EXPRESSED
AND SHOWN, LIKE, MY ABSOLUTE
LOVE...
YEAH.
FOR YOU, AND
I FEEL UPSET AND
DISAPPOINTED THAT
I WASN'T ABLE
TO GET THAT FROM YOU.
I DO UNDERSTAND MAYBE YOU
WERE PICKING UP
ON A LITTLE BIT
OF A DIFFERENT VIBE.
I HAVE BEEN TRYING TO GAIN
CLARITY THIS WEEK
AS WELL, AND I
DO REALLY FEEL LIKE I DID FIND
IT.
I FELT LIKE
THE CONCERNS WITH
THE AGE PART...
YEAH.
WAS A COMPLETE KIND OF
BLINDSIDE.
I WAS JUST TRYING TO FIND
THAT MISSING PIECE FOR ME.
AND I DID THINK
IF WE COULD JUST
SPEND THE NIGHT TALKING THAT
MAYBE I COULD FIND IT.
IT'S JUST,
IT'S KIND OF HARD
TO WRAP MY HEAD AROUND IT.
YEAH, I DID REALLY LOVE YOU.
YOU KNOW.
I SAW A FUTURE WITH YOU.
BUT I NEED TO GO.
I TRULY NEED
YOU TO KNOW THAT
I WISH I COULD HAVE GOTTEN TH
THERE.
BUT YOU KNOW,
A RELATIONSHIP
IS A TWO-WAY ROAD, AND, YOU
KNOW, I CAN'T
MAKE IT ANY OTHER
WAY.
AT LEAST NOW WE KNOW.
OH, JEEZ LOUISE.
THAT WOULD BE, I BELIEVE,
ZACH GETTING
WALKED OUT, IF YOU
ARE READING THIS
CORRECTLY TOO.
YEAH, THAT'S WHAT IT'S
LOOKING LIKE.
THIS IS AWKWARD.
THAT'S REALLY SAD.
HONESTLY THIS IS SO SAD.
IT'S OVER JUST LIKE THAT.
JUST LIKE THAT.
I CAN SEE IN HER EYES THAT IT
REALLY MEANT
SOMETHING DIFFERENT
TO HER THAN IT DID TO ME.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT I MISSED.
I MEAN, I SAW IT THAT NIGHT IN
THE FANTASY SUITE THAT IT WAS
OFF.
I DON'T KNOW.
BUT, LIKE, IT
STILL DOESN'T FEEL
REAL.
LIKE, SHE WAS, IN MY MIND,
THE FUTURE MRS. SHALLCROSS.
OH, MY GOODNESS.
I'M SO SORRY.
UM, ZACH LEFT.
I DO WISH HIM THE BEST.
I DON'T REALLY WANT TO SPEAK
ILL.
BUT FOR PEOPLE WHO ESPECIALLY
SAY THAT THEY CARE ABOUT ME TO
KIND OF TAKE THINGS INTO THEIR
OWN HANDS AND QUESTION MY
CHARACTER, IT'S
OBVIOUSLY REALLY
DISAPPOINTING.
I DON'T REALLY HAVE ANY OTHER
WORDS.
HER RESPONSE, IT FELT SO
COLD THAT I THOUGHT
MAYBE THAT I
MEANT MORE, BUT I GUESS I
DIDN'T.
TINO?
TINO, WILL YOU
ACCEPT THIS ROSE?
ALWAYS.
ONE OF THE THINGS I FELL IN
LOVE WITH WAS,
LIKE, SHE MADE ME
FEEL...
LIKE, SPECIAL.
AND CARED FOR.
AND...
I QUESTION IF ANY OF THAT WAS
REAL.
IF THAT WAS JUST AN ACT.
AVEN?
AVEN, WILL YOU
ACCEPT THIS ROSE?
ABSOLUTELY.
OH.
OBVIOUSLY THAT WAS REALLY
HARD TO WATCH.
ARE YOU DOING OKAY?
WHEN WE COME
BACK, YOU'LL GET A
CHANCE TO SPEAK
TO ZACH FOR THE
FIRST TIME SINCE THAT DAY IN
MEXICO.
BACHELOR NATION,
DON'T GO AWAY.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
WELCOME BACK TO THE LIVE
FINALE OF "THE BACHELORETTE."
I'M HERE WITH RACHEL.
GABBY IS STIL HERE BUT SHE'S
STEPPED AWAY TO
GIVE RACHEL SOME
SPACE.
YOU LOOK NERVOUS.
ARE YOU DOING OKAY?
I AM READY TO TALK TO ZACH?
I'M READY.
LADIES AND
GENTLEMEN, PLEASE
WELCOME ZACH.
GOOD TO SEE YOU.
ZACH, IT'S GREAT HAVING YOU
HERE.
I KNOW YOU HAVEN'T SEEN OR
SPOKEN TO RACHEL
SINCE THAT DAY
IN MEXICO.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO SAY TO HER?
WOW, GREAT SEEING YOU.
IT'S BEEN A LONG TIME.
LITTLE NERVOUS, LITTLE NERVOUS
OF COURSE.
I JUST WANT TO SAY THAT I DO
APOLOGIZE FOR EVER MAKING YOU
FEEL LIKE I CALLED YOU OUT FOR
YOUR CHARACTER.
WATCHING THAT BACK, BOOKS THE
LAST THING I WANTED.
THAT'S THE LAST
THING I WANTED.
I WAS KIND OF IN SHOCK AND
DISBELIEF IN WHAT
WAS HAPPENING
BETWEEN US.
I AM SO SORRY.
I'M SORRY TOO.
I REALLY WANT YOU TO KNOW THAT
OBVIOUSLY THERE
WAS REALLY HARD
FOR ME TO WATCH
BACK AND SEE YOU
EMOTIONAL AND I
WANT YOU TO KNOW
THAT THOSE FEELINGS
THAT I HAD,
THEY WERE REAL.
I DON'T EVER WANT YOU TO FEEL
LIKE I WAS PUTTING
ON AN ACT OR
ANYTHING I DO
APOLOGIZE AS WELL.
TAKE US BACK TO THE ROSE
CEREMONY WHEN YOU DECIDED TO
LEAVE AND WALK AWAY.
HOW HARD OF A THAT?
I WAS SICK TO
MY STOMACH THE
WHOLE WEEK.
I KNEW FROM OUR NIGHT OF THE
FANTASY SUITE, IT FELT OFF.
THE DAYS LEADING UP TO THE
ROSE CEREMONY,
I WAS CONSTANTLY
FEELING THAT THING IN MY
STOMACH.
I HAD TO SHARE WHAT I WAS
FEELING I DIDN'T WANT TO HIDE
THAT FROM YOU.
IT WAS THE TOUGHEST WEEK.
GRANTED, THINGS
HAPPENED THE WAY
THEY DID, AND THAT'S OKAY.
THAT'S WHAT WAS MEANT TO BE.
IT WAS A TOUGH, DIFFICULT
SITUATION FOR US BOTH.
AGAIN, I'M SORRY.
I COULD HAVE
HANDLED IT BETTER.
RACHEL, SAFE
TO SAY THAT YOU
LOOK PRETTY STUNNED AND CAUGHT
OFF GUARD.
DO YOU FEEL LIKE YOU SAID
EVERYTHING YOU
NEEDED TO SAY OR
IS THERE SOMETHING YOU WANT
DISPLAYED TO ZACH?
I REALLY WANT YOU TO KNOW
THAT YOU MEANT SO MUCH TO ME.
I CARE ABOUT YOU
AND I REALLY DO
WANT ALL THE HAPPINESS IN THE
WORLD FOR YOU.
EVERYTHING THAT
HAPPENED, IT WAS
AWKWARD AND I AM SORRY.
I WAS REALLY JUST LOOKING FOR
CLARITY AND I WANTED US TO BE
ABLE TO HAVE THAT NIGHT TO SEE
IF WE COULD GET THERE.
ULTIMATELY I JUST COULDN'T.
BUT I NEVER WANT YOU TO FEEL
LIKE I WAS GOING TO PUT YOU
THROUGH SOMETHING LIKE THAT IF
IT WASN'T A TRULY TO SEE IF WE
COULD COME OUT ON THE OTHER
SIDE.
I'M SORRY.
I GET THAT.
THERE IS NO ONE
-WAY OR RIGHT WAY
TO NAVIGATE IT.
IT WAS A TOUGH
PILL TO SWALLOW.
IT WASN'T WHAT
I THOUGHT IT WAS
GOING TO BE BECAUSE I SAW A
FUTURE WITH YOU.
THE REALITY OF IT WAS THAT IT
JUST WASN'T GOING
TO HAPPEN AND
THAT WAS A HARD THING TO REA
REALIZE.
I JUST WANT YOU TO BE HAPPY.
I'M GLAD SEE YOU AFTER ALL OF
THIS TIME.
THINGS WERE GOING...
IT'S GOOD TO HEAR
YOU SAY THAT.
THINGS WERE GOING SO WELL
BETWEEN THE TWO
OF YOU UP UNTIL
THAT OVERNIGHT DATE.
I THINK FOR A LOT OF PEOPLE,
THEY ARE WONDERING
IF SOMETHING
NEFARIOUS OR
SOMETHING CRAZY MAN
HAPPENED BEHIND CLOSE DOORS IN
THE OVERNIGHT DATE FOR THE
RELATIONSHIP TO COME CRASHING
DOWN THE WAY HE DID.
WHAT DID HAPPEN THAT MIGHT?
RACHEL, PLEASE
CORRECT ME IF
I'M WRONG.
IT WAS ONE OF
THOSE MOMENTS WHEN
THE FANTASY SUITE STARTED, WE
WERE IN THERE AND TALKING.
IT KIND OF FELT
IMMEDIATELY OFF.
HE FELT LIKE WE
WERE KIND OF TWO
STRANGERS IN A WAY.
I THINK IT WAS
THE MOMENT THAT I
DIDN'T FULLY RECOGNIZE AT THE
TIME BUT MAYBE YOU HAD ALREADY
REALIZED I WASN'T GOING TO BE
YOUR FUTURE PERSON.
WE HAVE THE REST
OF THE NIGHT TO
STILL HANG OUT AND BE TOGETHER
AND IT WAS TOUGH.
IT WASN'T UNTIL THE DAYS AFTER
WHERE IT WAS ALL RIGHT, I NEED
TO SHARE MY FEELINGS.
ABOUT HOW THERE ISN'T AN US.
IT STARTED OFF EARLY IN THE
FANTASY SUITE AND IT WAS A
TOUGH, TOUGH CONVERSATION.
IT WAS JUST OFF.
FELT LIKE TWO VERY DIFFERENT
PEOPLE.
DOES THAT
SOUND ABOUT RIGHT?
I DO AGAIN WANT YOU TO KNOW
WATCHING IT BACK, I WAS NEVER
ACCUSING YOU OF
NOT BEING READY
AND I DON'T WANT
YOU TO FEEL AS
IF I WAS COMING AFTER YOU.
I JUST WANTED TO
KNOW IF YOU ARE
READY IN GENERAL,
WHICH IS WHEN
I ASKED EVERYONE.
I WANT YOU TO
KNOW THAT'S WHERE
I WAS COMING FROM.
I WAS HOPING WE COULD HAVE
CLEARED UP IN
THE MORNING BUT I
DO KNOW THAT IT
WAS AWKWARD FOR
BOTH OF US.
MAYBE THERE WAS A
MISCOMMUNICATION.
BUT I REALLY JUST WANT YOU TO
KNOW THAT I WAS NEVER, LIKE,
TRYING TO MAKE IT AWKWARD.
I KNOW.
IT WAS TOUGH.
IT WAS REALLY TOUGH.
THERE IS NO WAY
T WAY TO NAVIGAT
THE RIGHT WAY.
YOU DID AN ADMIRABLE JOB AND I
WAS TRYING TO HANDLE IT WHEN I
COULD.
DO THE BEST I COULD.
I UNFORTUNATELY FAILED.
IT'S OKAY.
YOU HAVE HAD SOME TIME TO
PROCESS IT.
THINKING BACK TO THAT DAY IN
MEXICO.
DO YOU HAVE ANY
REGRETS WALKING
AWAY?
YOU KNOW.
I DON'T REALLY
HAVE ANY REGRETS.
ALL THE MOMENTS I SHARED WITH
YOU, RACHEL, BEING IN L. A. ALL
THE WAY TO
AMSTERDAM, I'LL NEVER
FORGET THOSE MEMORIES.
MEXICO WAS GREAT UNTIL IT WA
WASN'T.
I WOULDN'T TRADE
ANYTHING IN THE
WORLD.
EVERYTHING HAPPENS
FOR A REASON.
SO IT WAS GREAT
GETTING TO KNOW
YOU.
RACHEL, HOW ABOUT YOU?
ANY REGRETS?
ZACH, YOU'RE SUCH AN
INCREDIBLE GUY.
YOU TRULY MADE THIS EXPERIENCE
FOR ME.
I KNOW IT DIDN'T WORK OUT
EXACTLY WHAT WE MIGHT HAVE
THOUGHT IN THE
MOMENT BUT I JUST
WANT YOU TO KNOW HOW MUCH I
APPRECIATE YOU AND I REALLY DO
APPRECIATE THIS CONVERSATION
HONESTLY.
ALL RIGHT, ZACH.
BEFORE WE MOVE ON, ANY LAST
WORDS THAT YOU
HAVE FOR RACHEL?
AGAIN.
THE MEMORIES WE
SHARED TOGETHER,
I WILL NEVER FORGET THEM.
I REALLY JUST
HOPE YOU'RE HAPPY
AND I WANT THE BEST FOR YOU
ALWAYS.
YOU'RE AWESOME.
FEEL LIKE YOU GOT SOME
CLOSURE.
I KNOW IT'S HARD TO DO, TO
RELIVE IT.
THANK YOU FOR YOUR HONESTY AND
WHILE IT DIDN'T
WORK OUT FOR YOU
ROMANTICALLY IT'S OBVIOUS YOU
HAVE A LOT OF MUTUAL RESPECT.
I LOVE SEEING THAT.
THANK YOU BOTH SO MUCH.
ZACH, THANK YOU.
ALL RIGHT, WHEN WE RETURN, THE
REMAINING GUYS
MEET RACHEL'S AND
GABBY'S FAMILIES.
THINGS DON'T GO EXACTLY AS
PLANNED.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
WELCOME BACK TO
"THE BACKELORETTE"
LIVE FINALE.
IT'S ALREADY BEEN AN EMOTIONAL
NIGHT AND IT'S
ABOUT TO GET EVEN
MORE EMOTIONAL.
I'M HERE RIGHT NOW WITH RACHEL
AND GABBY WHO ARE
WATCHING ALONG
WITH EVERYONE ELSE, AND IT'S
TIME FOR THEIR GUYS TO MEET
THEIR FAMILIES.
ARE YOU READY TO DO THIS?
HERE WE GO.
I'M JUST
EXCITED TO SEE HER.
IT'S JUST BEEN A REALLY LONG
TIME.
YEAH.
I JUST CAN'T WAIT TO TOUCH
HER, YOU KNOW.
ARE YOU GOING TO CRY?
I AM HOPING
NOT TO, BUT WE'LL
SEE.
DO YOU KNOW YOU'RE GOING TO
ASK, TONY?
WE KNOW YOU ARE THE BIG SCARY
ONE, SO...
NO.
HEY!
OH, MY BABY GIRL.
OH, I'M JUST SO EXCITED.
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT'S ALREADY
TIME FOR, LIKE, THEM TO MEET
EVERYONE.
I MISSED YOU SO MUCH.
I MISSED YOU.
HI.
I HAVE A FAMILY AND TWO
BEST FRIENDS WHO ARE VERY
OPINIONATED AND
WHO WILL NOT BE
AFRAID TO TELL
ME HOW THEY FEEL.
I REALLY JUST
HOPE THAT THEY SEE
WHAT I SEE BECAUSE HAVING MY
FAMILY'S APPROVAL IS HUGE.
I FEEL LIKE THERE
IS THIS, LIKE,
BIG STIGMA, OR, LIKE, PRESSURE
ABOUT MY DAD AND BIG TONY.
LIKE, I KNOW THEY'RE PROBABLY
FREAKING OUT.
OH, MY GOSH.
SO.
WHAT'S NEW?
SO WHAT'S NEW?
YOU'RE SMILING.
I'M DYING HERE.
WHO, WHO, WHO?
SO THIS HAS
BEEN THE CRAZIEST
THING EVER.
THIS WAS NOT EASY.
BUT I DO HAVE TWO INCREDIBLE
PEOPLE FOR YOU TO MEET.
AND I WANT YOU
GUYS TO KNOW THAT
I AM SO HAPPY.
I GUESS REALLY
WHAT I'M LOOKING
FOR JUST IN
GENERAL IS CLARITY.
BECAUSE I AM A BIT CONFLICTED.
I HAVE TALKED TO BOTH OF THEM
ABOUT ENGAGEMENT AND A LIFE
AFTER THIS AND WHAT WOULD IT
LOOK LIKE.
AND I DO REALLY, LIKE, HAVE
THESE FEELINGS
FOR BOTH OF THEM
AND I COULD SEE MY LIFE WITH
BOTH OF THEM.
DO THEY BOTH WANT KIDS?
THEY DO.
YES.
OKAY.
SO TODAY YOU'LL BE MEETING
AVEN.
AND TOMORROW YOU'LL BE MEETING
TINO.
OKAY.
IMMEDIATELY I KNEW I REALLY
LIKED AVEN, LIKE, I EVEN TOLD
GABBY, I'M LIKE, I LIKE THIS
ONE.
WHEN YOU SEE HIM, YOU'RE
GENUINELY GOING
TO BE, LIKE, WHY
DO YOU LOOK LIKE THAT?
IT'S ALMOST LIKE IT HURTS YOUR
FEELINGS.
OKAY, RIGHT.
HE IS SOMEONE THAT I TRUST
COMPLETELY AND,
LIKE, I KNOW IS
HERE FOR ME AND I KNOW HE'S
READY.
HAS HE SAID
ANYTHING TO YOU?
HE TOLD ME HE IS FALLING IN
LOVE WITH ME.
HE JUST HAS SOMETHING.
LIKE, YOU GUYS
KNOW MY BIG THING
IS, LIKE, SUPPORT AND, LIKE,
SOMEONE WHO'S GOING TO BE
SUPPORTIVE.
AND THERE WERE
CRAZY THINGS THAT
WOULD HAPPEN, AND THE FIRST
THING I'D SAY IS
"I JUST NEED TO
SEE AVEN."
LIKE, HE JUST MAKES ME FEEL
SO...
THAT IS HUGE, RACH.
SUPPORTED.
THAT'S HUGE.
I LIKE THE WAY YOU'RE
EXPLAINING WHO WE'RE GOING TO
MEET, BECAUSE THIS IS REALLY
MAKING IT SO MUCH
EASIER FOR US.
SO YOU'RE DOING A GREAT JOB OF
TELLING US
EVERYTHING WE WANT TO
KNOW.
I'M GOING TO GO GET AVEN.
I'M EXCITED.
AND I'LL BE
BACK IN A MINUTE.
LOOK AT THAT FACE.
I'M SO EXCITED.
I'M JUST EXCITED TO REALLY
TALK ABOUT OUR
RELATIONSHIP AND
I'M SO EXCITED
TO HEAR WHAT THEY
HAVE TO SAY, AND I REALLY JUST
HOPE IT'S ALL POSITIVE.
AVEN TOLD ME HE'S 100% READY
FOR AN ENGAGEMENT.
SO I'M VERY CONFIDENT IN AVEN
MEETING MY FAMILY.
HI.
HI, BEAUTIFUL.
HOW ARE YOU?
YOU LOOK SO GOOD.
YOU DO TOO.
HOW ARE YOU?
HI.
GOOD TO SEE YOU.
WHAT'S UP?
HI.
HOW ARE YOU FEELING?
I'M GOOD.
I'M EXCITED, A LITTLE NERVOUS.
DON'T BE NERVOUS.
I KNOW.
I JUST KNOW HOW YOU'RE FEELING
NOW.
LIKE, IT'S A REAL THING.
IT'LL BE OKAY.
I KNOW HOW IMPORTANT HER
PARENTS ARE TO RACHEL, AND I'M
REALLY EXCITED FOR TODAY.
I HOPE IT REALLY GOES WELL.
YOU READY TO GO?
EVERYTHING?
I'M GOOD, EVERYTHING.
OKAY.
GRAB MY HAND.
HELLO.
HOW ARE YOU GUYS?
HI, EVERYONE.
HOW'S IT GOING?
THIS IS AVEN.
HOW ARE YOU DOING?
GREAT TO MEET YOU.
I'M AVEN.
I WANT IT TO WORK
BETWEEN US AND
GET TO A POINT OF STARTING A
LIFE TOGETHER AND ALL OF THAT.
SO, YOU KNOW, FAMILY IS A BIG
FACTOR INTO THOSE DECISIONS.
BIG DAY.
HUGE.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
YEAH, I WAS REALLY LOOKING
FORWARD TO MEETING YOU GUYS.
THIS IS AMAZING.
I REALLY APPRECIATE IT.
OH, I HAVE SOMETHING FOR YOU
TOO.
I ALMOST FORGOT, IT'S IN MY
POCKET.
THERE YOU GO.
THANK YOU.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
MY WIFE WILL BE REALLY EXCITED
ABOUT THIS.
OH, MY GOSH.
YEAH, THIS IS FINALLY HERE.
I'VE HEARD A LOT
ABOUT YOU GUYS.
DID IT GO BY QUICK FOR YOU?
IT WENT BY REALLY QUICK.
BUT WE HAVE, LIKE, DONE A LOT
TOGETHER.
UP TO THIS POINT, SO IT FEELS
SLOW AT THE SAME TIME.
IT'S, LIKE, A WEIRD THING,
YOU KNOW.
YEAH.
TO BE AT THIS POINT, IT'S
JUST VERY SPECIAL, ESPECIALLY
SHE'S MET MY FAMILY TOO.
WE TALK ALL THE TIME ABOUT HOW
IMPORTANT THIS IS, SO I REALLY
APPRECIATE IT.
SHE'S VERY SPECIAL TO ME.
IT'S JUST AN HONOR TO MEET YOU
ALL.
WELL, WE ARE
REALLY HAPPY TO
MEET YOU TOO.
YEAH, WE'RE EXCITED.
I APPRECIATE IT.
SLIGHTLY NERVOUS.
YEAH, IT IS A NERVE-RACKING
EXPERIENCE BUT, LIKE, AFTER
HEARING EVERYTHING RACHEL SAID
ABOUT YOU BEFORE YOU CAME IN.
IT WAS NICE.
SOME GOOD STUFF.
SOME NICE THINGS.
SEE IF YOU CAN GET BIG TONY
TO SMILE.
TRYING MY HARDEST.
I GAVE HIM A CIGAR.
WE ARE GETTING SOMEWHERE.
TRYING.
I'VE BEEN
LOOKING FORWARD TO
IT, BUT YOU'RE ALWAYS NERVOUS
BECAUSE, YOU KNOW, YOU WANT TO
MAKE A GOOD IMPRESSION.
YOU WANT TO REALLY
REMIND THEM,
YOU KNOW, WHY YOU'RE HERE AND
HOW YOU FEEL
TOWARDS, YOU KNOW,
THEIR DAUGHTER.
LET'S GO TALK.
THE FIRST THING I SAID TO
RACHEL IS I DO NOT WANT TO END
UP ON BIG TONY'S BAD SIDE.
SO YOU THINK I'M
GOING TO NOT BE
HONEST WITH THAT GUY?
ME AND RACHEL ARE FALLING IN
LOVE WITH EACH OTHER.
I KNOW THAT, YOU KNOW, RACHEL
SEES SOMETHING IN ME AND A
FUTURE WITH ME
THE SAME WAY I DO
WITH HER.
I THINK TODAY IS, LIKE,
A BIG DAY TO PROVE THAT.
I'M HERE TO PUT YOU ON THE
SPOT, BECAUSE,
YOU KNOW, I DON'T
WANT TO HEAR SOMEBODY MUMBLING
AROUND.
ABSOLUTELY.
I WANT TO KNOW
WHY, YOU KNOW,
THIS IS MY DAUGHTER.
SHE'S MY PRIDE AND JOY.
AND NOBODY IS
GOING TO TAKE HER
AWAY FROM ME WITHOUT A FIGHT.
OF COURSE.
SO TOMORROW I'M GOING TO BE
SITTING IN THIS CHAIR, THERE'S
GOING TO BE A DIFFERENT GUY
SITTING IN THAT CHAIR.
YEAH.
SO WHAT ARE
YOU GOING TO SAY
TODAY THAT'S GOING TO MAKE ME
REMEMBER YOU BETTER THAN THE
OTHER GUY?
YEAH, I MEAN, I
THINK, YOU KNOW,
ONE THING, I'VE
REALLY TRIED TO
BE AS OPEN AS HONEST AND AS
MYSELF THROUGH ALL OF THIS.
I CONSIDER RACHEL'S
FEELINGS IN EVERY
DECISION I'VE
MADE GOING THROUGH
THIS BECAUSE
THIS ISN'T, LIKE,
A JOKE TO ME.
THIS IS MY LIFE
JUST AS MUCH AS
IT'S HERS, AND I WANT TO MAKE
SURE THAT IF WE
END UP TOGETHER,
THAT IT'S RIGHT
FOR BOTH OF US.
WHAT ARE YOUR FEELINGS?
'CAUSE SHE TOLD
ME HER FEELINGS
ABOUT YOU.
WHAT ARE YOUR FEELINGS ABOUT
HER?
ABSOLUTELY.
SO I'M GOING TO PUT YOU ON
THE SPOT NOW.
ABSOLUTELY.
SO I CAN SEE THAT WE SHARED A
LOT OF THE SAME VALUES, WHICH
WAS SO IMPORTANT.
SAME SENSE OF HUMOR.
YOU KNOW, WE LAUGH TOGETHER.
SHE'S OBVIOUSLY, YOU KNOW,
I THINK SHE'S GORGEOUS, ALL OF
THAT STUFF.
SO IT WAS PRETTY
MUCH EVERYTHING
FOR ME ALL COMBINED AT ONCE.
I COMMUNICATED TO HER AFTER MY
HOMETOWN THAT I'M FALLING IN
LOVE WITH HER.
I'M FALLING IN LOVE WITH YOUR
DAUGHTER.
AND THE FEELINGS
ARE SO STRONG.
AND IT'S BEEN A PROGRESSION
FOR US.
WE'VE BUILT ON EVERY SINGLE
MOMENT WE'VE HAD TOGETHER.
I WANT TO STRESS TO YOU JUST
ABOUT HOW STRONGLY I DO FEEL
TOWARDS RACHEL.
SO WHAT'S YOUR,
LIKE, INITIAL
FIRST IMPRESSION OF HIM?
OH, I LIKE HIM.
YEAH?
YEAH.
HE SEEMS VERY SWEET.
I MEAN, I LIKE THE WAY HE SAT
AND WAS RIGHT
AWAY HOLDING HANDS
WITH YOU AND THE WAY HE WAS
INTERACTING WITH US, HE SEEMED
PRETTY CONFIDENT.
YEAH.
WITH AVEN, I JUST FEEL LIKE I
TRUST HIM.
IF WE WERE TO BE AT THE END OF
THIS AND AVEN WAS
TO GET DOWN ON
ONE KNEE, HE WOULD BE THE MOST
INCREDIBLE PARTNER, AND I KNOW
THAT FOR SURE.
FOR SURE.
I HAVE, LIKE, NO
DOUBTS IN HIM.
I LOVE HEARING
YOU SAY THAT.
I LIKE THAT.
HE'S SO INCREDIBLE.
HE'S SO GREAT.
RACHEL, I LOVE
THE WAY YOU'RE
TALKING.
I CAN SEE IT.
IT'S OVERFLOWING.
I AM SO, SO HAPPY.
I FEEL LIKE ALL THE ANSWERS I
NEED, I KNOW.
SO I'M JUST HOPING
HE CAN, LIKE,
TELL YOU FROM HIS SIDE, HOW HE
FEELS AND SEE WHAT MATCHES UP.
RIGHT AND YOU THINK HE'S
READY TO GET DOWN ON ONE KNEE?
YES.
OKAY, GOOD.
WE TALKED ABOUT IT.
AT LENGTH.
OKAY.
YEAH.
OH, MY GOSH.
I LOVE THAT FACE.
YOU'RE SO HAPPY.
I KNOW, I'M SO HAPPY, YEAH.
YOU KNOW, I THOUGHT IT WAS
GOING TO BE WEIRD.
YOU KNOW, MY
DAUGHTER IS GETTING
ENGAGED, AND I MET THE GUY ONE
TIME.
HOW WEIRD THAT IS, YOU KNOW.
BUT THE MORE I'M
TALKING TO YOU,
THE MORE CONFIDENCE YOU'RE
GIVING ME, SO WOW.
IT'S A LITTLE WILD FOR ME TO
THINK THAT IN A COUPLE DAYS
SHE'LL BE ENGAGED.
BUT SHE WAS JUST GUSHING.
THERE WAS NO THINGS THAT I HAD
TO QUESTION HER ON.
SHE WAS JUST HAPPY.
SO I GUESS THIS IS KIND OF,
LIKE, THE BIG
QUESTION, BUT ONE,
HAVE YOU SAID THAT YOU WERE
FALLING IN LOVE
OR IN LOVE WITH
RACHEL?
YEAH, I'VE TOLD...
I EXPRESSED TO RACHEL AFTER MY
HOMETOWN THAT I'M FALLING IN
LOVE WITH HER.
OKAY.
YEAH.
I GUESS NOW, LIKE, THE NEXT
STEP, THIS ENGAGEMENT COULD
POTENTIALLY HAPPEN SO SOON,
LIKE, IN A MATTER OF DAYS,
WHERE ARE YOU?
DO YOU THINK THAT
COULD HAPPEN?
I WANT TO BE WITH RACHEL AT
THE END OF THIS,
LIKE, I WANT TO
HAVE A LIFE WITH HER.
AND I WANT THE
ENGAGEMENT ASPECT
OF IT TO BE PERFECT.
'CAUSE, FOR ME, LIKE, SEEING
WHAT MY PARENTS WENT THROUGH,
I WANT IT TO BE
A ONE-TIME SHOT
FOR US.
BUT, LIKE.
CAN YOU TELL US,
ARE YOU THERE?
BUT WHAT I WAS GOING TO SAY
IS, LIKE, I CAN,
LIKE, 1000% SEE
MYSELF GETTING THERE.
DO YOU HAVE ENOUGH TIME TO
GET THERE?
I DON'T KNOW.
I DON'T KNOW HOW MUCH TIME WE
HAVE LEFT.
BUT I AM FALLING IN LOVE WITH
HER, AND MY FEELINGS ARE VERY
STRONG.
HOW DOES IT
FEEL THAT I COULD
BE ENGAGED IN FIVE DAYS?
I THINK I WILL
BE, SO I'M GOING
TO BE ENGAGED IN FIVE DAYS.
I'M GOING TO SAY THAT VERY
CONFIDENTLY.
YOU KNOW, I'LL TAKE IT
ONE DAY AT A TIME.
I FEEL LIKE HE REALLY IS IN
THAT PLACE WHERE HE IS READY.
WHEN I TELL YOU EVERYTHING I
WANT IN A PARTNER, I FEEL LIKE
HE EMBODIES ALL OF THAT.
A FATHER WANTS
TO HEAR THAT.
I DON'T WANT TO PUT MY GUARD
DOWN ALREADY, BUT I LIKED HIM
JUST BECAUSE OF
THE WAY YOU WERE
TALKING ABOUT HIM.
I LOVE SEEING YOU THAT HAPPY.
WHEN YOU WALK
ABOVE THE GROUND.
AS FAR AS, LIKE, WANTING TO
BE WITH HER AFTER
ALL THIS, IS,
LIKE, A NO-DOUBT MY MIND.
AND GETTING TO A POINT OF A
MARRIAGE AND A
LIFE TOGETHER IS
SOMETHING I WANT WITH HER.
IT'S JUST ABOUT THE TIMING
OF IT.
HAVE YOU SAID THAT TO HER?
I'VE EXPRESSED THAT TO HER.
HAVE YOU SAID,
"I DON'T KNOW
THAT I WANT TO GET ENGAGED AT
THE END OF THIS"?
I'VE EXPRESSED
THAT I'M READY
FOR AN ENGAGEMENT.
LIKE, AS FAR AS MY LIFE IS
CONCERNED, LIKE,
WHERE I'M AT IN
LIFE.
SHE IS READY FOR AN
ENGAGEMENT.
SHE TALKS ABOUT
IT ALL THE TIME.
AND IF SHE COMES HOME NOT
ENGAGED, THAT'S GOING TO BE
REALLY HARD.
YEAH.
WELL, I THINK ULTIMATELY IT
IS A RED FLAG.
IT'S NOT HER INTENTION TO COME
HOME WITH A BOYFRIEND.
I DO THINK AVEN NOT WANTING TO
BE ENGAGED AT THE END OF THIS
PROCESS WILL BE
A DEAL BREAKER.
ENGAGEMENT IS NO JOKE.
A MARRIAGE IS NO JOKE.
I JUST KNOW THAT'S HER
INTENTION.
YEAH.
SO JUST TO
KEEP THAT IN MIND.
DO YOU WISH YOU COULD DATE
THE MOST ELIGIBLE
BACHELORS AND
BACHELORETTES IN AMERICA?
YOU CAN.
APPLIED TO BE ON THE BACHELOR.
GO TO ABC.com/Casting NOW.
WELCOME BACK TO THE LIVE
FINALE OF "THE BACHELORETTE."
I'M HERE WITH OUR STUDIO
AUDIENCE, AND OF COURSE
GABBY AND RACHEL.
I LOVE SEEING BIG TONY IN THAT
PINK SHIRT HE WAS WEARING.
THAT'S ALL
EVERYBODY IS TALKING
ABOUT ON SOCIAL MEDIA.
#RealMenWearPink.
WE WATCHED AS AVEN REVEALED HE
MIGHT NOT BE READY TO GET
ENGAGED.
IS THAT GOING TO BE A
DEAL BREAKER FOR RACHEL?
LET'S FIND OUT.
SO TELL ME EVERYTHING.
TELL ME EVERYTHING.
RIGHT.
I FEEL, LIKE, THIS WEEK, LIKE,
I GAINED SO MUCH CLARITY IN MY
OVERNIGHTS.
AND, LIKE, I WOULD NEVER BRING
AVEN HERE IF I
GENUINELY, LIKE,
DIDN'T SEE THIS
FUTURE WITH HIM
AND IF HE DIDN'T
FEEL LIKE THIS
COULD BE MY HUSBAND.
NOT ONLY COULD IT BE,
BUT I SEE IT.
MM-HMM.
TODAY IS JUST
AS AMAZING AS I
THOUGHT IT WOULD BE.
MY FAMILY LOVES AVEN.
I AM READY FOR AN ENGAGEMENT.
THEY KNOW HOW BIG
OF A DEAL THIS
IS FOR ME, SO I COULD NOT BE
HAPPIER.
ON PAPER...
MM-HMM, HE'S
THE PERFECT GUY.
HE'S THE CHOICE.
LIKE, IF YOU DON'T CHOOSE HIM,
YOU ARE STUPID.
AND IT'S THE WAY THAT YOU,
LIKE, SAY, LIKE,
WHEN YOU'RE IN
A STRESSFUL
SITUATION, YOU LOOK
FOR HIM.
LIKE, YOU WANT THAT.
THAT'S VALUABLE.
SPEAKING ON AVEN,
AFTER TALKING WITH HIM.
I WAS GOING TO SAY, DID YOU
GUYS ASK HIM?
DID YOU KILL HIM?
DID HE KILL HIM?
NO, HE DIDN'T.
HE JUST SAID HE JUST WAS
UNSURE THAT, LIKE, THERE WOULD
BE AN ENGAGEMENT AT THE END.
LIKE, HE COULDN'T GIVE AN
ANSWER.
HE COULDN'T GIVE ME AN ANSWER.
I DON'T KNOW IF HE'S
NECESSARILY READY FOR AN
ENGAGEMENT BUT THE WAY
THAT HE... LET
ME FINISH BEFORE
YOU FREAK OUT.
BUT, LIKE, THE WAY HE WORDS IT
IS, HE KNOWS HE
WANTS TO BE WITH
YOU.
I THINK HE'S
BEING VERY LOGICAL
ABOUT THIS.
HE SAID I WANT
RACHEL IN MY LIFE
FOREVER.
HE'S, LIKE, THAT'S NOT A
QUESTION.
IT'S, LIKE, DO WE GET ENGAGED
RIGHT AWAY?
WITH HER COMPLETELY. G HONEST-
HE'S, LIKE...
YEAH, BUT THIS IS, LIKE,
SHOCKING BECAUSE THIS IS NOT
WHAT HE TOLD ME.
HE TOLD US THAT HE TOLD YOU
ALL OF THIS.
I MEAN, HE
TOLD ME, HE'S LIKE
I FEEL CONFIDENT, LIKE 100%
READY.
LIKE, I FEEL GOOD.
LIKE, I WOULD
NEVER BRING HIM IN
FRONT OF YOU IF I DIDN'T THINK
SOMEONE WAS, LIKE, READY 100%.
THIS IS, LIKE, SHOCKING.
LIKE, I REALLY THOUGHT HE WAS,
LIKE, GOING TO
SIT DOWN WITH YOU
AND BE LIKE, 100%.
YEAH, NO.
HE WASN'T LIKE THAT.
WHOA.
NO.
HE'S EXCITED.
HE'S EXCITED FOR SURE.
LIKE, HE DOES...
HE CARES ABOUT
YOU SO DEEPLY.
RIGHT, BUT I'M
NOT COMING OUT
OF THIS, LIKE, NOT ENGAGED.
AND I REALLY, LIKE, I'M HAPPY
THAT YOU GUYS
DID ALSO GET THIS
CLARITY, TOO, BECAUSE IT'S
SOMETHING I'M
OBVIOUSLY GOING TO
HAVE TO TALK TO HIM ABOUT, YOU
KNOW.
TO NOT FULLY CONVINCE YOU BOTH
THAT HE IS 100%
FOR ME, THAT'S,
LIKE, A VERY BIG WORRY FOR ME.
MM-HMM.
ESPECIALLY
WITH THE FACT THAT
THIS WHOLE JOURNEY HAS BEEN
REALLY HARD.
LIKE, NOW TO HAVE
ANOTHER THING.
YOU KNOW, I KNOW WHAT YOUR
EXPECTATION IS OUT OF THIS.
AND IF HIS EXPECTATION IS NOT
THE SAME, THEN WE HAVE
A PROBLEM.
MM-HMM.
I DON'T KNOW WHY.
IT'S A CONVERSATION
YOU'RE GOING
TO HAVE TO HAVE WITH HIM.
I DO NOT THINK
THIS WAS GOING
TO HAPPEN WITH AVEN AT ALL.
I'M SHOCKED.
I MEAN, ME AND AVEN TALKED AT
LENGTH ABOUT
BEING READY FOR AN
ENGAGEMENT AND BEING READY FOR
THIS NEXT STEP, AND THIS IS
WHAT'S HAPPENING IN A COUPLE
DAYS.
SO WHY WOULD YOU SAY ONE THING
TO ME AND THEN
SAY ANOTHER THING
TO MY FRIENDS AND FAMILY?
LIKE, I APPRECIATE
YOUR HONESTY,
BUT WHY DID YOU LIE TO ME?
OH, THAT WAS AMAZING.
JUST MEETING ALL OF THEM.
LIKE, THE CONVERSATION I HAD
WITH NATE AND SAM.
YEAH, HOW DID THAT GO?
IT WENT SO WELL.
I COULD JUST TELL
HOW MUCH THEY
CARE ABOUT YOU
AND I CAN SEE WHY
YOU HAVE THEM HERE.
THEY ASKED SOME TOUGH STUFF.
AND I JUST TRIED
TO BE AS HONEST
AND OPEN WITH EVERYONE ABOUT,
YOU KNOW, WHERE WE'RE AT AND
WHERE I'M AT AND EVERYTHING.
SO YEAH, DID YOU, LIKE, HAVE
ANYTHING THAT YOU
WANTED TO ASK?
OKAY.
YEAH.
SO OBVIOUSLY I TOLD THEM
EVERYTHING I FELT AND, LIKE,
THEY ARE SO HAPPY TO SEE ME SO
HAPPY.
I GUESS, LIKE, I'M, LIKE,
A LITTLE BIT CONCERNED.
BECAUSE THEY EXPRESSED TO ME
THAT MAY BE YOU MIGHT NOT BE
READY FOR AN ENGAGEMENT.
YEAH, SO IT'S NOT ABOUT NOT
BEING READY.
AND I WANT YOU TO KNOW THAT
NOTHING HAS
CHANGED IN TERMS OF
HOW I FEEL ABOUT YOU.
I'M FALLING IN LOVE WITH YOU.
AND I SEE A LIFE WITH YOU
AFTER THIS.
AND I WANT TO
GET TO THAT POINT
WITH YOU SO MUCH.
LIKE, I JUST... I JUST WANT TO
MAKE SURE THAT IT'S 100% RIGHT
FOR BOTH OF US RIGHT NOW.
AND IN THIS VERY
MOMENT IN TIME.
YEAH, I'M JUST, LIKE, VERY
CONFUSED, I GUESS, BECAUSE,
LIKE, FOR ME, LIKE, WE TALKED
ABOUT, LIKE, ENGAGEMENT AND
AFTER THIS AND, LIKE, YOU KNOW
THIS IS WHAT I WANT SO, LIKE,
YOU DON'T FEEL
LIKE YOU'RE READY
TO GET ENGAGED?
I DO FEEL LIKE I'M READY TO
GET ENGAGED.
I JUST WANT TO MAKE SURE THAT
IT'S RIGHT.
I'M SO CONFUSED.
THAT'S NOT WHAT YOU TOLD ME.
I...
I STRESSED TO THEM I WANT
NOTHING MORE THAN
TO BE WITH YOU
AFTER THIS.
I KNOW THAT THERE'S STILL
SOMEBODY INVOLVED IN THIS.
THAT'S ANOTHER THING.
OKAY, BUT AVEN,
THIS IS ABOUT US.
I KNOW.
BUT RACHEL, THIS
IS, LIKE, BOTH
OF OUR LIVES.
THIS IS A VERY BIG DEAL.
I KNOW, AND I'M BEING
SERIOUS.
I KNOW YOU ARE.
IS IT, LIKE, CRAZY FOR ME TO
THINK THAT, LIKE,
WE ARE GETTING
TO THAT POINT AND I'M JUST
TRYING TO MAKE SURE...
IT'S NOT CRAZY,
BUT WE TALKED
ABOUT THIS.
WHY AM I TELLING EVERYONE IN
THERE, "I'M SERIOUS," AND
YOU'RE, LIKE,
"I'M NOT READY TO
GET ENGAGED."
SO, LIKE, WHY IS
THAT HAPPENING?
YOU UNDERSTAND
WHERE I'M COMING
FROM?
I DO.
LIKE, THIS IS,
LIKE, HARD FOR
ME BECAUSE I SEE
YOU AT THE END
OF THIS.
LIKE, THAT'S HARD FOR ME TO
HEAR.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND WHY THEY
ARE SITTING THERE
BEING, LIKE "I
DON'T THINK HE'S READY TO GET
ENGAGED."
LIKE, WHERE IS
THAT COMING FROM?
IT'S NOT COMING
FROM ANYTHING
THAT HAS TO DO
WITH WHERE I'M AT
WITH YOU.
I SEE US IN THE
END OF THIS TOO,
RACHEL.
I DO.
I'M TRYING TO
MAKE SURE THAT THE
ENGAGEMENT IS THE
BEST THING FOR
BOTH OF US.
MY FEELING TOWARDS
YOU HAVE NOT
CHANGED AT ALL.
AT ALL.
I KNOW BUT, LIKE, BUT AVEN
THIS IS, LIKE, I WANTED YOU...
I KNOW HOW I FEEL ABOUT YOU.
AND, LIKE, I
WANTED YOU TO WALK
IN THERE AND, LIKE, BE, LIKE,
100%.
LIKE, I DON'T
LIKE PEOPLE COMING
UP TO ME AND BEING LIKE,
"RACHEL, I DON'T KNOW."
LIKE, THAT'S HARD FOR ME.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND THAT?
LIKE, I WANTED
EVERYONE IN THERE
TO BE CONFIDENT.
LIKE, YOU HAVE TO UNDERSTAND
WHERE THIS IS COMING FROM.
I UNDERSTAND WHERE IT'S
COMING FROM.
LIKE, I WAS SO...
I'M TRYING.
I'M TRYING NOT
I'M TRYING TO
JUST BE AS OPEN WITH YOU ABOUT
THIS.
I WANT TO TALK ABOUT THIS.
I'M LISTENING TO YOU.
AND I'M SORRY
IF I AM COMING
OFF STRONG RIGHT NOW.
I'M NOT TRYING TO.
I JUST REALLY
CARE ABOUT YOU AND
I CARE ABOUT US.
THIS IS A BIG DEAL.
LIKE, LIKE, I HAVE NO DOUBT IN
MY MIND ABOUT US
GETTING THERE.
WHETHER IT'S IN A FEW DAYS
OR WHATEVER THE CASE MAY BE,
RACHEL.
I JUST WANT TO BE WITH YOU.
AND I'M SORRY IF
WHAT THEY SAID
YOU CAME OFF DIFFERENTLY.
BUT WHAT IF
WHAT I WANT IS TO
GET ENGAGED?
IF THAT'S WHAT YOU WANT,
THEN...
BUT I'M NOT GOING TO FORCE
YOU INTO SOMETHING THAT YOU
DON'T WANT.
IT'S NOT ABOUT NOT
WANTING IT.
I'M JUST TELLING YOU
WHERE I'M AT.
LIKE, I'M TRYING TO BE HONEST
WITH YOU.
AND TELL YOU WHERE I'M AT.
AND HOW I FEEL ABOUT YOU.
WHY ARE YOU SHAKING YOUR HEAD
AT ME?
BECAUSE I'M JUST, LIKE,
SO CONFUSED.
LIKE...
OH, MY GOODNESS.
EVERYTHING WE'VE DONE TO THIS
POINT HAS MADE
ME FEEL THE WAY I
FEEL ABOUT YOU.
I'M FALLING IN LOVE WITH YOU.
I'M NOT GOING TO SIT HERE AND
THROW WORDS AROUND
IN YOUR FACE
BECAUSE IT MAKES YOU HAPPY.
I'M GOING TO BE
HONEST WITH YOU.
I KNOW, BUT YOU TOLD ME...
THAT'S ONLY FAIR TO YOU.
THAT'S WHAT YOU TOLD ME.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
YOU TOLD ME YOU WERE READY
FOR AN ENGAGEMENT.
I AM READY.
BUT WHY ARE
THEY SAYING THAT
YOU SAID YOU WEREN'T?
BECAUSE I WANT TO MAKE SURE
THAT THE TIMING
OF IT IS RIGHT,
RACHEL.
WHY ARE YOU YELLING AT ME?
I'M SORRY.
I'M NOT TRYING TO YELL.
I'M JUST VERY... I'M TRYING.
I'M VERY PASSIONATE.
I'M SORRY.
I'M NOT TRYING TO YELL AT YOU.
ALL I WANTED
WAS FOR US TO GO
INTO THIS ON THE SAME PAGE.
SO NOW WHY DO I FEEL LIKE YOU
JUST DIDN'T TELL ME WHAT PAGE
YOU WERE ON.
I DIDN'T GET THE CHANCE TO
TALK TO YOU AFTER LAST WEEK.
AFTER OVERNIGHTS,
YOU CHANGED
YOUR MIND?
NO, DIDN'T.
OH, MY GOSH.
I DID NOT CHANGE MY MIND ABOUT
ANYTHING.
YOU NEED TO
UNDERSTAND ALSO,
LIKE, I WANT
SOMEONE WHO CAN SIT
IN FRONT OF MY FAMILY AND BE
LIKE, "THIS IS 100%.
I'M SO CONFIDENT."
LIKE, THE FACT THAT YOU'RE,
LIKE, "I DON'T KNOW,"
THAT'S, LIKE, HARD FOR ME.
I'M NOT INCONFIDENT IN US.
AT ALL.
I WANT YOU IN THE END OF THIS.
I JUST WANT TO MAKE SURE THAT
ENGAGEMENT IS THE RIGHT THING
FOR BOTH OF US AT THIS TIME
MUTUALLY, OKAY?
I PROMISE YOU.
AND I'M SORRY.
I DO NOT WANT TO EVER SEE YOU
UPSET, ESPECIALLY
IF IT'S LIKE,
LIKE, ME MAKING YOU UPSET.
LIKE, I CAN'T...
I DON'T WANT THAT AT ALL.
YEAH.
READY?
I REALLY DON'T
WANT TO END THIS
ON A BAD NOTE.
IT'S NOT A BAD NOTE.
I UNDERSTAND.
I JUST NEED YOU
TO UNDERSTAND ME TOO.
I KNOW, AND THAT'S...
I KNOW.
I UNDERSTAND.
I'M JUST TRYING TO BE HONEST
WITH YOU.
AND I KNOW YOU ARE.
EVERYTHING WE'RE DOING IS
OBVIOUSLY ADDING TO THIS.
I KNOW.
AND I KNOW YOU'RE
BEING HONEST.
IT'S NOT A BAD NOTE.
OKAY.
I'LL SEE YOU SOON.
OKAY?
I'M SORRY.
I HAD A REALLY GRAT
CONVERSATION WITH ALL OF THEM.
I LOVE ALL OF THEM.
AND I CAME IN
HERE TRYING TO BE
MYSELF AND BE
REAL AND BE HONEST
AND CONSIDER YOUR FEELINGS
IN ALL OF THIS.
AND I'M HERE FOR YOU, OKAY?
I AM.
I WANT TO BE WITH YOU.
I NEED YOU TO
KNOW THAT BEFORE I
WALK AWAY FROM HERE.
OKAY.
OKAY?
ARE YOU OKAY?
I'M OKAY.
PROMISE.
MM-HMM.
I'LL SEE YOU LATER.
SEE YOU.
OKAY.
YEAH.
I JUST FEEL SHOOK UP.
AT THIS POINT, I
JUST REALLY AM,
LIKE, NOT SURE HOW AVEN AND I
MOVE FORWARD FROM IT.
I JUST FEEL REALLY CONFUSED
AND BLINDSIDED.
LIKE, HOW AM I
SUPPOSED TO HAVE
CONFIDENCE IN ANYTHING ANYONE
SAYS TO ME?
LIKE, HOW AM I
SUPPOSED TO TRUST
ANYONE?
EVERYONE IS LYING TO ME.
IS IT BETTER JUST TO LEAVE BY
MYSELF?
LIKE, WHAT AM I
SUPPOSED TO DO?
WELCOME BACK
TO THE TWO-NIGHT
LIVE FINALE OF
"THE BACHELORETTE!"
GABBY AND RACHEL ARE HERE
WATCHING ALONG WITH OUR STUDIO
AUDIENCE AND THE REST OF
AMERICA.
ALL I'VE GOT TO
SAY I FEEL LIKE
EVERYONE HERE HONESTLY IS A
LITTLE BIT SHOCKED
BY WHAT THEY
JUST SAW BECAUSE I DON'T THINK
ANYONE REALLY EXPECTED AVEN TO
EVER QUESTION GETTING ENGAGED.
RACHEL, WATCH YOUR FACE IN THE
VIDEO AND YOU WERE TALKING TO
AVEN, I THINK IT SAYS IT ALL.
WHAT WAS GOING
THROUGH YOUR MIND
WHEN AVEN WAS EXPRESSING HIS
TREPIDATION WITH A PROPOSAL?
I THINK FOR ME IT WAS JUST
REALLY HARD BECAUSE I DID WALK
IN SO CONFIDENT.
IT'S A KIND OF GET HIT WITH
THAT, IT WAS JUST REALLY TOUGH
FOR ME.
YOU THOUGHT YOU WERE ON THE
SAME PAGE.
GABBY, CAN YOU HELP PEOPLE AT
HOME UNDERSTAND
JUST HOW INTENSE
ARE THOSE CONVERSATIONS YOU'RE
HAVING ABOUT COMMITMENT?
YOU KNOW THAT A PROPOSAL, IT
MIGHT BE DAYS AWAY.
I THINK THESE CONVERSATIONS
ARE MAKE OR BREAK AND IT DOES
SEEM LIKE THE END DATE SOMEHOW
SPEEDS UP THEN
YOU HAVE TO WEIGH
WHAT YOU'RE GOING THROUGH.
THAT'S WHEN THINGS CATCH UP TO
YOU.
YOU HAVE TO BE HONEST WITH
YOURSELF AND KNOW
WHAT YOU WANT
WHICH I THINK
THAT'S WHAT RACHEL
DID.
EVEN WITH
AVEN'S HESITATIONS
AT THAT POINT,
YOU STILL WANTED
TO MOVE FORWARD.
HOW COME?
I MEAN, I JUST REALLY WAS
HOPING THIS WAS SOMETHING WE
COULD GET PAST THAT WE COULD
KIND OF GET BACK ON THE SAME
PAGE.
THAT'S WHAT I WAS HOPING FOR.
YOU WEREN'T THE ONLY ONE
HAVING FAMILY IN MEXICO.
GABBY, IT IS ERICH'S TURN TO
MEET YOUR FAMILY AND YOUR
BELOVED GRANDPA.
IT'S GOING TO BE
THE SECOND TIME
THAT HE MEETS JOHN.
THAT'S RIGHT.
A DOUBLE DOSE OF GRANDPA JOHN.
A DOUBLE SHOT.
HOW IS IT GOING TO GO?
LET'S TAKE A LOOK.
READY TO SEE GABBY.
I KNOW.
YEAH.
IT'S HARD WHEN
YOU CAN'T REALLY
HEAR FROM HER.
WELL, MY GUESS IS SHE FOUND
HER PERFECT PERSON.
THERE'S OUR GIRL!
HEY, SHRIMP.
OH, MY GOSH, GRANDPA,
YOU LOOK SO NICE.
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
I DON'T ALWAYS LOOK NICE?
I LOVE MY
FAMILY, SO, SO MUCH
AND I'M SO GRATEFUL THAT THEY
ARE HERE.
I'M JUST EXCITED JUST HONESTLY
TO BE IN THEIR PRESENCE AND TO
GIVE THEM ALL A HUG.
IT'S SO GOOD TO SEE YOU ALL.
THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR COMING.
THEY LOVE ME UNCONDITIONALLY
WHICH IS THE BEST
KIND OF LOVE.
IT'S, LIKE, A SAFE LOVE.
SO WE HAVE TO
HEAR, HOW MANY?
HOW MANY WHAT?
HOW MANY
SUITORS DO YOU HAVE
LEFT?
SO ERICH IS
THE ONLY ONE THAT
I WANT YOU GUYS TO MEET.
I KNOW ERICH.
HE'S A.
BUT THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
I LOVE HIM ANYHOW.
YEAH.
GRANDPA CAME ON A DATE AND THE
ONE THAT HE CAME ON WAS ERICH.
I REALLY LIKED HIM A LOT.
WELL, I DID
TELL HIM I LOVED
HIM.
OH.
WE WERE GOING TO ASK THAT.
I KNOW.
I MEAN.
WELL, HE'S A LIKABLE GUY.
I'M SURE IF YOU SAID IT,
YOU MEANT IT.
YEAH.
GOOD FOR YOU.
SO PROUD OF YOU.
YEAH.
SO I'M GOING TO GO GET HIM.
OKAY.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
I DIDN'T THINK THIS DAY WOULD
EVER COME.
I DIDN'T THINK MY FAMILY
WOULD EVER REALLY BE MEETING A
POTENTIAL HUSBAND.
HI.
SO FOR ME KIND
OF COMING IN AND
TELLING THEM TODAY
THAT ERICH IS
THE PERSON THAT I WANT TO BE
WITH NOW AND FOREVER
FEELS SO CRAZY.
HI.
THIS IS ERICH.
HI, HOW ARE YOU?
HOW'S IT GOING?
HI, THIS IS MY AUNT JULIE.
YES, HI.
I KNOW YOU.
HOW ARE YOU?
ARE YOU DOING ANY BOWLING
BETWEEN YOUR LEGS ANYMORE?
NO.
I DIDN'T GET ANY BETTER.
HOW'S IT GOING?
NICE TO MEET YOU.
NICE TO MEET YOU, ERICH.
I WANT THEM TO ACCEPT ERICH
AND I WANT ERICH
TO ACCEPT THEM
IN A WAY THAT HE
CAN SEE A LIFE
WITH ME AND WITH THEM.
SO HOW WAS YOUR HOMETOWN?
MY HOMETOWN WAS AMAZING.
LIKE, I KNEW GOING INTO THAT,
LIKE, I REALLY WANTED GABBY TO
MEET MY PARENTS.
AND THEY WERE JUST, LIKE,
OBSESSED WITH HER.
REALLY?
OH.
THE MOST APPROVAL AND
VALIDATION YOU COULD EVER GET
IS, LIKE, THE PEOPLE THAT MEAN
THE MOST TO YOU.
ABSOLUTELY, ABSOLUTELY.
SO AFTER THAT, I WAS PRETTY
CONVINCED THAT,
YOU KNOW, I WAS
FALLING IN LOVE WITH HER AND I
WANTED TO TAKE THAT NIGHT TO
JUST BE, LIKE,
THIS WAS A REALLY
BEAUTIFUL AND
SPECIAL DAY FOR ME
AND, YOU KNOW, I AM FALLING IN
LOVE WITH YOU.
I NEEDED TO TELL HER BECAUSE I
DON'T WANT TO WALK OUT OF HERE
JUST NOT BEING 100% HONEST
AND TRUE TO THIS.
I DON'T WANT TO
WALK OUT OF HERE
WITH ANY REGRETS.
I TOLD HIM
EARLIER, YOU KNOW,
WITH EVERYTHING WE'VE BEEN
THROUGH AND HOW
I FEEL ABOUT YOU
AND HOW MUCH YOU
MEAN TO ME AND
STUFF.
BUT HEARING YOU SAY IT TO THEM
OBVIOUSLY MEANS THE WORLD.
SO CHEERS.
I'LL DRINK TO THAT.
I THINK GABBY IS DEFINITELY
IN LOVE.
I MEAN, SHE SAID IT.
SHE LOOKS IT.
YOU CAN TELL JUST
FROM THE GLEAM
IN HER FACE THAT SHE POSSIBLY
HAS FOUND THE PERSON SHE'LL
SPEND THE REST
OF HER LIFE WITH.
AND I THINK HE WOULD FIT IN
PERFECTLY BECAUSE WE ARE A FUN
FAMILY.
WE DO ENJOY EACH OTHER'S
COMPANY.
WE LIKE BEING TOGETHER.
WE'RE VERY CLOSE.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
I LIKE ERICH.
HE'S A KEEPER.
YEAH, HE IS.
MORE IMPORTANT, WHAT DO YOU
THINK ABOUT HIM?
HE'S BEEN,
LIKE, NOTHING BUT
REALLY, REALLY GOOD TO ME.
HIM EVEN BEING WITH THE FAMILY
AND BEING ABLE TO SAY HOW HE
FELT ABOUT ME, LIKE, WASN'T
EXPECTING HIM TO DO THAT.
I HOPE HE WOULDN'T DO THAT
UNLESS HE WANTED TO...
I'M SURE, I'M SURE HE
WOULDN'T SAY IT
WITHOUT MEANING
IT.
YEAH.
SO I THINK
HE'S SINCERE ABOUT
IT.
YOUR GRANDMA WOULD BE TICKLED
PINK.
I REALLY WISH SHE COULD HAVE
BEEN HERE FOR THIS.
ME TOO.
SHE WOULD HAVE LOVED IT.
I KNOW.
AND SHE WOULD'VE GIVEN YOU
THE SAME ADVICE
I'M GIVING YOU.
IT'S GOT TO BE 90-90.
NOT JUST 50-50.
YEAH.
OKAY.
ALL RIGHT, SWEETHEART.
I LOVE YOU.
I LOVE YOU, I LOVE YOU,
YOU TAKE CARE.
I LOVE YOU TOO.
I JUST GET EMOTIONAL.
I'M SORRY.
OH, GRANDPA.
THAT'S OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
I MEAN, I'M SO GRATEFUL FOR
YOU GUYS AND...
ME TOO.
I KNOW.
I WISH...
I'M GRATEFUL TO HAVE A DANG
BAD BEAUTIFUL GRANDDAUGHTER.
TALKING TO MY GRANDPA IS
ALWAYS, LIKE, A
BREATH OF FRESH
AIR.
YOU KNOW, HE DID GET REALLY
EMOTIONAL WITH ME TODAY AND
HEARING THAT I'M LOVED FROM MY
GRANDPA AND HAVING HIM GIVE IT
TO ME SO FREELY,
HONESTLY, MEANS
EVERYTHING.
IT'S NICE TO
FINALLY MEET YOU
AFTER THAT INTRODUCTION,
HOLY COW, GABBY SEEMS PRETTY
EXCITED.
HOW DO YOU FEEL?
OBVIOULY YOU
EXPRESSED A LITTLE
BIT ALREADY.
WHY DO YOU KNOW, I GUESS, THAT
GABBY IS THE RIGHT PERSON?
IF YOU REALLY FEEL THAT WAY?
LIKE, WE HAD THIS CRAZY
CONNECTION FROM THE BEGINNING
AND I WAS HONESTLY INTIMIDATED
BY HER.
BECAUSE SHE WAS,
LIKE, MAKING A
LOT OF JOKES AND
PICKING POINTS
OF MY INSECURITIES.
I WAS LIKE, "OKAY, THIS IS,
LIKE..."
BUT WHAT I DIDN'T REALIZE WAS
THAT I WAS GOING TO FALL FOR
YOUR DAUGHTER AND I'M OBSESSED
WITH HER.
I THINK SHE'S AN
AMAZING PERSON
AND I CAN'T IMAGINE MY LIFE
WITHOUT HER AT THIS POINT.
WOW.
THAT MAKES US HAPPY.
YEAH, THAT DOES.
YEAH.
WE JUST LIKE THE FACT THAT
SHE GOES, "WELL, I COULD HAVE
BROUGHT THESE OTHER PEOPLE.
BUT WHY, WHEN I KNOW WHO I
WANT?"
SHE IS VERY CERTAIN FOR THE
FIRST TIME IN HER LIFE.
WE ARE KIND OF GUARDED OVER
HER HEART, SO WE
DON'T WANT HER
TO GET HURT.
NO.
EXACTLY.
JUST BECAUSE OF
WHAT SHE'S GONE
THROUGH, YOU KNOW, WITH MYSELF
AND HER MOM EARLY ON.
SHE'S BEEN THROUGH A LOT.
I THINK SHE NEEDS SOMEBODY TO
VALIDATE THAT SHE
IS WORTHY OF A
GOOD RELATIONSHIP.
YEAH.
YOU KNOW.
BECAUSE SHE IS.
GABBY'S BEEN THROUGH A LOT
AND SHE REALLY
DOES WANT TO FIND
LOVE.
I LIKE ERICH A LOT, AND WE ALL
WANT GABBY TO FINALLY SETTLE
DOWN AT SOME POINT IN TIME.
SO IT WOULD BE
GOOD IF SHE DOES.
YOU'VE NEVER COME HOME WITH
SOMEBODY WHERE
YOU SAID "THIS IS
HIM."
I MEAN, WHY ARE YOU SO SURE?
HOW DO YOU KNOW THAT A COUPLE
WEEKS FROM NOW,
YOU'RE NOT GOING
TO BE LIKE "YEAH, THAT WAS
GOOD."
BUT WHAT'S DIFFERENT?
I THINK THAT'S
I'VE ALMOST
BEEN AT ODDS WITH MYSELF WITH
HIM A LITTLE BIT
BECAUSE I THINK
IT WAS SOME OF
THE "TOO GOOD TO
BE TRUE."
I CAN'T BELIEVE,
LIKE, I'VE KIND
OF MET SOMEONE LIKE ERICH.
HE JUST LOVES ME
IN A WAY THAT I
REALLY HAVEN'T HAD BEFORE.
THAT I KNOW I NEED.
YOU DESERVE IT.
YEAH.
YOU DO.
YOU'VE BEEN THROUGH A LOT.
YEAH.
I DO REALLY THINK WE CAN LAST
A LONG TIME.
WHICH I THINK IS WHY I GET SO
EMOTIONAL.
YEAH.
YOU JUST NEED TO TRUST
YOURSELF.
YEAH.
DON'T DOUBT YOURSELF.
WHICH IS HARD, I MEAN, IT'S A
BATTLE EVERY DAY, EVEN COMING
TODAY, I'M LIKE "IS HE STILL
HERE?"
BUT I THINK WHEN SOMETHING IS
THAT GOOD, YOU'RE
AFRAID TO LOSE
IT.
RIGHT.
SO THAT'S HOW
I AM WITH HIM.
I LOVE ERICH MORE THAN I EVER
THOUGHT I COULD REALLY LOVE
SOMEONE.
I GET EMOTIONAL THINKING ABOUT
MY DAD TALKING TO HIM.
BREATHE, OKAY?
YOU'RE OKAY.
JUST TAKE A MINUTE.
BECAUSE IT'S LIKE, I DON'T
KNOW IF HE EVER
THOUGHT HE WOULD
HAVE THESE CONVERSATIONS WITH
ANYONE.
ALL OF THIS EXACERBATES,
YOU KNOW, NOT HAVING, LIKE,
REALLY FELT LOVE FROM MOM
AND STUFF.
I KNOW.
I HATE THAT FOR YOU.
I KNOW, BUT...
THAT SUCKS.
IT'S OKAY.
NO, IT'S REALLY NOT OKAY.
YOU KNOW, IT'S NOT.
AND YOU SHOULDN'T
HAVE HAD TO GO
THROUGH THAT.
I'M REALLY SORRY THAT YOU DID.
I DON'T KNOW IF IT WILL,
LIKE, SEND A MESSAGE TO ERICH
THAT I'M, LIKE, UNLOVABLE.
IT'S, LIKE, HOW IT MAKES ME
FEEL.
I GET IT.
BUT PROMISE ME SOMETHING.
DON'T HIDE THIS FROM ERICH.
IF YOU TRULY FEEL
LIKE ERICH IS
THE ONE FOR YOU,
LET HIM BE THE
ONE TO UNDERSTAND YOU.
YOU HAVE TO COMMUNICATE.
AND YOU HAVE TO
LET HIM SEE YOU
VULNERABLE AND SEE YOU AT YOUR
WORST AND UNDERSTAND WHY YOU
ARE.
BECAUSE OF THE THAT
YOU'VE GONE THROUGH.
LET HIM SEE YOU
FOR ALL THAT YOU
ARE.
YEAH.
HAVING MY AUNT
HERE TODAY REALLY
HELPED GUIDE ME THROUGH
EVERYTHING, 'CAUSE
I WAS FEELING
A LOT OF EMOTIONS.
I MEAN, I DON'T TAKE ANYTHING
LIGHTLY.
GOOD TO MEET YOU.
YEAH.
SHE LET ME
KNOW IT'S OKAY TO
BE WHO I AM WITH ERICH AND
THAT'S WHY HE IS
HERE IS BECAUSE
HE'S ALWAYS
ACCEPTED EVERY PART
OF ME.
OKAY, I'LL SEE YOU SOON.
GOOD.
SEE YOU REALLY SOON.
REALLY SOON.
DON'T DO ANYTHING FUN
WITHOUT ME.
I'LL TRY NOT TO.
BYE.
I'M JUST SO EXCITED
FOR GABBY.
BECAUSE SHE JUST
SO DESERVES TO
FIND LOVE.
YOU'RE GOING TO MAKE ME CRY
NOW.
I JUST LOVE HER.
I WANT THE BEST FOR HER.
TIRED OF DATING
MARRIED GUYS
WHO DRIVE AROUND IN A CREEPY
OLD VAN?
WE CAN DO BETTER.
APPLY TO BE ON NEXT SEASON
OF THE BACHELOR!
GO TO ABC.COM/CASTING NOW!
WELCOME BACK
TO THE EMOTIONAL
LIVE FINALE OF
"THE BACHELORETTE."
I'M HERE WITH GABBY AND RACHEL
AND SO FAR,
SOMETHING OF A MIXED
BAG IN THE MEET THE FAMILY
DEPARTMENT.
WOULD YOU BOTH AGREE?
DEFINITELY A MIXED BAG.
UPS AND DOWNS.
I WILL SAY IT'S
GOOD TO SEE BIG
TONY AND GRANDPA JOHN AGAIN.
WE ARE GOING TO SEE THEM NEXT
WEEK WITH A TWITE
FINALE AND I'M
SURE THEY'RE GOING
TO HAVE A LOT
OF OPINIONS.
THERE'S A LOT OF CHATTER ABOUT
GRANDPA JOHN FOR BACHELOR.
PEOPLE LOVE GRANDPA JOHN.
WATCH OUT, LADIES.
HE'S COMING IN HOT.
RACHEL, YOU'RE BACK UP BECAUSE
IT'S TIME FOR
TINO TO MEET YOUR
FAMILY.
LET'S SEE HOW TINO DOES.
TODAY TINO IS MEETING MY
FAMILY AND I'M TRYING TO BE
HAPPY.
BUT, LIKE, YESTERDAY
JUST WAS SO
SHOCKING.
I JUST AM REALLY
DISAPPOINTED IN
AVEN, AND I'M, LIKE, SO SAD
ABOUT IT RIGHT NOW.
LIKE, I'M HAPPY
ABOUT TINO, BUT
NOW I'M, LIKE,
OBVIOUSLY NERVOUS
THAT TINO ALSO ISN'T READY FOR
AN ENGAGEMENT.
HI.
HELLO!
YOU LOOK SO PRETTY.
THANK YOU.
YOU GUYS LOOK SO GREAT.
I REALLY JUST HOPE ME AND
TINO ARE ON THE
SAME PAGE STILL
AND THAT HE
IMPRESSES MY FRIENDS
AND FAMILY.
THEY SEE SOMETHING
I DON'T SEE,
THEN I DON'T KNOW
WHAT I'M GOING
TO DO.
HOW WAS YOUR NIGHT?
WELL, I'LL BE HONEST.
I FEEL LIKE TODAY
IS JUST ONE OF
THOSE DAYS WHERE
I'M JUST, LIKE,
NOT IN THE BEST MOOD.
I REALLY FELT LIKE ME AND AVEN
WERE ON THE SAME PAGE, SO IT'S
JUST NOT HOW I
WANTED IT TO GO.
I WANTED HIM TO
WALK IN AND FOR
YOU ALL TO BE, LIKE, "THIS IS
IT."
SO YOU CAN UNDERSTAND IT'S A
LITTLE FRUSTRATING.
NOW TODAY I'M
LIKE "OKAY, WHAT'S
GOING TO HAPPEN?
WHAT'S GOING TO GO WRONG?"
BUT I REALLY AM
EXCITED FOR YOU
GUYS TO MEET TINO.
HE GOT MY FIRST
IMPRESSION ROSE,
AND I FELL FOR TINO REALLY
EARLY.
BUT TINO'S FAMILY DOESN'T LIKE
ME, REALLY.
WHY?
DID THEY NOT UNDERSTAND YOU
OR, LIKE, YOU, OR WAS IT THE
PROCESS?
WHAT WAS THE HESITATION?
I DON'T KNOW.
I THINK THIS JUST WASN'T
SOMETHING THAT THEY EXPECTED.
IS IT YOUR INTERPRETATION
THAT THEY DON'T LIKE YOU?
OR WHAT HAPPENED?
WE CAN ASK HIM.
HE'S ALSO A GROWN ADULT AND
IF, LIKE, THIS
IS HIS DECISION,
I'M SURE THEY'RE
GOING TO, LIKE,
EVENTUALLY COME AROUND.
BUT I THINK I'M
GOING TO GO GET
HIM.
SO I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
I'M REALLY EXCITED.
RACHEL CAME AND NOT AS
EXCITED, NOT GUSHING LIKE SHE
WAS THE FIRST TIME, YOU KNOW,
YESTERDAY.
I THINK SHE'S WORRIED THAT
THERE'S GOING TO BE ANOTHER
ISSUE THAT WE'RE GOING TO FIND
AND SHE'S GOING TO BE
DISAPPOINTED AGAIN.
HI.
HI, BEAUTIFUL.
YOU LOOK GREAT.
HOW ARE YOU DOING?
SO MUCH BETTER.
NOW THAT I'M WITH YOU.
I MISS YOU TOO.
HOW ARE YOU DOING?
LET'S SIT.
YEAH.
DO YOU FEEL SWEATY TODAY?
NO, SURPRISINGLY.
SO LET'S NOT JINX IT.
ARE YOU NERVOUS?
I'M A LITTLE BIT NERVOUS,
YEAH.
YOU KNOW, I JUST
I WANT THEM
TO GET EXCITED
ABOUT US AS MUCH
AS I AM.
YEAH, ME TOO.
OKAY, COME ON.
HI.
HELLO.
THIS IS TINO.
HOW ARE YOU DOING?
NICE TO MEET YOU, SIR.
TODAY I'M MEETING RACHEL'S
FAMLY AND FRIENDS.
AND THERE'S A TON ON THE LINE.
I REALLY, REALLY WANT, PRETTY
MUCH NEED THEIR APPROVAL
BECAUSE, LIKE, THAT'S, LIKE,
SOMETHING THAT'S REALLY
IMPORTANT TO HER.
SO, DO YOU
WANT TO TELL THEM
ABOUT OUR STORY?
YEAH, SO I RODE IN ON A
FORKLIFT.
PROBABLY THIS IS THE MOST
NERVOUS I'VE BEEN SINCE.
BUT SO, YOU KNOW, WE, UH, WE
KIND OF LIKE
CAUGHT EACH OTHER'S
EYE REALLY EARLY.
WHAT'S THE MOST SPECIAL
MOMENT THAT YOU
TWO HAVE SHARED
SO FAR?
I THINK OUR
DINNER, OUR LAST
DINNER WHEN YOU
WERE ABLE TO BE
REALLY HONEST WITH ME AND YOU
TOLD ME...
OH, YEAH.
YOU WERE IN LOVE WITH ME.
YEAH.
I'M IN LOVE WITH
HER AND I CAN'T
WAIT TILL YOU GUYS ALL GET TO
KNOW ME A LITTLE BIT BETTER.
US TOO.
ME TOO.
WHEN HE FIRST
WALKED THROUGH
THE DOOR, HE LOOKED NERVOUS.
I COULD TELL HE
LOOKED NERVOUS.
TINO, I WOULD LOVE TO TALK TO
YOU.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S DO IT.
LET'S GO.
BUT AFTER THE CONVERSATION
WITH AVEN YESTERDAY, I THOUGHT
IT WAS VERY
IMPORTANT FOR ME TO
ASK WHERE HE STANDS.
LET'S JUST HOPE THERE'S NO
SURPRISES.
DO YOU THINK YOU GUYS HAVE
ENOUGH IN COMMON?
YEAH.
I MEAN, DO
YOU HAVE A LOT TO
DO TOGETHER?
YEAH, I MEAN, LIKE, I DON'T
EXPECT HER TO GO SURF WITH ME.
BUT YEAH, THE
FUN THING WILL BE
WE'LL PICK UP THINGS TOGETHER.
DID YOU EVER BRING A GIRL
HOME BEFORE?
YEAH, I MEAN, A COUPLE MET
THEM BUT IT WAS, LIKE...
BECAUSE I KNOW THAT MEANS A
LOT TO HER TO HAVE FAMILY,
ESPECIALLY WHO LIKES HER.
DO YOU THINK YOUR FAMILY WOULD
BE COMING MORE UNDERSTANDING
ABOUT IT?
ABSOLUTELY.
I AM A MILLION
PERCENT CONFIDENT
THEY'LL LOVE RACHEL,
'CAUSE I DO.
SO THEY DON'T HAVE A CHOICE.
NO.
I KNOW.
AND THAT'S ALL
THAT MATTERS, BUT
I DO KNOW FAMILY DOES MAKE A
DIFFERENCE.
IT CAN CAUSE PROBLEMS IN THE
FUTURE, TOO, IF FAMILY DOESN'T
LIKE SOMEBODY.
SO IF YOU'RE CONFIDENT.
RACHEL WANTS THE
OTHER FAMILY TO
LIKE HER TOO.
YOU KNOW, IF
FAMILIES LIKE EACH
OTHER, IT'S GOING TO MAKE THE
MARRIAGE BETTER.
AND HE KNOWS HIS DAD.
IF HE THINKS HIS
DAD'S GOING TO
ACCEPT HER, THEN
I FEEL BETTER.
HE'S SUCCESSFUL, LOVES WHAT
HE DOES.
DOES HE BUILD TOWNHOMES OR
DOES HE BUILD SKYSCRAPERS?
YEAH, THAT'S WHAT HE DOES.
LARGE BUILDINGS
GO FOR YEARS
AND YOU CAN'T WORK REMOTE WHEN
YOU'RE BUILDING A BUILDING.
RIGHT, I'M JUST THINKING ABOUT
YOU.
AND YOUR DREAMS.
SO IF YOU WANT TO WORK IN
EUROPE.
YEAH, I MEAN, DEFINITELY.
BUT IT'S NOT LIKE I NEED TO DO
THAT RIGHT NOW IF IT DOESN'T
WORK OUT, HE WANTS TO TRAVEL.
HE LIVES A VERY INTERESTING
LIFE, FROM WHAT YOU TOLD US.
AND THAT'S GOT TO BE EXCITING.
AND I KNOW THAT'S THE WAY YOU
LIVE LIFE.
YEAH, HE HAS
ALL THESE CRAZY
HOBBIES AND HE WANTS TO DO ALL
THESE THINGS, AND IT MAKES ME,
LIKE, WELL, I
WANT TO BE A PART
OF THAT AND I WANT TO DO THAT
CHARITY WORK WITH YOU AND I
WOULD LOVE TO
LEARN HOW TO SURF
AND LIVE IN THAT
BEACH TOWN WITH
YOU.
YOU'VE GOT TO HAVE FUN IN
LIFE.
LIFE GOES REALLY QUICK.
YEAH.
I'M EXCITED FOR YOU
TO TALK TO HIM.
I'M EXCITED
TO SPEAK WITH HIM
ALSO.
WHEN SHE DESCRIBED TINO,
SHE DESCRIBED HIM WITH SUCH
ENTHUSIASM.
AND I'M EXCITED TO SEE MY
DAUGHTER THAT HAPPY,
BUT I'M A FATHER.
I'M NOT LOOKING FOR WHAT'S
HAPPENING TOMORROW.
I'M MORE CONCERNED TO SEE WHAT
THEIR FUTURE IS GOING TO BE.
HOW ARE YOU DOING TODAY?
I'M DOING PRETTY GOOD.
YOU KNOW, LET'S
GET RIGHT AT IT.
TELL ME A LITTLE BIT ABOUT THE
HOMETOWN.
WHAT HAPPENED
THERE THAT CHANGED
HER MIND OR...
MADE HER FEEL UNCOMFORTABLE?
YEAH, I HOPE SHE DIDN'T
CHANGE HER MIND.
SO HOMETOWN WAS A LITTLE
SURPRISING TO ME TOO.
TO BE HONEST WITH YOU, ALL I
TALK ABOUT WITH MY DAD IS
SPORTS.
SO IT WAS REALLY SHOCKING.
BUT I AM 100%
SURE THAT IF THEY
GET A DAY WITH HER WHERE WE GO
TO THE BEACH, THEY'LL, LIKE,
FALL IN LOVE WITH
HER JUST LIKE
I DID.
SHE'LL HAVE A JOB THAT SHE
COULD LIVE IN
CALIFORNIA AND BE
WORKING OUT OF ATLANTA.
BUT YOU AREN'T AS MOBILE
AS SHE IS.
IS THAT GOING TO BE A PROBLEM?
IF SHE WANTED
TO GO, I DON'T
KNOW, LIKE TO A
FOREIGN COUNTRY,
I WOULD JUST SAY
OKAY, "WE NEED
AT LEAST A COUPLE
YEARS SO I CAN
BE ON THE BUILDING."
GOOD.
BECAUSE, YOU KNOW, SHE IS THAT
ADVENTUROUS TYPE, AND SHE
EXPLAINED ABOUT YOU BEING THE
SAME TYPE OF PERSON.
IN THE MOST
GENUINE WAY I CAN
PUT IT, I MEAN, YOUR DAUGHTER
DOES MEAN THE WORLD TO ME.
LIFE IS HARD, BUT I WANT TO BE
THAT PERSON WHO
IS SHARING THAT
BURDEN WITH HER AND THERE TO
EXPERIENCE THE
AMAZINGNESS THAT
WE BRING TO EACH OTHER.
I'M GOING TO MAKE
YOUR DAUGHTER
HAPPY FOREVER.
WELL, I DO LIKE YOU.
I DO LIKE YOU.
I AM A LITTLE BIT IN AWE OF
HOW WELL MEETING
RACHEL'S FAMILY
JUST WENT.
SERIOUSLY, THANK YOU GUYS
SO MUCH.
I'M KIND OF REALLY
FEELING LIKE
WHAT I'VE WANTED FOR WEEKS NOW
IS REALLY GOING TO HAPPEN.
NICE MEETING YOU.
ABSOLUTELY.
SO NICE MEETING YOU.
BYE, GUYS.
TODAY WENT BETTER THAN I
THOUGHT IT COULD'VE WENT.
BIG STAMP OF APPROVAL FROM
EVERYONE.
NOW WE JUST HAVE TO WORK
ON YOUR FAMILY.
THEY WILL LIKE YOU.
YOU'VE ALREADY
GOT THE APPROVAL
THE IMPORTANT ONE.
AND THE REST WILL FOLLOW SOON.
AND I REALLY
DO FEEL LIKE HE
DOES WANT A LIFE WITH ME BUT I
DON'T KNOW HOW TO, LIKE, THINK
ABOUT WHAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN
NEXT.
BYE.
BECAUSE I STILL HAVE TO HAVE A
DISCUSSION WITH AVEN.
HE'S SOMEONE I
REALLY CARE ABOUT
TOO AND I KNOW
HE PROBABLY ISN'T
FEELING GOOD RIGHT NOW.
I THINK HE'S PROBABLY, LIKE,
WAITING UNTIL HE GETS A CHANCE
TO EXPLAI THINGS TO ME AGAIN
AND THIS REALLY HARD
CONVERSATION HAS TO HAPPEN.
SO YEAH, I JUST
HAVE TO TAKE IT
ONE STEP AT A TIME RIGHT NOW.
WE ARE BACK.
WE ARE LIVE.
AND YOU ARE
WATCHING THE HIGHLY
CHARGED "BACHELORETTE" FINALE.
TWITTER RIGHT NOW IS ON FIRE.
SOME FOLKS ARE TEAM RACHEL.
SO MARTIN AVEN.
SUMMER TEAM GABBY AND EVERYONE
IS TEAM GRANDPA JOHN.
I AM NOT SURE IF GRANDPA JOHN
GETS DMs.
BUT IF HE DOES, LOOK OUT.
I WANT TO CIRCLE
BACK WITH YOU.
I WANT TO GO BACK
TO THAT REALLY
INTENSE CONVERSATION YOU HAD
WITH AVEN WHEN HE TOLD HIM HE
WASN'T SURE IF HE COULD SEE
HIMSELF GETTING ENGAGED YOU AT
THE END OF ALL THIS AND
UNDERSTANDABLY
WAS VERY SHOCKING
TO YOU.
WHAT ABOUT THAT
MOMENT MADE YOU
SO UPSET?
WALKING IN, ALL I REALLY
WANTED FOR US TO
BE ON THE SAME
PAGE AND TO REALIZE WE WEREN'T
WAS REALLY THE
HARDEST THING FOR
ME.
GOING INTO
THAT FINAL NIGHT,
WHAT WERE YOU HOPING FOR?
WHAT DOOMED TO HEAR FROM HIM?
I DON'T KNOW
IF I NECESSARILY
NEEDED TO HEAR ANYTHING.
I JUST NEEDED TO
THE SEE ACTIONS
WITH WHAT HE TOLD ME BEFORE.
IT SEEMS LIKE AT THIS POINT
THE RELATIONSHIP IS ON ROCKY
GROUND.
MAYBE REACHING THE BREAKING
POINT.
AVEN HAS ONE LAST SHOT.
IS HE GOING TO BE ABLE TO TURN
THINGS AROUND WITH RACHEL?
LET'S FIND OUT.
TONIGHT IS MY LAST DATE
WITH AVEN.
AND I AM EXTREMELY NERVOUS
TO SEE HIM AGAIN.
BECAUSE I WAS SO CONFIDENT
IN AVEN, AND WE HAD A FULL
OVERNIGHT DATE TOGETHER WHERE
AVEN TOLD ME HE IS 100% READY
FOR AN ENGAGEMENT.
BUT WHEN HE TALKED
TO MY FAMILY,
HE TOLD THEM SOMETHING
DIFFERENT.
AND THERE WAS A POINT WHERE I
WAS, LIKE, I SEE MY LIFE WITH
AVEN.
LIKE, AVEN IS IT.
SO I NEED TO TALK TO HIM ABOUT
WHETHER OR NOT
WE ARE COMPLETELY
ON THE SAME PAGE.
HI, BEAUTIFUL.
HI.
HOW ARE YOU?
I'M GOOD.
IT'S GOOD TO SEE YOU.
THANK YOU FOR COMING.
IT'S SO GOOD TO SEE YOU.
IT'S GOOD TO SEE YOU.
HOW HAVE YOU BEEN?
DOING OKAY.
I REALLY MISSED YOU.
I'M SO HAPPY TO SEE YOU.
I'VE BEEN LOOKING FORWARD TO
TODAY, AND OBVIOUSLY THERE'S
SOME STUFF THAT I WANT TO TALK
TO YOU ABOUT.
BUT, LIKE, BEFORE KIND OF
GETTING INTO IT, DO YOU WANT A
GLASS OF CHAMPAGNE?
LET'S JUST...
DO YOU WANT TO JUST TALK?
I JUST FEEL LIKE WE NEED...
YOU WANT TO...
YEAH.
ABSOLUTELY.
WELL, I NEED YOU TO KNOW THAT
THESE LAST COUPLE DAYS FOR ME
HAVE BEEN REALLY HARD.
JUST FROM THE PURE FACT OF,
LIKE, HOW I SAW YOU THE OTHER
DAY WHEN WE HAD
A CONVERSATION.
I AM SO, LIKE, DEEPLY SORRY
ABOUT MAKING YOU
FEEL LIKE THAT.
IT REALLY KILLED ME TO SEE YOU
LIKE THAT.
I NEVER WANT TO BE THE REASON
WHY YOU CRY OR ARE UPSET OVER
ANYTHING.
IT REALLY CRUSHED ME.
AND I KNOW A LOT OF IT IS
BECAUSE YOU MIGHT
HAVE FELT THAT
THAT CAME OUT OF NOWHERE, AND
I'M TRULY SORRY ABOUT THAT.
AND THE NEXT STEP
IN ALL OF THIS
IS SO IMPORTANT TO ME
BECAUSE I CARE ABOUT YOU.
BUT YOU KNOW, REALIZING THAT I
WANT MORE TIME WITH YOU AND I
WANT TO COME VISIT YOU IN
FLORIDA AND SEE
WHERE YOU LIVE.
I WANT YOU TO COME VISIT ME.
I WANT TO DO LIFE OUTSIDE OF
THIS WITH YOU, AND I JUST FEEL
LIKE THAT'S SO
IMPORTANT FOR US
AT THIS POINT BEFORE THAT NEXT
STEP, AND I WANT
US TO BE FULLY,
FULLY IN LOVE WITH EACH OTHER.
SO THAT'S THAT
POINT WHEN WE GET
HERE IS SO SPECIAL
FOR US AND WE
CAN GO RIGHT INTO
A MARRIAGE AND
START OUR FAMILY TOGETHER WITH
OUR KIDS, OUR TWO OR FOUR,
HOWEVER MANY YOU WANT.
DOES THAT MAKE SENSE SO FAR?
YEAH.
I THINK...
I'M SORRY.
I'M JUST, LIKE, STRUGGLING.
LIKE, I HATE THE WAY WE LEFT
THINGS REALLY.
AND I NEED YOU
TO KNOW I HAVEN'T
STOPPED, LIKE, THINKING ABOUT,
LIKE, HOW THINGS WERE LEFT.
AND, LIKE, I NEED YOU TO KNOW,
LIKE, HOW HARD
IT IS FOR ME TO,
LIKE, WALK IN TO MY FAMILY AND
BE, LIKE...
WHEN AVEN SAYS
SOMETHING TO ME,
HE MEANS IT AND
HE WOULD NEVER,
LIKE, LIE TO ME.
AND I THINK THE ONE THING I
WANTED OUT OF
THIS WAS WHEN YOU
SAT DOWN WITH MY
FAMILY THAT WE
WERE ON THE SAME PAGE.
AND I FEEL SO
BLINDSIDED BY YOU,
LIKE, I CAN'T EVEN TELL YOU.
WHEN I SAT DOWN WITH SAM AND
NATE AND THEY LOOKED AT ME AND
SAID "YOU DON'T
KNOW WHERE HE'S
AT RIGHT NOW," DO YOU KNOW HOW
THAT FELT TO ME?
BECAUSE I THOUGHT
WHEN WE TALKED
THAT NIGHT THAT WE WERE ON THE
SAME PAGE.
I REALLY, LIKE, I THINK A
PART OF YOU IS THINKING THAT I
DON'T WANT THIS ANYMORE, AND
THAT IS 1000% NOT THE CASE.
I WANT TO LEAVE HERE WITH YOU.
I WANT THAT MORE
THAN ANYTHING.
AND I'M SITTING HERE TRYING TO
FIGHT FOR IT.
AND I KNOW THAT I MIGHT HAVE
BEEN...
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
IT IS, CAUGHT
UP A LITTLE BIT IN SOME OF IT.
CAUGHT UP?
NOT IN A BAD WAY, RACHEL.
NOT IN A BAD WAY.
I DON'T WANT THAT TO COME OFF
IN A BAD WAY.
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN,
"CAUGHT UP"?
IN SAYING THAT I THOUGHT I
MIGHT'VE BEEN
READY FOR THIS IN
TWO WEEKS.
BUT I'M TELLING YOU THAT MY
FEELINGS TOWARDS YOU HAVE NOT
CHANGED AT ALL,
AND A LIFE AFTER
THIS IS SOMETHING THAT I WANT
WITH YOU.
IT REALLY HURTS TO HEAR YOU
TELL ME ONE THING AND THEN SAY
YOU GOT CAUGHT
UP IN IT WITH ME.
I DIDN'T MEAN FOR IT...
BUT I THINK
YOU NEED TO KNOW
THAT, LIKE, LIKE, I WANT TO BE
ENGAGED.
I WANT SOMEONE
WHO'S SURE ABOUT
ME AND, LIKE, I'M
NOT WILLING TO
SACRIFICE THAT
AT THE END OF THE
DAY.
AND I'M HAVING
SUCH A HARD TIME
BECAUSE, LIKE,
I FEEL LIKE FROM
THE BEGINNING, I'VE SEEN THIS,
LIKE, WITH...
LIKE I CAN SEE THIS LIFE WITH
YOU OUTSIDE OF THIS AND I FEEL
LIKE IF THIS WAS ANY OTHER
SITUATION THAT IT WOULD BE ME
AND YOU OUTSIDE OF THIS.
BUT I'M JUST NOT WILLING TO
SACRIFICE THAT.
LIKE, I NEED
SOMEONE WHO IS SURE
ABOUT ME AND YOU'RE NOT SURE
ABOUT ME.
I AM SURE ABOUT YOU.
BUT I FEEL LIKE YOU CAN'T
GIVE ME WHAT I NEED RIGHT NOW.
I WANT TO GIVE THAT TO YOU.
AVEN, YOU CAN'T, THOUGH.
LIKE, I ULTIMATELY FEEL LIKE I
JUST CAN'T, LIKE,
I CAN'T, LIKE,
MOVE FORWARD.
IT'S OVER.
OH.
I'M SO...
RACHEL.
I'M SITTING HERE TELLING YOU
THAT I...
LIKE, I'M
NEVER GOING TO GET
OVER THIS.
THIS...
I DID NOT INTEND FOR THIS
TO HAPPEN AT ALL.
I'M SO SORRY.
I JUST FEEL LIKE MY HEART IS,
LIKE, BREAKING RIGHT NOW.
LIKE...
I'M SORRY.
I JUST WANT
YOU TO BE HAPPY.
I WANT YOU TO BE HAPPY
IN ALL OF THIS.
CAN I GIVE YOU A HUG?
YEAH.
I'M SO SORRY, RACHEL.
DO YOU WANT TO WALK ME OUT?
I FAILED.
BYE.
I'M SO SORRY.
I'M SORRY.
I HAVE NO IDEA WHERE I'M
GOING FROM HERE
BECAUSE I DIDN'T
THINK I WAS GOING
TO BE LEAVING
HERE WITHOUT RACHEL.
I SAW A LIFE WITH HER.
AND I WILL ALWAYS
THINK THAT IF
I DID SOMETHING DIFFERENT,
THINGS WOULD HAVE
BEEN DIFFERENT
WITH US.
FOREVER.
I'M UPSET THAT I WASN'T THERE.
I KNOW THAT WE
WOULD HAVE GOTTEN
THERE.
IT'S JUST
REALLY SAD BECAUSE
IT'S JUST, LIKE, HARD TO KNOW
IT'S OVER.
I DID SEE IT BEING HIM AND I
AT THE END.
I'M HAVING TOO MANY OF THESE
MOMENTS.
LIKE, HOW MUCH LONGER CAN I GO
ON THIS ROLLER COASTER?
RACHEL, I'M SORRY.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT TO SAY.
THAT WAS OBVIOUSLY COMPLETELY,
COMPLETELY UNEXPECTED.
I WAS WATCHING YOU WATCH THAT
BACK AND IT SEEMS LIKE YOU'RE
STILL TRYING TO PROCESS
EVERYTHING THAT HAPPENED.
YEAH.
I THINK THERE'S
REALLY NO WORDS
TO DESCRIBE IT.
IT'S OBVIOUSLY HURTS TO WATCH
BACK.
IT STILL FEELS
THAT WAY WATCHING
IT BACK AGAIN.
I KNOW THIS WHOLE THING IS
BEEN SUITABLY
EMOTIONAL FOR YOU
OBVIOUSLY.
THAT MIGHT'VE BEEN THE MOST
EMOTION THAT WE
SAW FROM YOU ON
THIS JOURNEY.
WHEREDO YOU THINK THAT WAS ALL
COMING FROM?
I MEAN,
EVERYTHING I SAID IS
EXACTLY, LIKE, WHAT I WAS
FEELING.
I REALLY DID SEE HIM AND I AT
THE END OF IT SO IT WAS REALLY
HARD TO SAY GOODBYE.
I CAN SEE THE
EMOTION ON YOUR
FACE.
SEEMS LIKE YOU'RE
FIGHTING BACK
TEARS.
IS THAT TRUE?
IS THAT HOW YOU FEEL?
I'M ALWAYS FIGHTING BACK
TEARS, JESSE.
YEAH, THAT'S TRUE.
GABBY, YOU'VE
BEEN SUPPORTING
EACH OTHER ON THIS ENTIRE
JOURNEY.
I KNOW HOW YOU BEEN SUPPORTING
EACH OTHER.
HOW EMOTIONAL WAS IT FOR USING
RACHEL GO THROUGH ALL THIS?
IT'S DEVASTATING
JUST KNOWING
HOW MUCH YOU WENT THROUGH.
AND BEING A GOOD FRIEND, MY
HEART HURTS WHEN HERS DOES.
NONE OF THIS IS REALLY EASY.
AVEN IS HERE.
HE'S BACKSTAGE.
DO YOU FEEL LIKE
YOU'RE READY TO
TALK TO HIM AND
HEAR WHAT HE HAS
TO SAY?
YEAH.
WE'LL DO THAT.
WHEN WE COME BACK, RACHEL AND
AVEN WILL GO FACE
-TO-FACE IS THE
FIRST TIME THEY BROKE UP IN
MEXICO.
WELCOME BACK TO THE LIVE
FINALE OF THE BACHELORETTE.
THIS ENTIRE JOURNEY HAS BEEN A
MASSIVE ROLLER COASTER.
OBVIOUSLY TONIGHT IS NO
DIFFERENT.
WE ARE AT THAT POINT NOW.
EVERYONE HAS JUST WATCHED YOU
END THINGS WITH AVEN.
ARE YOU READY TO SEE HIM?
I AM CHECKING BECAUSE YOU SEEM
NERVOUS.
ARE YOU SURE?
YEAH.
ALL RIGHT, LADIES AND
GENTLEMEN, PLEASE
WELCOME AVEN.
HOW ARE YOU?
YOU LOOK BEAUTIFUL.
IT'S SO GOOD TO SEE YOU.
RACHEL AND AVEN, IT'S GREAT
SEEING YOU BOTH BACK HERE
TOGETHER.
I WILL START WITH YOU, RACHEL.
WHAT'S IT LIKE SEEING AVEN FOR
THE FIRST TIME
SINCE THAT DAY IN
MEXICO?
IT'S REALLY BITTERSWEET
OBVIOUSLY BUT IT'S REALLY GOOD
TO SEE YOU.
IT'S GOOD TO SEE YOU TOO
PITTSBURGH I'M
SURE YOU'VE GOT A
LOT ON YOUR MIND.
WHAT WOULD YOU LIKE TO SAY TO
RACHEL?
YEAH.
I'LL MISS SAM'S
SO NERVOUS RIGHT
NOW.
I'VE BEEN VERY ANXIOUS TO SEE
YOU.
I THINK ONE THING
THAT I WANT TO
SAY IS I'M
EXTREMELY, EXTREMELY
SORRY THE WAY THINGS ENDED
BETWEEN US.
I KNOW THAT I HURT YOU.
THE WAY THAT THINGS KIND OF
TRANSPIRED, I BLINDSIDED YOU
WITH EVERYTHING THAT WASN'T
FAIR.
I CARED ABOUT YOU
TOO MUCH TO DO
THAT TO YOU.
SO I KNOW I
DEFINITELY FEEL LIKE
I LET YOU DOWN IN THAT MOMENT.
I'M TRULY SORRY.
THAT'S THE FIRST
THING I WANTED
TO SAY.
RACHEL, WAS THERE ANYTHING
AVEN COULD HAVE
SAID OR DONE TO
SALVAGE THE RELATIONSHIP THAT
NIGHT WHEN YOU SAW HIM?
IT'S HARD BECAUSE IT'S NOT
LIKE ANYTHING WENT WRONG.
WE NEVER HAD A PROBLEM.
AT THE END OF
THE DAY, YOU JUST
KNEW WHAT WAS RIGHT FOR YOU.
AND THAT'S OKAY.
I DON'T KNOW IF
THERE'S ANYTHING
WE COULD HAVE DONE TO SALVAGE
IT.
WE WERE BEING TRUE TO HOW WE
FELT IN THE MOMENT
AND I RESPECT
THAT.
YOU ARE ABLE TO BE HONEST WITH
ME.
ABSOLUTELY.
I THINK A BIG
PART OF IT TOO IS
I JUST DIDN'T FULLY UNDERSTAND
WHAT YOU NEEDED AND WHAT YOU
WANTED.
THAT WAS ON ME.
THAT WAS MY FAULT.
AGAIN, I'M SORRY ABOUT THAT.
AS FAR AS SALVAGING
IT, I DON'T
KNOW IF WE COULD HAVE OR NOT.
WE TRIED.
BUT I AGREE.
AVEN, YOU SEEMED BLINDSIDED
WHEN SHE ENDED THINGS WITH YOU
THAT NIGHT.
GOING INTO THAT
NIGHT, WHAT WERE
YOU HOPING?
YEAH, OBVIOUSLY LEAVING YOU
THAT DAY ON THE BRIDGE WAS TO
TOUGH.
I WASN'T FEELING GOOD ABOUT
WHERE WE ARE AT OBVIOUSLY.
I THINK THAT NIGHT
I REALLY JUST
WANTED TO REITERATE
TO YOU THAT
I WASN'T GIVING UP ON US.
I WANTED TO CONTINUE WITH YOU.
I WANTED TO CONTINUE OUR
RELATIONSHIP AND MOVE PAST AND
MOVE FORWARD.
BUT OBVIOUSLY
KIND OF REALIZING
AGAIN THAT THERE WAS SOMETHING
THAT YOU WANTED BETWEEN US.
I'M SORRY THAT I WASN'T THERE.
I'M SORRY THAT
WE WEREN'T THERE.
I FELT LIKE WE
WEREN'T THERE IN
THAT MOMENT.
I WAS JUST HOPING THAT WE CAN
CONTINUE THINGS.
OBVIOUSLY WE DIDN'T REALLY SEE
EYE TO EYE ON THAT.
RACHEL, HOW
DO YOU FEEL ABOUT
THAT?
I THINK IT'S ALL COMPLETELY
UNDERSTANDABLE.
AT THE END OF
THE DAY, YOU WERE
BEING HONEST WITH YOURSELF AND
IT WAS OBVIOUSLY
REALLY HARD TO
HEAR BECAUSE I THOUGHT WE WERE
ON THE SAME PAGE.
BUT I APPRECIATE YOUR HONESTY
AND YOU DON'T
HAVE TO APOLOGIZE.
HELP US CLEAR
THAT UP, AVEN.
OBVIOUSLY IN THE FANTASY SUITE
YOU TOLD RACHEL THAT YOU ARE
READY FOR AN
ENGAGEMENT BUT THEN
YOU MET HER FAMILY AND HER
FRIENDS AND ALL
OF A SUDDEN, YOU
WEREN'T.
WHAT CHANGED?
WHAT HAPPENED?
YEAH.
I THINK KIND OF LEADING UP TO
MEETING YOUR FAMILY, I KIND OF
JUST HAD SOME TIME AND TOOK A
LOOK AT WHERE WE
WERE AT, WHERE
I WAS AT.
I WAS REALLY ANTICIPATING
MEETING THEM
BECAUSE I WANTED TO
GO UP THERE AND BE AS HONEST
WITH HOW I WAS FEELING IN THAT
MOMENT TOWARDS THE PEOPLE THAT
MEAN THE MOST TO YOU.
I JUST UNFORTUNATELY
DIDN'T GET
THE OPPORTUNITY TO TELL YOU
FIRST.
WHICH OBVIOUSLY
WAS THE DOWNFALL
TO THE WHOLE THING.
YOU KNOW, OBVIOUSLY THAT WEEK
LEADING UP, I STILL DIDN'T
REALLY KNOW WHERE YOU ARE AT
WITH TINO ON THE OTHER SIDE OF
THINGS SO THAT WEIGHT ON THE A
LITTLE BIT.
ULTIMATELY I THOUGHT THAT WE
COULD HAVE GOTTEN THERE.
IF WE WOULD'VE CONTINUED ON.
BUT I JUST DIDN'T GET THE
OPPORTUNITY TO
KIND OF SPEAK TO
YOU BEFORE AND
I DIDN'T WANT TO
NOT TO BE HONEST WITH YOUR
FAMILY.
I'M SORRY THE WAY THINGS
TRANSPIRED.
WHEN YOU MET HER FAMILY AND
YOU SPOKE TO HER
FRIENDS, DO YOU
FEEL LIKE HER
FRIENDS SABOTAGED
YOUR RELATIONSHIP WITH RACHEL?
ABSOLUTELY NOT.
THEY DIDN'T SABOTAGE THE
RELATIONSHIP AT ALL.
THE QUESTIONS THEY WERE ASKING
ME WERE WAY FORWARD, UP FRONT,
THEY A PURPOSE.
IN THAT MOMENT I WANTED TO BE
HONEST ABOUT WHERE I FELT WE
WERE AT AND I WAS AT.
YEAH, GOING BACK TO YOU AND
LETTING YOU KNOW
WHAT I SAID AND
EVERYTHING LIKE THAT.
YEAH, I WAS JUST TRYING TO BE
HONEST WITH THEM
WHEN THEY WERE
ASKING THOSE TOUGH QUESTIONS.
YOUR FRIENDS LOVE YOU SO
MUCH.
WHEN YOU SAW THAT
BACK, WHAT DID
YOU THINK?
I ASKED THOSE QUESTIONS TO
EVERYONE.
I FEEL LIKE
EVERYONE IS A TOUGH
BUNCH.
THEY REALLY WANTED
TO MAKE SURE
THAT HE WAS READY ND THAT'S
WHAT THEY WERE DOING.
I DON'T THINK THEY WERE EVER
TRYING TO SABOTAGE ANYTHING.
ABSOLUTELY NOT.
AVEN, OBVIOUSLY YOU AND
RACHEL HAVE BEEN
THROUGH SO MUCH
TOGETHER.
UPS AND DOWNS, WHEN YOU LOOK
BACK AT THIS WHOLE THING, ANY
REGRETS?
I MEAN, YEAH.
I COULD HAVE GONE ABOUT
COMMUNICATING TO
YOU ABOUT WHERE
I WAS AT A LOT BETTER.
BEING ABLE TO HAVE THE
OPPORTUNITY TO SPEAK TO YOU
BEFORE THAT DAY OBVIOUSLY IS A
BIG REGRET OF MINE.
AGAIN, JUST NOT TAKING ENOUGH
TIME TO REALIZE
WHAT YOU WANTED
OUT OF ALL OF THIS.
AND WHAT WAS IMPORTANT TO YOU.
IT'S SOMETHING
I REGRET BECAUSE
I COULD HAVE DONE A WAY BETTER
JOB AT THAT.
I REGRET THAT DEEPLY.
RACHEL, I KNOW FOR YOU WITH
RESPECT TO AVEN, NONE OF THIS
HAPPENED BECAUSE OF A LACK OF
FEELINGS.
HOW HARD IS IT
FOR YOU NOW THESE
LAST COUPLE MONTHS, TRYING TO
AVOID THE THOUGHTS
OF "WHAT IF"
WITH AVEN?
I THINK YOU CAN ALWAYS GO
BACK ON "WHAT IF."
AT THE TIME, HE WAS DOING WHAT
WAS BEST FOR HIM.
MY FEELINGS WERE ALWAYS THERE.
IT JUST WAS KIND
OF, WE WEREN'T
ON THE SAME PAGE AT THE END OF
THE DAY AND THERE'S NOTHING
BESIDES THAT.
YOU ARE PERFECT.
IT WAS HARD.
CANT REALLY LOOK BACK.
WHAT ABOUT YOU, AVEN?
AT THE TIME YOU
WERE SAYING YOU
WERE FALLING IN LOVE WITH
RACHEL.
DO YOU EVER THINK
ABOUT HER AND
WONDER WHAT COULD
HAVE HAPPENED,
CONSIDERING THAT
THE TIMING JUST
WASN'T RIGHT?
YEAH, ABSOLUTELY.
LIKE I SAID THAT NIGHT, I WAS
TRYING TO FIGHT FOR OUR
RELATIONSHIP
WHERE IT WAS AT AT
THAT POINT.
I WANTED TO CONTINUE.
I WASN'T GIVING UP ON YOU.
UNFORTUNATELY WITH THE EVENTS
THAT HAPPENED AND
THE WAY THAT I
WENT ABOUT THINGS, YOU JUST
DIDN'T AGREE.
I THINK THAT'S
ALL ABOUT TIMING
AND ALIGNING THINGS.
YEAH.
I WANTED TO CONTINUE WITH
EVERYTHING.
BUT I AGREE THAT MAYBE THE
TIMING WAS OFF ABOUT WHERE WE
WERE AT NOT BEING ON THE SAME
PAGE.
BEFORE WE MOVE
ON, RACHEL, I
WILL GIVE YOU THE FINAL WORD.
WHAT WOULD YOU LIKE TO SAY TO
AVEN?
I'M REALLY
HAPPY TO SEE YOU.
I REALLY JUST WISH YOU NOTHING
BUT THE BEST.
I REALLY JUST UNHAPPY THAT WE
WERE ABLE TO HAVE
THE CHANCE TO
SIT DOWN AND TALK.
I FEEL LIKE IT WAS REALLY
HELPFUL.
IT IS REALLY
GOOD TO SEE YOU.
AVEN, THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR
BEING HERE.
I KNOW THESE THINGS ARE ALWAYS
VERY UNCOMFORTABLE.
THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR BEING
HONEST.
WISH YOU ALL THE BEST MOVING
FORWARD.
APPRECIATE IT.
WHEN WE RETURN, GABBY WILL BE
BACK WITH US LIVE ON STAGE.
ERICH.
RACHEL HAS ONE GUY LEFT.
THAT'S TINO.
WILL THESE TWO MEN GIVE THESE
INCREDIBLE WOMEN THE LOVE THEY
SO DESERVE?
YOU ARE NOT GOING TO WANT TO
MISS WHAT HAPPENS
NEXT WHEN THE
LIVE FINALE OF
"THE BACHELORETTE" RETURNS.
WELCOME BACK TO THE LIVE
FINALE OF "THE BACHELORETTE."
I AM HERE WITH
GABBY AND RACHEL,
TWO AMAZING WOMEN
WHO HAVE BEEN
IN THIS THING
TOGETHER FROM THE
VERY BEGINNING.
IT'S BEEN QUITE A SURPRISING
NIGHT SO FAR,
SO MANY TWISTS AND TURNS.
AND WE'RE NOT DONE YET.
NOT EVEN CLOSE.
WE ARE OVER OUR ALLOTTED TIME
BUT WHAT WE ARE
DISCUSSING IS SO
IMPORTANT.
WE'VE GOTTEN
SPECIAL PERMISSION
FROM ABC TO
CONTINUE THIS SO WE
ARE GOING TO REJOIN THE
10:00 P. M. SHOWING PROGRESS AS
SOON AS WE CAN.
RACHEL, I WANT
TO ASK, WHAT HAS
IT BEEN LIKE
REHASHING A LOT OF
STUFF IN FRONT OF A LIVE
AUDIENCE?
VERY EMOTIONAL.
GETTING SOME GOOD CLOSURE.
HOPEFULLY CAN
COME OUT POSITIVE.
GABBY, HOW ABOUT YOU?
YES, THE SAME.
IT'S ALWAYS HARD.
HARD FOR BOTH OF US.
I'M SO GRATEFUL TO HAVE
RACHAEL'S SUPPORT
AND TO BE HERE
FOR YOU.
A LOT OF NERVOUS ENERGY.
IT'S NOT JUST YOU.
HAVING YOU BOTH HERE TONIGHT.
HAVING YOU BOTH
HERE, THANK YOU
BOTH SO MUCH.
MS. GABBY.
IT'S TIME FOR YOUR FINAL DATE
WITH ERICH.
TAKE A LOOK.
I'M SO EXCITED TO SEE ERICH
TONIGHT.
I'VE BEEN THINKING
ABOUT HIM ALL
DAY.
I JUST WANT TO
BE WRAPPED UP IN
HIS ARMS AGAIN.
I CAME HERE TO FIND MY PERSON,
AND ERIC REALLY HAS SHOWN ME
THAT HE'S IT FOR ME.
HI.
I LOVE HIM
'CAUSE HE MAKES ME
FEEL SAFE.
HE MAKES ME FEEL SEEN.
AND HE JUST HAS
EVERYTHING THAT
I'VE EVER LOOKED
FOR IN SOMEONE.
SO I REALLY, REALLY, REALLY
REALLY, REALLY HOPE THAT HE'S,
AT THE END OF
THIS, PROPOSING TO
ME AND FEELS THE SAME.
YOU KNOW, IF HE
WAS, LIKE, "I'M
NOT READY," I THINK THAT WOULD
MAKE ME THINK,
LIKE, "IS IT ME?"
LIKE, "IS THERE SOMETHING THAT
WENT WRONG?
ARE WE NOT READY FOR EACH
OTHER?"
IT'S, LIKE, CRAZY THAT THIS IS
OUR LAST DAY.
AND I DO FEEL, LIKE, MORE THAN
GOOD ABOUT LEAVING HERE WITH
YOU.
AND THAT'S SCARY
FOR ME TO SAY.
I'M SURE IT'S
THE SAME TO HEAR.
BUT I HONESTLY
CAME HERE, LIKE,
NOT KNOWING WHAT WAS GOING TO
HAPPEN AT THE END.
EVERYTHING ALONG
THE WAY, LIKE,
SOME OF MY HARDEST GOODBYES I
FEEL LIKE HAVE
ALWAYS LED ME TO
YOU.
SO I DON'T KNOW.
I DON'T KNOW.
WE'VE TALKED ABOUT A LOT.
I THINK THIS IS... IT'S, LIKE,
INSANE TO LOOK BACK ON.
NO, HONESTLY, WHICH IS WHY,
LIKE, I FEEL LIKE I DON'T WANT
TO PUT PRESSURE ON ME OR YOU.
YEAH.
I THINK IT'S,
LIKE, I OBVIOUSLY
DIDN'T EXPECT TO
EVER BE HERE IN
THIS POSITION OR EVEN, LIKE,
STEPPING OUT OF THE LIMO NIGHT
ONE, LIKE, LOOKING BACK ON IT
NOW, IT'S JUST, LIKE, "WHAT IN
THE HELL?"
LIKE, IT'S INSANE.
AND IT WAS, LIKE, FROM THAT
POINT, I, LIKE,
I REALIZED THAT
I WAS STARTING
TO FALL FOR YOU.
AND IT JUST KEPT
GETTING, LIKE,
MORE AND MORE.
I THINK THAT'S KIND OF, LIKE,
OUR RELATIONSHIP IN THE
BEGINNING WAS, LIKE, PHYSICAL
AND FUNNY.
AND THEN I WAS,
LIKE, ALL RIGHT,
I'M GOING TO TAKE A RISK AND
JUST OPEN UP TO THIS GIRL AND
JUST GIVE HER,
LIKE, 100% OF ME.
AND YOU MATCHED
ME, LIKE, EVERY
STEP OF THE WAY,
WHICH I KNOW IS
NOT EASY TO DO.
AND FOR ME, IT WAS NOT EASY TO
DO EITHER.
IT'S BEEN CRAZY.
BUT I TRULY LOVE YOU, AND I
DO...
I DO WANT TO SPEND THE REST OF
MY LIFE WITH YOU.
AND I DON'T WANT TO RUSH
ANYTHING AND I
DON'T WANT THERE
TO BE ANY EXPECTATIONS OR
ANYTHING THAT WOULDN'T BE
NATURAL TO US.
I'M TELLING YOU
HOW MUCH I LOVE
YOU.
I STILL HAVE SO MANY
QESTIONS THAT I
JUST HOPE I CAN
FIGURE OUT,
BECAUSE I DO WANT A
PROPOSAL FROM HIM.
AND I'M JUST
LOOKING FOR HONESTY
WITH HIM.
I KNOW, LIKE, THE
TRUTH, IF IT'S
NOT WHAT I WANT TO HEAR, IF HE
SAYS HE'S NOT
READY TO PROPOSE,
IT'S GOING TO HURT NO MATTER
WHAT.
BUT I JUST WANT TO KNOW THE
TRUTH.
I MEAN, OBVIOUSLY, I WANT TO
LEAVE HERE WITH YOU.
I DO.
I KNOW THIS
IS A BIG DEAL, AN
ENGAGEMENT AND EVERYTHING.
I WISH I KNEW BETTER AND I CAN
JUST BE, LIKE, "THIS IS 100%
EVERYTHING AND I'VE BEEN HERE
BEFORE AND I KNOW
HOW TO HANDLE
THE SITUATION."
BUT IT'S JUST, I DON'T KNOW.
I FEEL PRETTY
GOOD ABOUT WHAT
A LIFE WITH YOU WOULD BE LIKE.
I HOPE IT'S LIKE THIS.
THE LAST THING I WANT TO DO IS
PUT PRESSURE ON YOU.
BUT I DON'T... I'M NOT THE ONE
PROPOSING, AND
THAT'S WHY, LIKE,
I DON'T KNOW, WE KIND OF LIKE
SEE, MAYBE.
BUT IF WE HAVE
TO, LIKE, LISTEN
TO OURSELVES.
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN, "SEE?"
I DON'T KNOW.
I REALLY WANT US
TO WORK, AND I
KNOW, LIKE, I
THINK ALL ODDS ARE
KIND OF WORKING AGAINST THAT.
BUT I JUST, LIKE,
I WANT TO DATE
YOU.
IN THE REAL WORLD, LIKE,
I WANT TO DATE YOU.
AND IT'S...
GETTING ENGAGED BEFORE THAT
HAPPENS, IS THAT HOW THINGS
USUALLY GO?
YEAH.
ALL I WANTED WAS CLARITY.
I'M SORRY IF THIS HAS BEEN
UPSETTING.
I FEEL LIKE I CAN'T REALLY
TALK ABOUT IT.
OKAY.
HE SAID "I WANT TO CONTINUE
TO DATE YOU."
SO THAT DOESN'T SCREAM
"I WANT TO PROPOSE."
I DON'T WANT TO FORCE HIM
INTO A DECISION.
THIS IS ACTUALLY CRAZY.
I DON'T WANT TO
DO THIS ANYMORE.
NO, I DON'T WANT ANYONE TO BE
FORCED, JUST...
LIKE, I AM SO SICK OF THIS.
GABBY.
WHAT IS THIS?
HE'S NOT READY.
HE JUST TOLD ME.
HE SAID "I WANT TO DATE YOU."
THAT'S WHAT HE SAID.
WHEN HIM AND I WERE OUT ON THE
BALCONY, HE SAID "I WANT TO
LEAVEHERE AND I WANT TO DATE
YOU."
I WANT TO BE WITH ERICH.
FOREVER.
SO I WANT HIM TO PROPOSE.
WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO DO, WALK
AWAY BECAUSE HE'S NOT READY TO
PROPOSE?
SO HERE WE ARE, BIG FAT
DUMPSTER FIRE.
BIG MESS.
WELCOME BACK TO THE LIVE
FINALE OF "THE BACHELORETTE."
I AM HERE WITH
RACHEL AND GABBY
WHO HAVE BEN WATCHING WITH US
ALL NIGHT.
AT THIS POINT,
ALL I CAN SAY IS
WOW.
OBVIOUSLY I WAS THE BACHELOR
YEARS AND YEARS AGO.
ANYTHING AS
EMOTIONAL AS WHAT WE
ARE SEEING.
THE BIG QUESTION RIGHT NOW IS,
HOW IS THIS WHOLE
THING GOING TO
END?
EVERYBODY, WHAT DO YOU THINK?
ARE YOU READY
FOR A SNEAK PEEK?
ALL RIGHT.
HERE IT IS.
THIS IS CRAZY.
WE ARE LITERALLY ABOUT TO BE
ENGAGED TOMORROW TO OUR DREAM
GUYS.
LITERALLY DREAMS.
TINO TRULY IS THE MAN OF MY
DREAMS.
THIS IS THE DAY I'VE BEEN
WAITING FOR MY WHOLE LIFE.
I DO LOVE ERICH WITH ALL MY
HEART, SO I DO WANT A PROPOSAL
FROM HIM.
LIKE, I'M SO SICK OF THIS.
I JUST REALLY NEED TO TELL
YOU SOMETHING THAT'S BEEN
WEIGHING ON ME.
THERE IS NO WAY THIS WORKS
OUT.
NOBODY CAN
TELL ME I'M CRAZY.
HE SAID I WANT TO LEAVE HERE
AND I WANT TO DATE YOU.
SHE'S THROWING ME UNDER THE
BUS SAYING ALL
OF THIS IS LIES?
SHE CALLED IT.
ALL I KNOW IS REJECTION.
IT'S SCARY AS HELL.
YOU'RE LYING STRAIGHT TO MY
FACE.
LOOK ME IN THE EYES
AND LIE TO ME AGAIN.
YOU DID SAY THAT.
YOU SAID THAT.
I WANT TO LEAVE
HERE ENGAGED.
IF HE DOESN'T PROPOSE,
I'LL BE DEVASTATED.
I WANT AN ANSWER FOR WHY
YOU DID WHAT YOU DID.
HONESTLY, I THINK HE MIGHT
WALK AWAY.
I HAVE NEVER FELT THIS
BLINDSIDED AND BETRAYED.
I'M DONE.
SEE?
I TOLD YOU.
THIS WAS THE MOST DRAMATIC
FINALE IN
BACHELORETTE HISTORY.
WE'LL BE BACK HERE ON STAGE.
WHO WILL BE ON
STAGE WITH A RING
ON HER FINGER?
WILL IT BE GABBY?
WILL IT BE RACHEL?
MIGHT IT BE BOTH?
WE CERTAINLY HOPE IT IS.
WHO IS GOING TO BE THE NEXT
BACHELOR?
YOU'LL GET THE
ANSWERS TO ALL OF
THOSE QUESTIONS NEXT WEEK.
TUESDAY, SEPTEMBER 20.
JOIN US.
THEY WILL LEAVE ALL OF
BACHELOR NATION
AND SPEECHLESS.
THIS LIVE FINALE.
WHAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN?
I'M NOT GOING TO TELL YOU.
BIG TONY IS GOING TO BE HERE.
GRANDPA IS ALSO GOING TO BE H
HERE.
ALSO A HISTORY MAKING
INTERACTIVE EVENT.
FIND OUT.
SEE YOU HERE.
AWESOME.
I WANT TO GIVE A BIG THANK YOU
TO OUR MUSINGS
TO YOUR AUDIENCE.
OF COURSE ALL OF
YOU OUT THERE.
I'M JESSE PALMER.
GOOD NIGHT.
>>>>oakislandtk
www.opensubtitles.org