- Previously
on "The Bachelorette"...
- Welcome to New Orleans.
My family's gonna love you.
Are they?
- Meeting families is huge.
If his family doesn't like me,
like, how is this gonna work
in the future?
- I just saw the chemistry
and I said to myself,
"She could be the one."
- That's a scary thing
to say itself.
- Best-case scenario,
they live happily ever after.
- I could never see myself
getting engaged.
Like, that's just not
something I could see
myself doing, at this point.
- I just have
a hard time believing
a whirlwind fairy tale trip
is really gonna prepare you
for marriage.
- I feel like I could be
the most perfect person,
and they wouldn't have liked me.
- I mean, you're saying
all the right things,
but I want to see him
fall for the right person.
- I don't know how I made it
out of that house alive.
I almost cried.
- And tonight...
- Whoo!
- We're here in Mexico.
Bienvenidos.
And I am ready
to fall in love this week.
You good, Rach?
I fully expect to be
getting down on one knee
at the end of this.
I am in love with you, Gabby,
and I do not want to leave here
without you.
- You're so sweet.
- I'm just in shock
that we're at this point.
This is the moment
during Clayton's season
where everything went haywire,
everything went off the wall.
- It's really, really hard
to think about her
being on an Overnight.
It's gutting
to even think about.
- I'm, like, ready
to be engaged.
- Are you asking where I feel
with that whole thing...
- Yeah.
- 'Cause we have a week left?
- No pressure.
- You know, when you have
crazy feelings for somebody,
it's gonna hurt to know
that there are
other people still there.
It's not my intention to have
any sort of ultimatum
or anything like that,
but I can't just, like,
go through this week
being like everything's fine.
- I feel like
we were able to have,
like, an honest conversation
about it.
So you brought me here
to tell me it again.
There she is!
- Is that my two favorite
things, Rachel and champagne?
- Oh, my God!
- Hi!
- You look so beautiful.
- You too.
Oh, my God, it's so good
to see you in México.
- I know, we're here!
I can't believe it.
We have so much to celebrate
and talk about.
- Oh, my God. I know.
- First of all, cheers to you.
You look so beautiful.
- You do.
- And I'm just in shock
that we're at this point.
- Me too.
- Because I feel like
this is the point when
we were on Clayton's season
where everything went haywire,
like, everything
went off the wall.
- Yeah.
You know, this week is serious.
It's Overnights
with multiple men,
and being adult women
and looking for engagement,
like, it is something that
where intimacy, physical
intimacy, is something,
you know, that we need
to, like, figure out
and see if we're compatible
in that sense too.
But as much as I want to revert
back to, like,
"Let's play, let's giggle,
let's, like, chase each other
around naked"...
- Well, we could
still do that, but...
- Yeah, but I know
I'm gonna have to, like,
flip it into, "But we do
have to utilize this time."
- Right.
To be honest, like,
I have been,
like, dreading this week.
- Yeah.
- Because of what happened
with Clayton...
- Mm-hmm.
- I have been so scared
to be honest with them
because of how he made me feel
in that moment
when he stood in front of us
and he was like,
"Not only am I intimate
with both of you,
"I'm love with all of you.
I'm in love with Susie."
- Yeah.
- And just the general disregard
for everyone's feelings
but his own.
- You know, I thought the way
that he told me he loved me
and the way
that we were interacting,
I'm like, "It's me."
- Exactly.
- And that's when, like...
That's where my pain
came from is,
I almost felt
like I was manipulated.
- Yes.
- So I never want
to make anyone else
feel the way that we did,
but that's kind of...
Where are you at with your guys?
- With Tino, I feel like
he was the first one
that I knew had
really strong feelings for.
- Yeah.
- It's never changed.
It's really only gotten better.
There's so many things
about Tino
that I can see myself
being with forever.
But I do obviously
have to talk about
what happened with his Hometown.
- Yeah.
- Because his family
weren't accepting of me.
- Yeah.
- And I don't know if it's,
they're just against the fact
that this is so not traditional
and that's maybe what
they wanted for him,
and this just isn't that,
but, I mean, Tino is an adult,
he's making his own decisions,
and he finally told me
he's falling in love with me.
Which was so important to me.
I was freaking out.
Like, I didn't know
how I'd get through this week
if he didn't tell me.
- Yeah.
- And he did tell me,
so I'm really happy
that he did that,
but I just really, I think,
ultimately want clarity
with myself because I don't
have a decision right now.
- Mm-hmm.
- And with Zach,
every single piece is there.
Zach has never left me
in the dark with how he felt.
He was the first one to
tell me he was falling for me.
He is so incredible.
He is funny and he's a gentleman
and he is vulnerable
and emotional
and just able to connect
in a different way.
But I don't think
I'm there with Zach.
And this is getting
days away from an engagement.
I want to use the time
to really be honest
with myself and with him...
- Yeah.
- To see if I can get there,
because like you said, we have
to be honest with them.
But everything is
so perfect on paper.
- Yeah.
Wait, okay,
so who are you bringing first?
- Aven.
- Wow.
Look at this.
- I think immediately with Aven,
we really had
this great foundation
and we just continued
to build on it.
- Yeah.
- We have
that romantic connection
and that physical connection
and he's able to be
so honest with me,
and every single he says,
I 100% believe.
I'm a little nervous
because I haven't
told Aven how I feel yet.
- Yeah.
Like, what are you feeling now?
- I feel like I'm falling
in love with Aven, for sure.
And he told me he was
falling in love with me
during his Hometown,
but I didn't say it back.
I was just kind of at the point
where I was still really scared
because of what happened
on the season with Clayton.
- Yeah.
- I don't want Aven
to feel like that as well,
so I want to get
that fear behind me.
And I really want
to tell him how I feel,
but I'm so nervous about it.
- Aww.
- So what do you honestly need
with your time with Jason,
and, like, how do you feel
right now?
- We just have, like,
a special connection
that I feel like
I've never really
felt with anyone before.
He's always been the most
kind of emotionally available
to me.
- Do you feel like you're
falling in love with him?
- I think I'm definitely
falling in love with him,
but I don't actually know
how he feels about me.
I feel like
I have to just let him know
exactly what I need, and then...
- I think you deserve it.
You deserve
to know how he feels.
- Yeah.
- How do you feel about Johnny?
- Johnny and I do have
so much fun together
and I have watched him
grow so much.
I think, unfortunately,
we could be
in two different places
in our lives
where I'm very ready for
an engagement and marriage,
and he's not.
But I can see the growth
in him as a person,
so he could really surprise me.
- Right.
So, wait, how are you feeling
going into tonight?
I know you've already told Erich
that you're falling in love
with him.
- I love how playful
we are together.
We have good banter.
Our relationship has grown
so much
over last Hometown week,
and I told him I was
falling in love with him
because it's true.
And I didn't realize
that I needed
to hear that until he told me.
But, you know,
we're going into this week
having feelings
in a certain way,
but they can definitely change.
- And we're really
gonna have to use
every single second of the time
we have left
to really make a decision
that's best for us.
- Yeah, I think
this week is gonna be
unreal, transformative.
- We get to rewrite
what this week means.
- Yeah.
- And make it
into something positive
and ending with an engagement
for both of us.
- I'm so excited.
- And chase each other around
naked.
This is the most important week
of my whole journey.
- Let's get on
with our big days...
- I know. Let's go.
- And ever bigger nights.
- Bigger nights.
And I'm so excited
to see my guys this week.
Because it is just
absolutely gorgeous here.
Beaches. The jungle.
Literally the perfect place
to fall in love.
- I'm so excited.
I love it here.
I love the warm weather.
Rachel and I are going
on our first Overnights
this week.
It is so exciting
because I can see myself
potentially being engaged
with one of my men.
So there's a lot
riding on these dates.
And this is the perfect place
for me to end my journey.
Not just because
it's beautiful and tropical,
but also because I'm ready.
I know what I want.
I am ready
to fall in love this week
and to hear the words
"I love you, Gabby."
I can't wait.
I feel excited, hopeful,
ready for the future.
Let's get it started.
- Today's my first
Overnight date,
and I'm excited to spend
the day with Erich.
We've grown so close
after last week.
Erich and I had
such a good Hometown,
which was really
a huge stepping stone for us
because I saw
his emotional side.
His dad has been
battling cancer.
I truly can't imagine
how hard it is on Erich,
but seeing his family
and how much they mean to him
just show
what a good person he is.
And that night, we shared
that we were falling
in love with each other,
and I'm still just reveling
in that bliss.
Bienvenidos.
How are you?
- I'm good. How are you?
- It's good to see you.
- It's good to see you too.
This?
I've never met anyone
like Erich in the way
that we feel together
and around each other.
Okay, let's go.
Like, this is actually
our first date without family.
But this week could be
the most important week
even in the weeks to come
because there is
an Overnight date tonight.
It's the only time
we get uninterrupted time
alone, truly alone.
So today, I want him
to treat me like a girlfriend,
like a potential fiancée.
Because I think Erich and I
do have physical chemistry.
And I'm really
looking forward to seeing
where it goes tonight.
Yo.
- Is this water?
- Yeah.
- Do you know what that means?
"Salto de Los Enamorados."
Take off your clothes.
Oh, gladly.
- I mean, it doesn't,
but you can.
- Okay.
- But this is the lovers' leap.
- Hell yeah.
- Yeah.
- Let's do it, like, right now.
No, wait, hold on.
Have you jumped
off of things before?
- I have.
- You're gonna have
a lot of fun.
This is a cenote.
It's like a natural hole
in the ground in a jungle.
So should we jump?
- Yes!
I'm feeling absolutely amazing.
Gabby and I have had
such a crazy connection
this whole time.
And last time I saw her,
I told her I was
falling in love with her.
So we basically
crossed the threshold
where our relationship
kinda just took
this, like, crazy leap.
You ready?
- Ready.
- Go!
- No!
Oh, my God, that's actually
higher than I thought.
- But dating Gabby,
it hasn't been, like,
really easy to be honest
because there are
still two other people here.
So there's a possibility
I might not be the one for her.
- Whoo!
No!
- That's the risk for me.
That's the thing
that I think about,
you know,
in the back of my mind.
But at this point, I'm willing
to throw myself at her.
Kind of have to take
a leap of faith.
Because she is
so freaking worth it.
- It feels good
being in the water, though.
- Yeah, it's really nice.
- Now I want to do the high one.
I don't know if I can do it.
Okay, you go look.
- A little tall, not gonna lie.
- Yeah.
- You want to just do it?
- No.
- I think what it is
is just one step out.
- Oh, God.
Oh, I'm afraid.
- You got this.
- So just one step
- Literally one step.
- Standing here thinking
about making this jump,
it's a lot like falling in love.
It's a huge leap of faith
and it's very intimidating.
- Yep, you got it down.
You got this.
- Oh, I'm so scared.
I don't want to make
a big deal out of it.
I know we're trying to have fun.
And my heart is telling me
to leap, but it's so scary.
Maybe you go first.
- I want to go with you.
I'm gonna jump when you jump.
I'm not jumping without you.
- You know,
throughout this whole journey,
one of my biggest
fears has been,
will I be accepted for who I am?
I think I'm too scared.
You got this.
But I have to remind myself
how loving and supportive
Erich has been
every time we're together.
- You can do it.
- And right now,
he's definitely doing it again,
trying to give me courage
to take the leap.
And he does make me feel
really safe.
- Deep breath, deep breath,
and then you go.
- I'm gonna go.
- Okay.
Don't think. Just go.
Whoo!
Okay.
- Yeah.
Whoo!
- I'm not always
the most adventurous.
- Yeah! Whoo!
- But jumping
off of the highest landing
was really incredible.
And having Erich's support
makes it so much easier.
It makes me feel so loved
and that we can do
lots of hard things together.
And, honestly, that's what
I want in my husband.
Cheers to a great day.
- Cheers. Cheers for jumping.
- I wouldn't have been
so freaked out
if I, like, would've went
faster, but...
- You did it.
That's all that matters.
- Yeah.
- I feel like the last time
I saw you was so long ago.
- Me too.
I was really looking forward
to seeing you,
especially after, like,
how good our date was
with your family.
- Yeah.
I felt, like, so good
leaving there.
Like, it wasn't
an easy day, obviously.
- Yeah.
- But, like, I really
wanted you to be there.
I knew it wasn't gonna be
easy for me to, like,
make it through that day.
- Yeah.
- To see my dad, and, like,
I told you afterwards,
like, he's not... he's really not
doing that well.
- Yeah. I'm so sorry.
- And, like, being there
and then leaving quickly
was just like, damn.
- I know.
I didn't want to leave.
- And then to sit there and,
like, watch you drive away,
it was, like, so dramatic
and I was like, damn.
- I know. It was.
- I'm, like, getting emotional.
- Aww.
No, I know I always say,
like, thank you,
but really it means, like,
so much that you're here,
and I think seeing your family
put everything in perspective,
and so I understand
how hard it is for you
and how hard it must be.
So I hope you know how much
I do appreciate you.
And I didn't know that I needed
to, like, hear how you felt,
but it was so good to hear.
And I do,
I feel like it brought us,
like, so much closer,
just, like, everything.
- Yeah, I appreciate that.
Being here is not easy,
but it's, like,
moments like this
that I'm like,
"I, like, need to be here.
I need to be here with you."
- Today with Erich
was definitely as good
as I hoped, maybe even better.
I mean, it's always
felt easy with Erich,
but I feel like
there were moments
where he was able to really
support me as a true partner.
I love being wrapped around him.
I love when he holds me.
I love kissing him
in the middle of the cenote.
I feel like
I didn't want it to end.
- Now we're here and this has
to last forever now,
so I'm not leaving.
- I'm so happy.
Going into tonight's dinner,
I'm excited for us to really lay
everything out on the table.
The more time
I spend with Erich,
the easier it is for me
to really see my life with him.
I think tonight will
really help with that.
We know we're at that point
in our relationship,
and I think it could be
just what I need
to really see myself
engaged to him
and, you know,
at the end of this.
I just want to crawl inside you.
- You do look unbelievable.
- Oh, my gosh, thank you.
Being with Erich
today was amazing.
It was easy and natural
and comfortable and so much fun.
I felt really connected to him.
And tonight, there's a potential
to spend the night together.
So I'm excited.
Tonight, I want to push us
into being honest
with our feelings.
I know it's scary
as hell and I think,
honestly,
the Overnight portion of it
is where it becomes
the most real.
Isn't it cute?
But before we commit
to that, you know,
I need to know where he stands.
Will he be able to give me
unconditional love
and accept me for me?
- I'm taking this jacket off.
- I like
how you leave it unbuttoned.
So I'm hoping
that tonight with Erich,
I can be all the different
sides of myself in one breath.
- I was really looking forward
to seeing you.
Thinking that Hometown
was not easy.
- Yeah.
- And then to see you today,
I was like,
"We finally have this time,
like, just us."
Like you said, there's no
family involved for once.
I was like, "This is
actually gonna be amazing."
And then next thing you know,
we're doing something
that I really freaking like
to do,
which is scare myself.
- Yeah.
- And to see you scared too,
I was like, "This is perfect."
- Well, I didn't want to make
a big deal out of it,
and then it became a big deal,
but I feel like
you were, like, so supportive
and so patient with me.
And I really appreciate that.
- Yeah.
I think after our Hometown
and, you know,
seeing you with my family,
I could not have expected it
to go as well as it did.
And the thing
that I didn't tell you
was that my family is obsessed
with you.
And I just could not
have imagined...
- And I them.
- I can... I'm not up there
being like, "Wow,
this is freaking amazing," but,
like, to hear that from them
is, like, the ultimate
validation to be like,
"This girl is amazing."
And I'm just so ridiculously
attracted to you
and I couldn't wait
to see you after that.
- Definitely, like, walking in,
I think I had to get
my bearings and stuff too,
but after a second,
it was, like, so easy,
like, with your dad,
with your mom,
and with your sister.
They, I think,
welcomed me so much
to where I can really
see myself as a part
of your family, and it...
I think I've probably told you
a little bit about it,
but my growing up was
just really different
in that my parents,
like, separated early
and my dad was still
active duty in the Air Force,
so he moved away.
For a lot of years,
I would just see him
for Christmas and summers.
And my mom was working two jobs,
and they had us real young,
so I did a lot
of growing up on my own.
And, like, there were times
growing up
when I did have to change
who I was
in order to receive love
as a child.
- Yeah.
- And my mom and I don't
really have a relationship,
but I know she did
the best she could growing up.
It's just kind of complicated
and messy.
But looking at your family,
it's like...
It's so nice to see,
you know, you guys
really are a whole,
not, like, parts of a whole.
- Yeah. Yeah.
As hard as it is, I mean,
I can respect so much about you
and knowing where you came from
and how, like, strong you are
and how emotionally intelligent
you are
and how you handle situations.
Like, I just...
I don't know, I can't imagine
going through
what you've gone through
and you turned out
so amazing that...
You're a beautiful person.
- Aww.
Thank you.
So...
Like, last week,
you know, I told you
I was falling in love with you
and we left Europe
and I was, like,
falling for you,
and then I watched you leave
in that SUV
and I was just like,
"This is when it starts
to really hurt," when you
have to, like, get torn apart
and I don't get to see you
again for however long,
and I don't know how long it is.
So I spend that time in between
just thinking about us
and how much this relationship
means to me
and how much I hope
it means to you.
And I'm kind of past the point
where it's like,
"I'm falling for you."
"I'm falling in love with you."
Like, I am love
in with you, Gabby,
and I do not want
to leave here without you.
- You're so sweet.
I do really see
a future with you.
You have a way
of making me feel, like,
really safe, no matter what.
And I really, really
appreciate you.
And, like, I am
falling in love with you.
I really am.
I feel like I'm weightless.
Like, the happiest person
in the whole world.
When Erich said
that he was in love with me,
it felt so right.
It means a lot. It really does.
- I know.
- He's taught me so much
about myself
and that I can be loved
and that he's ready
to love me for me.
I'm just so excited to be
falling in love with him
and to share it with him.
There's something for you.
It's a surprise.
- Okay.
"Gabby and Erich, love is
really a leap of faith.
"Hopefully, you both
felt that today
"out in the beautiful
Mexican countryside.
"If you choose to take
this next leap,
"please use this key to stay as
a couple in the Fantasy Suite.
Jesse."
- What do you think?
Obviously yes.
I'm so happy right now.
You know, I am in love
with Gabby
and, you know, I told her
that I love her,
and for me it was a huge weight
lifted off my chest.
- Thank you.
- And now I get the most
meaningful time with her,
with just us.
Like, I'm just so excited.
- Being loved by Erich
just feels really incredible.
It's what I've been
waiting for for so long.
I just want to hold on to it
for as long as I can.
Oh, my God, it's big.
We finally get to, like, revel
in each other and be together.
Oh. Oh, is there a hot tub?
Oh, dear God.
Oh, my God.
This is insane.
So I want to shed
every last wall.
- This is really nice.
- I want to give both of us
the chance
to really feel
each other's love.
When I'm with him,
like, I want to be with him
and I can see myself
with him forever.
And every time we kiss,
the world really does melt away.
And for once,
I feel like the future
is gonna be so, so good.
- Whoa.
All right, make some breakfast?
- Mm-hmm.
- Are you gonna make me cook?
- No, I feel like I should cook.
- Waking up this morning,
it was amazing.
You know, we spent this
incredible night together.
I got to just see the raw Gabby
and have conversations,
and she is everything and more
than what I thought.
She is, to me, a person
I'm obsessed with.
- Am I doing this wrong?
100% yes.
And it's, like, mind-boggling
that I had the opportunity
to spend the night with her
and have
this, like, crazy
off-camera experience.
You know, I've thrown
myself out there 100%
and told her that I love her,
and for me that's, like...
That's all of me.
So going into the rest
of this week,
I'm gonna try not to think
about everything.
I mean, the reality is, it sucks
that there are
other relationships happening.
I love spending time with you.
- This was sad.
- I know thinking
about things like her
in, you know, the Fantasy
Suites with these other guys,
it's just not gonna
be healthy for me.
I know how I get.
I get really in my head,
and I'm not,
like, a super jealous person,
but, you know,
when you have
crazy feelings for somebody,
it's gonna hurt to know
that there are
other people still there.
- Do you know how I feel?
- Confused.
- You think I'm confused?
- I think I'm confused.
- Why?
- I don't know.
- What do you mean?
I feel like you know
that just being with you
is so easy.
And it does,
it feels like I've known you
for so much longer than I have.
Waking up this morning
with Erich, I feel...
I don't know. A lot.
Are you gonna miss me?
- I'm so gonna miss you.
I'm gonna cry in the shower.
- I am definitely
more than falling in love
with Erich.
I really think I am
in love with him,
and I know he deserves to know,
but I know how strong
those words are, and I want
to be able, honestly,
to tell just one person
at the end of this,
and I can definitely
see it being him,
but I know I have to save it
for the right moment.
I hope you know
I don't want to let you go.
- I believe you.
I'm here.
- I know.
And I know what you're feeling,
and I know it's not,
like, okay, but...
Please just be patient with me.
I mean, undeniably,
when I'm with him,
like, I want to be
with him and I can
see myself with him forever.
And I hope
that that feeling holds up,
but I'm scared that it won't.
- I'll miss the hell out of you.
- I'll miss you more.
- I'll see you soon?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- I have a pit in my stomach.
I get up nerves on what you're
gonna do when you walk away.
- I'm just gonna keep walking
all the way back to New Jersey.
- I didn't want to say goodbye.
I wanted to spend
the whole day with him,
so I know my heart's
in the right place,
but there is also
just this heaviness of,
I have more work to do on myself
and the other men that are here.
You know, what if I have
this same exact thing
with somebody else?
And then what?
You too.
- I'll see you soon.
- I want to be able
to say, you know,
I want to be engaged to him
because I know it's him,
but I don't know.
- Bye, Gabby.
- Okay.
Bye.
I'm gonna throw up.
- Bye.
You know, I almost didn't
want to leave,
but, you know, one thing
she said is, "Just be patient.
I'm here for you,"
but, you know,
this is incredibly painful
because what if she's falling
in love
with Johnny and Jason as well?
It's hard to think about that.
So I'm taking her advice
and I'm not gonna get emotional.
I'm not gonna cry
in the shower anymore.
I'm just gonna be patient
and look forward
to the next time I see her,
and hopefully it's soon.
- This week is really hard.
I know I'm falling
in love with Rachel.
And it's so hard
feeling this strongly about her
knowing she's on an Overnight
with one of the other guys.
It's just beyond me
at times that, like,
she's, like, even exploring
other physical connections.
I can't imagine her
wanting to spend
the night with anybody else.
This is just torture.
It's like being
in the Twilight Zone.
Even just talking about it now
makes me want to throw up.
- Hi.
I missed you.
Hi.
- I missed you too.
It's so good to see you.
- It's so good to see you again.
- You look beautiful!
- Thank you.
- My gosh.
- Oh, my gosh.
Well, I have
such a fun date planned.
You know,
the water is really blue,
so I figured we should
check it out together.
What do you think?
- I'm so in.
I want to do whatever today.
- Are you excited?
- I'm so excited.
- I'm so excited
to spend this day with Aven.
He is definitely someone
I was really interested
right off the bat.
Okay, let's go.
- Amazing.
- You look so good.
He is so attractive
and just an amazing person.
He really is
just the complete package,
and I do feel so lucky
that he's with me here today.
This is our ride today.
- Wow.
- You want to go see?
- Yeah, I'm in.
- Let's go and check it out.
- Rachel looks beautiful,
as always.
She's extremely attractive.
It's overwhelming sometimes.
And I'm excited.
This is so cool.
Look at all this.
There's a hot tub!
You're kidding!
- I know.
- So I'm really looking
forward to today.
I can't believe
how clear this water is.
- You want me to put
sunscreen on you?
- Yeah.
You want me to put some on you?
- Yeah. Can you get my back?
- Yeah.
The more and more I've gotten
to spend time with Rachel,
I continue to see her
as somebody that I can spend
the rest of my life with.
And last week at my Hometown,
I told her I was falling
in love with her.
So, hopefully, this week
is about going
where this is potentially
gonna end.
And the end is an engagement.
Cheers to building
on what we already have,
so cheers to you...
- Cheers.
- And to this week
and being in Mexico.
- Last week, when Aven told me
he's falling in love with me,
I felt so happy.
But I didn't say it back.
I was still in a headspace
where I didn't want
to say anything
to anyone until the very end
just because the love word
is a really big word
that was used by Clayton
really just carelessly
when I was on the other side.
But this week, I'm in charge
of how I want to move forward.
And after today, I really hope
to be ready to take that step.
- Mm.
How are we gonna
get tired of that?
The last time Rachel was
in this situation,
it wasn't easy for her.
I know this is kind of when
everything hit the fan.
I just want to do
everything I can
on my part to make her
feel special
and make her feel comfortable.
But it definitely is
a little bit scary
feeling this strongly
towards someone,
especially with other people
still being involved.
- Tino.
- Jesse, what's up?
- How's it going, man?
How you doing?
- What a pleasant surprise.
- Dude, it's been a minute
since I saw you back stateside,
so I just wanted
to check in with you.
- Yeah, come on in.
- You got a minute?
Awesome, man. Appreciate it.
- Absolutely.
- I just wanted
to catch up with you.
Like, tell me
where your head's at.
How's everything going?
- The waiting game is just,
like, gut-wrenching at times.
- Yeah.
- Every day here
when I'm not getting
the date card
or the invitation or whatever is
nails on a chalkboard to me.
It is trying my patience
beyond anything
I could've, like, ever imagined,
and it's not gonna make sense
to anybody who, you know,
like, I explain this to
later on.
Like, how much
I struggled this week.
Except for you, probably.
- Yeah. I get it.
- But Rachel leaves me
with no doubt it's worth it.
So I'm gonna see this through,
and this week's gonna be awful,
but it's gonna end amazingly.
- Yeah, no, for sure.
I hear that.
Catch me up first. though.
Take me back to your Hometown.
How'd it go
on Hometowns with Rachel?
- Well, so my dad decided
to really take an interest
and make sure he asked
some tough questions, and...
Yeah, Rachel walked out of it
thinking he didn't like her.
- Really?
- And, I mean, I think
that was hard on her.
So it's horrible to think about.
- I had such a good time
in your hometown.
- It went as best
as it could've gone
and better than I thought
it would, honestly.
Yeah, I know I talked
to both my parents, obviously,
and they both were like,
"She's so amazing."
And I could tell
that they could see me
and, like, how happy I was
and the energy I had around you.
And that's the first thing
they both said to me
when I sat down with them
was, like,
"Wow, you look very happy
right now."
And I'm like, "Yeah, I am."
- My hopes going into it was,
like, I just want them
to, like, accept me at least,
and I feel like they did
more than that.
Like, I felt so welcome.
That going so well has, like,
made this so much easier too
because I know that they would
accept me, and it's just...
And it's a good feeling.
- Absolutely. You're accepted.
- And I think
it went really well.
- Dad and Mom love you.
- I know.
- Naturally, Dad is, like,
a little bit skeptical,
but I think she was, you know,
a little caught off guard,
so is it my favorite
of situations
where I'm splitting time
with other guys?
No.
Like, no
by a million times over.
And if I wasn't so sure
that, like, she's future
Mrs., like, Forever for me,
like, this would be
a probably easy week
to walk away from.
- Yeah.
- I think, like, you
meeting my family
and the reaction
and, like, just the whole day
and night together,
I'm just, like, yeah,
falling in love with you.
So that's why I had to say it.
And I meant it.
- I know it's fast
even for this journey,
but I knew for, in hindsight,
probably, like, weeks
that I felt this strongly
for her.
- That you were falling
in love with her?
- Yeah.
I mean, probably since Bruges.
- Wow.
- It's really, really hard
to think about her
being on an Overnight.
You know, it's hard
to be patient and wait,
especially when you know,
like, what's going on
while you're waiting.
It's gutting
to even think about.
- Hope it goes great.
- Yeah.
- I'm around
if you need anything, man.
Thanks for the chat.
- See you later, Jesse.
- See you, man.
- It's mind-boggling to me
if, like, she's not sure
at this point.
I certainly don't need
to sleep with anybody else.
- And I'm certainly worried
that my family
being so skeptical could
weigh in on her decision.
- Tonight is my first Overnight,
and it's a really big deal,
and I definitely feel
like I want
to spend tonight
with Aven and have
that intimate time together.
I feel like
it's really important
to explore your
physical connection as well.
And I do feel like
me and Aven are at that point
in our relationship
where that is
the last kind of missing piece.
Hi.
- My gosh, look at you.
So good to see you again.
- How are you?
- I do think
that Aven could be the one.
- This is beautiful.
- I know.
Wait till you see
where we're eating.
It wasn't until his Hometown
that I knew for sure
that I'm falling in love
with him.
And I've been
wanting to tell him.
But I'm so terrified
because of how it went
last time with Clayton.
I was so blindsided by him.
I was so excited for today.
I had the best day with you,
and cheers to a better night.
- Cheers.
- I always am excited
for our dates,
and each time I feel like
we're able to grow so much more
even if it's just,
like, little things.
- Mm-hmm.
- Like, I mean, even just kinda
going back to last week.
Obviously,
it means so much to me
to be able to see myself
with your family
and to see where you came from.
And even just beyond that,
we have come so far.
- Long way.
- Such a long way.
- I definitely agree.
Like, I feel like
from the beginning,
from when I met you,
we just take the next step
every time, and like you said,
it just keeps getting
better and better
and we continue
to grow and grow.
And it's been
an amazing journey so far,
and I really hope it continues.
And yeah, last week
was so special to me.
It just meant a lot
that, you know,
you can potentially see yourself
a part of my family, so...
- And you would never be
in this position
if I didn't genuinely see
a life outside of this with you.
And that's exactly what I told
your parents as well.
- Mm-hmm.
- And I want us to be able
to be in a place
where we are on the page,
so I guess going into tonight,
I really do have a question.
Obviously, we're coming up
to a really big week.
- Absolutely.
- And moving forward,
can you genuinely see yourself
getting engaged in two weeks?
- I definitely can.
I think that, you know,
the moments that we've had,
we've continued
to build, build, and build.
And I think last week, you know,
that was really just kind of
the deciding factor for me
of knowing how ready I am
for this with you
and how I feel about you
and that I'm falling in love
with you.
And yeah, I can definitely see
a life with you
outside of all of this
and an engagement.
I feel like I'm ready for it.
Like, I came here in a really
good, like, mental space
and prepared for that.
And I didn't know if I was gonna
meet somebody that I felt
like I could do that with,
but I have.
- Mm-hmm.
- I'm 100% ready
and feel ready for it.
And you've made that
very easy for me.
But I definitely want it
to be something
that you feel as well.
I want you to feel the same.
- Yeah.
I feel like
everything I ask for,
you really embody.
I mean, we started out
a little bit slower,
but we were able to build
such a strong foundation,
and I feel like
from the beginning,
you were always
the person I was like,
"I feel so safe with him."
And that's huge for me
in a relationship.
- Mm-hmm.
- To feel that I can
be vulnerable with you,
and now I feel like
we are in the place
where we not only have
that friendship
and that foundation,
but just this incredible
romantic connection.
And you're so open
and you're so humble
and I think when I heard you say
that you were falling in love
when we were in Salem,
I was nervous to say
anything back to you
just because on my last journey,
I feel like that word was
really carelessly thrown around.
- Absolutely.
- And what that word
means to me is huge.
And of course I know
it means the same to you.
- Yeah.
- And you would never use
that word
if you weren't
absolutely feeling it,
which is why
I'm comfortable saying
that I am falling in love
with you.
Oh, my gosh.
- Ah!
- And I truly mean it.
- I'm on cloud nine.
It meant
the absolute world to me
that she was able to say
that she was falling
in love with me as well.
I didn't really have words.
I was just so happy to hear
that the feeling was mutual.
- I have something.
- Wow, a card?
I can open this and read it?
- Mm-hmm.
- Oh, wow.
- I feel so happy.
Aven truly has everything
I've asked for and more.
- "Please use this key
to stay together as a couple
in the Fantasy Suite."
Wow. I'm excited.
Let's do it.
- Is it a yes?
- That's a absolute yes for me.
- I really believe every
single thing Aven says to me.
And he continues
to prove with his actions
over and over again
that he wants to be with me.
Oh, my God!
I'm so happy right now.
Wow.
- I feel like this journey
is working for me.
It truly does feel like
he's too good to be true.
Ooh.
- Oh, my God.
- My God.
- This is so beautiful.
- So beautiful.
- I feel so excited
because I've been waiting
for this moment,
and it is the perfect end
to such a fairy tale day.
Like, I just really am
on cloud nine.
Whenever I'm with Aven, I just
fall for him more and more.
And I can definitely see
myself spending
the rest of my life with him.
- That was a good night.
- It was a great night.
I'm on cloud nine.
After last night, for sure.
- After spending the night
with Aven,
I just really am on
kind of a different level
with him right now.
It's gonna be hard to top.
I'm just running
on a high right now.
You're very chipper today.
- Yeah? Am I chipper?
Yes.
It's definitely really important
to explore
your physical connection,
and Aven is the full package.
The full package.
- Cheers to an amazing night
and an amazing morning.
- Cheers.
Oh, do we do this?
- Are we doing this?
Kind of slept
for, like, 20 minutes,
and the sun was just beaming in.
And I was like, "Dang,
this is really nice."
Just waking up next to her.
It felt like... it felt right.
It felt natural and right.
- I really am so excited
that we got to spend
the night together
and take our relationship
to a new level.
- I appreciate it.
- Aven, I am falling
in love with you.
- I'm falling in love
with you deeper.
I'm very confident
about where we're at.
And I would love
to be engaged to her
and start a relationship
and start a life with her.
The fact that I've
now met somebody
that I feel like I can get
there with is a big deal.
Yesterday was amazing.
Thank you.
- Don't forget about me.
- Oh, yeah.
- Don't forget
I'm falling in love with you.
Don't forget that either.
- I'm in love with you too.
I will not forget.
- I'm gonna miss you.
- Bye.
- Oh, my gosh, this has been
excruciating waiting.
I've been dying to see Rachel.
I was ready to pull out my hair.
You establish
an amazing connection
and tell each other
that you're falling in love
with each other
and then have to wait
while other guys are trying
to entertain her.
But that's all fading away
by the minute
because I'm so excited
for the date today.
I really, really want today
to go well.
Rachel's seen
how badly this week can go,
from her previous experience,
and I just, like,
need to keep making it known
that I am the for-sure thing.
I don't care
about the other guys.
And, you know, the light
at the end of the tunnel's
worth stomaching
all these challenges.
- Today, I'm seeing Tino.
Coming off the most incredible
day with Aven.
It's hard to switch
from Aven to Tino.
I'm excited, but I am
so nervous about today
just because last week,
Hometowns didn't go well
with his family.
So I think tonight we do
need to discuss the fact
that his family is
really not supportive
and, like, how we're
gonna move past it.
- Wow.
- Hi.
Good to see you.
- Great to see you.
How are you?
It's a big day.
And I know that this day has
so much potential
to bring us to a whole new
level of feeling.
And I really hope
that we can get there.
I think we can.
How are you doing?
- Better now.
- Better?
Are you ready to go?
- Yeah, I'm so ready.
- Okay, let's go.
- Let's do it.
- How are you?
- I'm good.
- You look nice.
- Thank you.
- I'm excited for you to see
what we're doing.
- I'm excited too.
Oh, horses. Sweet.
- Are you excited?
- Yeah.
- Have you ever
ridden a horse before?
- Not in a couple years.
- I saw that picture of you
with a cowboy hat on
in your house.
Perfect.
Hello, horses.
- Aww.
I've always wanted to do
something like this with Tino,
and the horses in the jungle,
it's just so magical,
so romantic.
It's definitely
a bucket list date.
Their little braids are so cute.
I think Tino is gonna do
great today on the horse.
Okay.
- Sorry, buddy,
I've seen thinner days.
- He's very athletic
and he had the cowboy hat on
in one of his baby pictures,
so maybe he's, like,
real country.
- Oh, this way, this way.
Oh.
- Wait, wait. Hey.
Oh, sorry. Whoa.
- We're not going this way.
Come on, turn around.
I haven't ridden a horse
in a couple years.
Mine's a little rambunctious.
You're good, you're good.
I'm here.
But we're having a great time.
- Oh, my goodness.
This is a ride.
- So excited to be here.
I'm falling really fast,
and when I'm not with her,
I wish I was with her,
and when I'm with her,
I don't want to be
anywhere else.
- Ooh!
- Oh, my God.
- You can do it, Rach.
- See, you're just trying
to race.
Attaboy.
You know, I had nerves
coming into today
just because last week,
Rachel met my family,
which presented
some unique challenges,
but when we see each other
for the first time,
and, like, it starts
going away exponentially
and then we're back
to the middle.
- Oh, no, I can't run
when I'm in this top.
- I mean, this journey's been
a lot of ups and downs,
but we're certainly
riding an up right now.
- They're so in love.
- What do you think?
Are you in love?
- Wow.
- I know.
- This is so cool.
No way. This is all ours?
- Right? Yes!
- Do we get to jump in?
- Do you want to?
- Yeah.
- If I slip and fall in,
are you gonna go in after me?
- 100%.
Are you good?
- I had my foot caught.
- This is so beautiful.
- Yeah, this is amazing.
- I haven't seen you in a while.
- Not since our Hometown.
- I know.
How have you been feeling?
- Really good.
I mean, like, how it ended
kind of, like, sent me
to cloud nine,
and that was amazing.
- Yeah.
Hearing you say you were
falling in love with me,
just hearing that at the end
of the night was just amazing,
and I'm glad I got to tell you
because I have
been feeling it for a while.
So I was just kind of hoping
that you would say something.
- I for sure had been
feeling it for a while.
I wanted to make sure
the moment was just, like...
It did it justice.
And it just could not have felt
more right when I did.
- Yeah.
- And I think all in all, like,
it turned out so amazing,
but yeah, I mean,
here and there, I kinda...
It makes me kind of,
like, scratch my head
'cause the night portion went,
like, a little different
than I expected.
- Mm-hmm.
- But anything
on your mind since?
- I just feel like I have had
a lot of nerves,
especially because I feel
so strongly about you.
And there is a little bit
just of general anxiety
coming off of Hometowns,
and what I've been through,
like...
- No, I know.
This week is loaded, yeah.
- Just in general,
this week is huge
just in so many ways.
You know, I'm so excited,
but in the back of my mind,
I am just, like, scared,
like, "Oh, my God,
like, what if,
like, it goes off the wall?"
- Don't do that.
Trust me.
- I know.
- I'm trying so hard not to.
Like, I'm trying
not to, like, "what if" myself
into, like, a bad place, like...
- Yeah. I know.
- This is the only thing
I care about.
- Me too.
- So it'll be fine.
- Rachel looks nervous.
I don't know why.
I mean, it could be
about my Hometown,
it could be about,
like, my parents
asking her some pretty
penetrating questions.
I hope it's not about that.
You know, I hope we can just
tackle it later tonight.
And I'll try
to kind of peel it back
and make sure
she feels as comfortable
as she always does around me.
- Okay, you count down,
then we go on three.
- One, two, three.
- Can we go again?
- Yeah.
- Okay, let's do it.
- I feel like I have
a lot of anxiety,
and I think he can tell
I'm nervous.
I really hope that tonight
we're able to have
really serious conversations
about last week and what
happened with his parents
and how we're
gonna move past it.
If we don't find a way
to solve the problem,
I just don't think
I can move forward.
- This is so beautiful.
I am so in my head.
As fun as today was,
I think tonight I have to have
some really serious
conversations.
With Tino,
I do have actual issues.
Like, I'm scared to move forward
because of what happened
at Hometowns with his family.
Wow.
- That's amazing.
- It scares me
because my one thing I wanted
out of Hometowns Week
was just acceptance.
And I didn't get it.
- This is yet again
one of the coolest things
I've ever done.
- Look at that.
How much in the back
of his mind is he like,
"My family doesn't like her"?
It's hard to think
that it would have no effect
on how he's thinking.
Thank you.
Can he honestly move forward
with an engagement
without support?
Like, there is kind of
that urgency for me
to really get to the bottom
of this.
How are you feeling?
- Amazing.
- Good.
- Today has been so amazing.
It's always so fun with you.
So I'm just glad we get
even more time together.
You know, I mean,
this week's been challenging.
I mean, I feel like
a broken record saying that
because every second
I have to wait to get
more time with you is like
nails on a chalkboard to me,
but, like always,
the second we're together,
all that fades away
and I'm just so excited
and I love every second
with you, so cheers to that.
- Cheers.
Is there anything on your mind?
- Yeah.
So you said that you were,
like, a little bit nervous
coming into today, and, like,
I just want, like, you to feel
so, like, comfortable
just telling me
whatever is on your mind,
if you're feeling a little nervy
or, you know, uncomfortable.
- Yeah, no, I don't think it's,
like, being uncomfortable.
You never make me
feel uncomfortable,
but I think just in general,
I just have felt
a lot of anxiety
with just this week,
and last time,
it just was such a rough week.
I'm trying to go into everything
with a really positive attitude,
but I guess with that,
I also have been kind of
wanting to talk about Hometowns.
- Okay.
- And kind of what
I spoke to your parents about
a little bit.
- Mm-hmm.
- I just feel like they really
just did not like me.
And it was just
a really big struggle for me,
I think specifically
with your dad.
And I got scared.
"Oh, my gosh, Tino's not
gonna want to move forward.
"Like, how are we
gonna get past this?
"How is this gonna end
in an engagement
when I know how much
your family means to you?"
We've talked so much at length.
You know, 'cause I'm like
"Well, how is he
"gonna move forward
when they they're just
they don't like me,"
and I can't convince anyone.
I think the last thing
your dad said to me,
like, one of the last things,
he was like,
"Well, like, I'm not gonna
disown him if he gets engaged.
Like, I just can't accept it."
And I was just like, "Whoa!"
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Wow, okay.
I didn't know that.
- Or, like, along those lines.
I was like,
"I desperately want this"...
Like, not even just approval,
but, like, "Okay,
we don't get it,
but, like, okay."
And I feel like
I didn't even get that,
and I was like, "Well,
I'm worried about you."
Like, can you get
to a point at the end
where, like, even if you don't
have their approval,
you're still like...
Can you honestly, like,
move forward with this?
- I don't feel like
my dad gets me as much
in the relationship sphere.
He's not... it's not, like, you.
They're really just skeptical
of the situation.
And I think that's...
- Understandable.
- Probably what your parents,
like, did the last time around.
Like, they just can't fathom
the situation we're in
where, like, we do get to know
each other and make each other
feel a certain way
so quickly, so strongly.
But they know me and they know
I wouldn't be here
if I didn't see you
as the future.
- I don't want you to say this
because you're like, "Oh, well,
"I really, like,
want this to work,
so I'm just gonna say that."
Like, do you genuinely believe,
like...
- Yes.
- If, let's say, we got engaged
and we call them up
and you're like, "I'm engaged,"
that they're gonna be like,
"Yes"?
Like, they're not gonna
be mad at you or me?
- They're not gonna be mad
at you or me.
100%.
- You think?
- Yes. No.
- You're, like, confident.
- I know
they're gonna come around.
End of story.
- Okay.
- It's probably not
gonna be overnight,
and I don't expect your parents
to, like, love me overnight...
- Mm-hmm.
- But I see you as the future.
There's just no reality here
where, like, they don't
get on board.
I see it so clearly with you
and I can't go home
without you at this point.
So they're gonna have
to get on board with that.
And they're gonna love you.
'Cause eventually
they're gonna see
the woman that I see,
and it'll be impossible not to.
You're so incredibly beautiful
and you match that
with being ambitious,
being smart, wanting a family,
wanting, you know, a career
and, like, all these things
that, like, I imagined
in, like, somebody
and it took forever and going
in front of the world stage
to find.
And my heart's a little bit
in my throat saying this,
but... I love you, Rachel.
I'm in love with you.
I love everything,
like, I find out about you,
and I feel like it's overdue,
but I'm so happy to say it.
I love you too.
I really do.
Oh, my God, like, it's been me
waiting for this declaration
for so long, and then
all of a sudden I hear it.
And it feels so amazing
to hear him say that.
And to say it back,
it's a huge moment in your life.
Like, everyone waits
for that moment.
- Oh, I get a date card.
- Tino did tell me
that if he loves me,
his family will come around,
and I think that answer
is good enough for me.
I would absolutely love to go,
if you want to.
- I would absolutely love to go.
- All I could do is
bring up my concerns
and moving forward,
hopefully with how he feels,
his family will
also come around.
They'd better.
Because I really do see Tino
at the end.
- I feel so amazing.
Oh, my God, this is huge.
What do you think?
- I love Rachel!
This is the best night ever.
- To hear that Rachel's in love
with me, it's indescribable.
I'm all about this girl.
I'm in love with her.
There's nothing else
to think about.
We're following the feeling,
and everything we do
reassures that we're right.
I really love Rachel.
- My last Overnight with Erich
was so special
and I really can
see us together,
but today is my Overnight date
with Johnny,
and I'm so excited.
I know we're gonna have
a ton of fun.
Whoa!
He really gets me
in a way that I never,
ever had a man get me before.
- So what are we gonna do?
- We're going on a boat.
- A sailboat?
- Yeah.
Yes.
I'm hoping today
just brings us together
and that we can see ourselves
one step closer
to an engagement.
Have you been on one of these?
- No, I actually have not.
- Really?
- I used to have a Hobie Cat.
I don't know if that's,
like, the same thing.
- Oh, me too.
It's like a hamster.
What?
What are you talking about?
- A boat.
- An animal?
- No.
Today's huge. I'm so excited.
I cannot believe
that I'm here with Gabby.
I mean, every time we hang out,
it kind or progresses
and builds a bigger foundation.
- Just nice being here.
- No, it's cool.
Just as long
as you're here, I'm good.
I don't care what we do.
- Great.
- It's all good.
She's opened me up and made me
feel confident about myself
in ways that I have
never felt confident.
And then, you know,
we hit Hometowns
and she met the family.
I think that kind of just
catapulted us further.
- Cheers.
- Can we cheers?
- Yeah.
To us in Mexico.
- Mexico. Hell yeah.
Gabby is the dopest girl
I think I've ever hung with.
You have beauty, you have
brains, you have a good time,
you have, like, my person.
- It's, like, so crazy.
I feel like we've seen so much
of the world together.
- Yes, we actually have.
Yeah, it's been wild.
- Yeah. I know.
Like, starting in LA,
and then Europe,
and then your hometown,
and now Mexico.
- Yeah.
- You're so easy to be with,
and I feel like I can be
my most ridiculous self
with you.
- 100%.
- Yeah?
- You can be whatever you want.
- I know.
- It's been moments with you,
so it's just been,
like, amazing moments that I'm,
like, trying to just take in.
- Me too.
- Like, this is a moment
right now.
Everything's a moment, so...
- It's so crazy, but it's like,
I can't believe that we're here.
The mansion feels like
yesterday and years ago.
- And years ago.
It went by so quick,
but then again,
I feel like it's never ending,
like it's, like, forever.
Like I'm stuck here.
- Yay, roses!
Whoa!
- I got another one.
- What happened?
- No, but it does
feel like that.
It feels like forever ago,
but yesterday too.
- I feel like every time
we're together,
I think I see a new side
of you, which is nice.
Even I feel like you're getting
more comfortable with me still.
I mean, like...
- I'm trying to.
- How are you?
Like, what you feel really.
- What? You don't think I...
- No, I... no, I feel like
you're comfortable around me.
- Oh, for sure.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, but still I feel like...
Not a whole lot,
but still, like, gotta get
somewhat more comfortable,
I don't know.
- Yeah, no, absolutely.
I think there's always gonna be
some of that, for sure.
- I think
you've opened up, too, a lot,
even just from the first time.
- Yeah.
- 100% yeah.
- Whenever I'm with Johnny,
it is so easy and effortless.
Being with him feels so natural.
He's really taught me
to trust people.
- Should we do this?
- And has led me to the point
where I truly can see a life
together outside of this.
I'm so hopeful
about a future with him.
There is something
about being from Colorado
that whenever I feel
cold things on my feet,
I get thirsty.
That's strange.
- That sounds like
a you problem.
Whoa, this is for us?
- Oh, my God.
- Wow.
- But before I move
into an Overnight with him,
I need to know that he can
see a future with me as well.
I feel like you have been
so open with me right away.
It's like you've taken it
upon yourself
to take a chance, but...
- Definitely don't open up
that quick,
so I never talk
about how I feel.
Like I do, but it takes a while,
and, like, I think you helped
me evolve in a way.
I've said it before,
but you make me
want to be a better man.
- Well, I think you, like,
always had it in yourself
and you were just ready,
you know?
- Just needed that person.
- Yeah.
I think, like, you were,
seems like,
at the point in your life
where you were ready to, like,
take a leap of faith too.
- For sure.
Yeah, I feel like I was
just kind of feeling stuck too
and just kind of needed
to go in a way,
and this was, like,
huge in that process.
And a lot of it is
to thank you for, so...
- Like I said before,
I really didn't know
what I was gonna get
coming into this.
And, like, much like
you've grown here,
I think so have I.
And I have, like, grown
into really wanting
something, you know.
- Yeah.
- It is, like, time
to make a relationship,
like, my full priority.
I'm just, like, at a place
where it is what I want
and, like, need almost.
- I, like...
It's a hard thing
to think about.
It's such a quick process,
and that's... like, I don't know.
Like, I know
how I was feeling about you.
I'm so into you.
- Yeah.
- And I just...
The end result scares me.
I also didn't know I'd be here
on the beach with you
and falling in love
with you, so...
- Hearing you say
how you feel about me,
like, means the world
no matter what.
And, like, these weeks
have been so fast,
and, like, we're, like,
ending, you know,
like, a week
or a little over a week.
So I don't know.
Kind of... like, what do you...
Like...
I am at a place in my life
where I do feel like, you know,
I'm, like, ready to be engaged.
- I mean,
are you asking where I feel
about that whole thing
'cause we have a week left?
- No pressure.
- Yeah.
- That's a hard thing
to think about.
It's like a battle in my head.
I don't know, like,
what to think or what to do.
And, like,
you deserve everything.
And you should get
everything you want, so...
- You too.
- Where do I stand in that?
And that's, like,
such a hard thing to decide.
- I'm just, like,
at a place, like,
I am... like, I'm ready.
- I told you, like,
I can see myself
falling in love with you.
- Yeah.
- I can see me and you
being together,
but it's more so just me
bringing 100% to the table
and if I'm ready to bring 100%,
and if I'm not,
do I drag you through that?
- Yeah.
Just give me a second.
It seems like
he's not able to commit.
It's just really frustrating.
Because I am so ready
at this point
to leave here engaged
with someone
who is committed to me.
But what if he feels like he
can't or shouldn't be with me?
- I am feeling really frustrated
because there is a part of me,
a big part of me,
that has asked to be loved
my whole life.
So having to ask Johnny about
his feelings really hurts.
I am terrified
that Johnny might tell me
that he can't get there.
But I don't want to step
into an Overnight
knowing that there's still big
questions being unanswered.
- It's all good?
- No.
You just have to, like,
be honest with yourself,
and me, 'cause it's not fair
to either of us,
you know, if we were at the end
and then having this talk.
- Life with you would be insane.
- Mm-hmm.
- You're exactly
the person that I'd want
to, like, fall in love with
and just be my person
forever, but...
But I just don't know
if I can get to an engagement
in the next week or so.
You know, it's not
that I don't like you.
It's not that I'm not
falling for you.
It's not that I can't
see myself with you.
It's just more so
just, like, it scares me.
And...
I don't know if I can
bring 100% to the table
and commit to that end result
if I'm not ready.
That's just me being
honest with you.
- No, I know, and, like...
- As much as I don't want
to tell you that either,
'cause as much as I want
to just hang out here
with you forever, I just...
- Yeah.
It's obviously
really hard to hear.
There was, like,
a big part of me
that hoped
it would be, you know, like, us
one way or another.
But I feel like
we're just... we want
two different things.
I think, like, if it was,
like, a different time
for both of us,
then we could be so, so great.
- You deserve the world.
You're an amazing person.
And you should get everything
you've ever wanted, so I...
- That's the hardest part
about relationships.
Honestly, like,
you want them to work,
you want them to work, but if,
like, timing isn't there,
we're at two different places,
like, you want to fix it,
but there's not anything to fix.
- So is this our goodbye?
- I think so.
- That's devastating.
- I know.
- My feelings are numb.
I don't know
how to feel right now.
I feel... like, I'm upset.
Gabby wants something
that I don't know
if I can give her
at this very moment.
It's not that I don't want to.
I would love to give that
to her,
but it's just something
I don't know how I can do
within the next week.
Thank you for everything.
- Mm.
Thank you for being honest.
- I'm just upset.
I don't want to say goodbye.
There goes my lady.
- Stop.
It feels like a little bit
of a punch in the gut
because it was a fear,
you know,
that I've had all along.
And now it's kind of
coming to fruition,
which is, I start to fall
for someone,
but they can't meet me where
I am or give me what I need.
And it's scary as hell.
Saying goodbye
to Johnny was hard,
but it's, like,
kind of meant to be.
Because as much as, like,
I don't want to say goodbye
to Johnny
and, like, I know he'll always
have a piece of me,
like, I know there's
something waiting for me
that's really great
with Erich and Jason.
I've been tired of fighting
for love for a long time,
and having it
right in front of my face
is, like, so enlightening,
in, like, the best way.
- This is obviously a big week.
- Yeah.
- One thing I do know
that is real
is the connection
between Gabby and I.
- Yeah.
- I feel like Erich and Jason
have been really able
to validate me
in a way that I didn't know,
like, I could ask for.
Like, it is just the feeling
of being loved
that trumps all.
- So do you feel like you're
falling in love with Gabby?
- Um, I mean, I would say,
yeah, not quite there just yet,
I would say.
But I have strong feelings
towards Gabby,
and, yeah, hopefully it turns
into something real
after this.
- I am ready for an engagement,
and it's not something
that I really planned for.
But I've seen myself progress
with Jason and Erich.
I didn't know
that I would get here.
that I could feel this way
in such a short amount of time,
but I'm hopeful
that I can leave here
with someone
that I want to spend
the rest of my life with.
- So you're at a point
right now where you don't
feel like you're ready
to get engaged to Gabby?
- Yeah.
- Do you think you could
get there
before this is all over?
- Right now, like, I'm just
kind of taking it day by day
and I want to be
as honest and upfront as I can
and I would never want
to hide anything from her.
You know.
- Yeah.
- I mean, truthfully, like,
it's hard... like, in two weeks,
like, it's hard
for me to see that.
Yeah, it's just, right now,
it's hard for me
to, like, get
to the point of engagement.
- Saying goodbye to Johnny
today was really difficult
and truly heartbreaking.
This is the hardest week,
definitely.
Now I really am placing
all my hopes
on what I'm feeling
from Erich and Jason.
But my heart is telling me
that they're both ready
for the commitment
to be together forever
and ready for an engagement.
Oh.
"I need to see you.
I'll be waiting on the bridge."
I hear a knock at the door
and there's a card.
I don't know
how to feel about this.
I have no idea
who wrote this note or why.
And I truly don't know
what to expect.
My mind's kind of spinning,
and I know I should go,
but I am a little scared.
- Hi.
I thought you were
gonna be my grandpa.
- Sorry to disappoint you.
- Oh, please.
You know, it's good to see you.
It always is.
How are you?
- I'm good.
I didn't have anything
to, like, tell you or anything,
I just wanted
to see you tonight.
I was like, "I need
to figure this out."
I do have one thing
I want to tell you.
You know our last date?
Like, the day part was amazing.
The night part, like,
I couldn't imagine that
going any better.
And I'm, like, now sitting here
picturing the girl
that, like, I'm in love with
doing that with somebody else.
Like, that kind of crushes me.
And this is not gonna be easy,
but I just want to tell you
how I feel because...
I think I'm having
a really hard time.
Didn't plan
on telling you anything,
but I just want to tell you
where I'm coming from.
I do want to say that.
- Yeah.
I know.
- This is supposed
to be positive.
- Is it?
- Yes.
This is a positive, seeing you.
- Yeah.
- This was not my intention
to put you on the spot
or anything.
I just wanted to tell you
how I feel, that's all.
- I think, like, in the spirit
of being honest,
like, we talked about this
off-camera.
- What do you mean?
- Like, I feel like
we were able to have,
like, an honest conversation
about it in Fantasy Suites.
So you brought me here
to tell me it again?
- No, this is not why
I brought you here at all.
I'm...
- I don't know.
- I mean, you do know.
- I feel
so frustrated right now.
Erich expressed to me
in the Fantasy Suite
that this week feels
like I'm cheating,
and now I feel like we're
rehashing the conversation
and I'm being pressured.
Him being like,
"I don't you to have
what we have
with somebody else,"
well, that's, like,
not for you to say.
You're here knowing that I could
have it with somebody else.
- I mean, I don't know
what's happened this week,
but, like, I can't just,
like, pretend like
I'm cool with everything and...
- I don't know, like,
what you want to me to say
or, like, if you feel
like I need
to prove something to you.
Because I think, like,
I'm always as, like, honest
and open as I can be.
And if you want to get into it,
we can get into it now.
- I really don't.
I didn't want to put
anything on you.
And I'm sorry...
This is not the way
I thought this was gonna go.
- Like, I know
where your heart is
and, like, I know, like,
what you're trying to say,
but, like, we did have
this conversation
when it was just you and I,
and, like, now I can talk
to you about it,
but then I feel like
I would be defending myself.
- That's not the point at all.
It was literally
just to see you.
But now that I see you,
I'm like,
I don't want to let you go.
- I don't know.
It just doesn't feel good
right now.
Why do I always
have to defend myself?
It's like, why don't you trust
what we have?
- It was not my intention
to, like,
have any sort of ultimatum
or anything like that,
but I need you to know
how I feel
because I can't just, like,
go through this whole week
being like, everything's fine.
- I feel like he was testing me.
And that's, like,
not something you do
to someone that you love.
Maybe he's not gonna
be my guy after all.
I'm starting to question it.
And I'm terrified
'cause what if I realize
that Jason isn't my guy either?
Now it's right
in front of my face,
my person might not be here.
'Cause it seems like the people
that I want to love me never do.
It's just, like,
all coming crashing down,
and I hope this doesn't end up
in a big, fat dumpster fire.
But right now, this feels
like the end for me.
I feel like I have, like,
walls and barriers and...
I don't know.
- Tomorrow night
on "The Bachelorette"...
- I'm having a lot
of anxiety this week.
I do have those fears
of leaving here alone.
- After Fantasy Suite,
everything took, like, a 180.
I felt blindsided.
That was the last thing
I could've ever expected.
- I don't necessarily know
where we are.
To feel this strong
about somebody and know
that, like, you could lose
that person?
That's a horrible feeling.
- This whole time
has been really hard.
It does take
kind of the right person
to know how to love me.
- I don't fully feel like
I know who you are.
- Gabby will not be joining you.
You're gonna be
the only Bachelorette here.
- I don't know
what it is about me
that's so hard to love.
Am I too broken
for anyone to love?
- It all continues
tomorrow night.
- I was so excited
for this week,
but I have been, like,
dreading this week.
- Yeah.
I'm just terrified
that it's gonna...
- We have a friend!
Oh, my God,
he's actually fearless.
- I don't want him
to bite my ankles.
- Should we gave it champagne?
- Oh, my God, he's gonna jump.
- Oh, there he goes.
I don't know.
It's something I think
that we'll have to see,
like, if conversation comes up.
Personally, like,
my conversation with Erich
is gonna look
completely different
than my conversation with Jason.
That's gonna look different
than with Johnny.
- I agree.
- Yeah, so it's like...
- Whoa!
That is...
- Oh, it likes pineapple!
He jumped so high!
- Positive reinforcement.
That thing is brave as hell.
He had it right in his mouth.
- Literally, they're like dogs.
It's so happy with himself.
Look, it's gonna go take a nap.
- It's like...
- Yeah, literally licking
his chops.
>>>>oakislandtk
www.opensubtitles.org