- Previously
on "The Bachelorette"...
- My heart's a little bit
in my throat saying this,
but I love you, Rachel.
- It was love in paradise...
- Don't forget
I'm falling in love with you.
- I'm in love with you too.
- Whoo!
- Until it wasn't.
- So is this our goodbye?
- I think so.
As much as like I don't
wanna say goodbye to Johnny,
I know there's
something waiting for me
that's really great.
- Right now it's hard
for me to like get
to the point of engagement.
- I'm not like
a super jealous person,
but I'm like picturing
a girl that like
I'm in love with
doing that with somebody else.
Like, that kinda crushes me.
- So you brought me here
to tell me it again.
No, no.
- And tonight...
- I'm scared that
I could leave here alone.
Erich up last night.
I felt like
I was being almost pressured
into a decision.
Ah!
But with Jason, I never
have to defend myself.
- To feel this strongly
about somebody
and know that you can lose
that person,
that's a horrible feeling.
- Zach is everything
that I want in a partner.
- We did have a big night.
Proposal is right
around this corner.
- For sure.
I'm having a lot of anxiety.
- After Fantasy Suite,
everything took a 180.
I felt blindsided.
That was the last thing you
could have ever expected.
- Tonight, like I wanna be
fully honest and transparent.
- Gabby will not be joining you.
You're the only Bachelorette
here.
- Is it me?
What is it about me
that's so hard to love?
- I'm scared.
You know,
I'm feeling really nervous.
Gabby walked away, and that
could be the end of it.
I, you know,
brought up something
that we had talked about
in confidence and in privacy.
At this point, there are
other people involved,
and she still has more,
you know, Fantasy Suite dates.
You know, I kinda lost trust
in us and her.
It got really in my head,
and I wish I didn't.
I up.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
I just sometimes need a second.
And I don't like wanna
be upset like wrongfully.
So I think 'cause we had talked
about it multiple times
just us two,
I didn't know if you truly
did want me to say something.
No., no.
Listen, the reality is
I am in love with you,
and I'm terrified of losing you.
So I up an opportunity
and this was just
supposed to be
like positive and just us
like to sneak in a moment.
- Yeah.
- 'Cause I'm scared.
- I think your heart
is in the right place,
but I don't...
I've like worked my ass off
for there to be like no question
on making good decisions.
- It came from
a moment of insecurity
and like these
unjustified doubts.
And then I'm like,
what the is going on?
Like...
But every time I see you,
it's like, all right.
- Yeah.
- I'm sorry.
I don't wanna see you sad.
- No, it's okay.
- I up a...
- It could have been
a good moment,
and I'm really sorry.
I just don't wanna lose you
at this point.
- So much has happened
this week,
but it's just like crazy.
And like, my head's everywhere.
It all started with my
overnight date.
Johnny and I decided that this
wasn't the right time with us.
I knew that he can't give me
what I deserve,
and it was time to say goodbye.
During our overnight,
Erich and I's relationship
has grown really strong.
A couple days ago,
leaving our morning together,
I felt so good about him,
like he really
could be the one for me.
But then he
all of that up last night.
Erich was telling me
how much he loved me
and how hard it is for him,
especially this week,
because this week
felt like cheating to him.
And I know that,
because in Fantasy Suites,
when it was just him and I,
we had the same exact
conversation.
And going through all those
emotions multiple times
is exhausting.
My first gut reaction was,
why are we rehashing this now?
- Mm-hmm.
- We had already
talked about it.
Like, when it was
just me and you,
wasn't that enough,
and didn't that mean more?
- You sort of have that
dropped on you
at a moment
you weren't expecting it.
- Right. It's unfair to me.
I didn't get any sleep.
I was still so confused,
and I felt so hurt.
And I don't think
I really understood
where he was coming from, so...
- I'm sorry, you know,
that happened.
I just know you guys shared
a lot of really special
moments together.
- Yeah.
I was definitely
disappointed 'cause
I felt like I was being almost
pressured into a decision.
And I know myself,
I just need a lot of space
in order to be able to think.
Um... oh.
I don't wanna cry.
But I think like this whole time
it has been just really hard
because I've wanted
to make a right decision,
like for myself and for them.
And like, Erich and I have
like gone through so much.
We don't have the best way
of communicating,
but he has like always
fought for me.
And I think I've always
fought for him.
Erich and I,
we've always struggled
with this miscommunication,
but I think
we're also
very different people.
I'm mad at him
because I still have
my overnight date with Jason.
I felt like
I was being pressured.
So I'm like, this is...
This is it, you know.
We're not meant to be.
Like I knew
it was too good to be true.
- It's not easy.
So you can see
how you could feel that way.
- Yeah.
I have to be honest with myself.
And if it's my decision
to be with Erich, it's mine.
to be with Jason,
like, it's nobody else.
I want this to be my decision.
- I'm around if you need me.
- Okay.
Sounds good.
- All right, Gabby.
We'll see ya.
- Okay.
I don't really know like where
to go from here or what to do,
but I know I just have to
continue to follow my heart.
Today is my overnight date
with Jason.
I do just wanna
like soak up these moments
we have with each other.
I am falling in love with him,
and this overnight date
is so important.
I'm hoping that it
just brings us together
and that we can see ourselves
one step closer
to an engagement.
I know there's no question
to his intentions.
- That's a big day for us.
I am here for Gabby.
When I'm with her, like I
just have an amazing time
and like we get each other
on like a deeper level too.
I'm just kind of reflecting
on this past Hometown Date.
I started feeling
that I'm not at a place
where I'm ready to get engaged.
I'm doing my best to stay true
to myself, and just for me,
it just doesn't feel right.
I need to tell Gabby
where I stand
and be honest with her.
I'm nervous.
I'm stressed out.
I have no idea
how she's gonna react.
- This week has been pretty
hard up until this point.
But today I get to focus on
the overnight date with Jason.
I really can't wait to see him.
- Hey.
- I'm falling in love
with Jason,
and I believe
he feels the same way,
but he hasn't been able
to tell me how he feels.
Hi.
I've been looking forward
to this day,
'cause I know
he's such a private person.
- It's so good to see you.
- You too.
- There's an option,
you know, for an overnight,
where we can just get
really private time
and have some intimacy
to see if we're truly
as compatible as I think we are.
Our whole relationship
could change tonight.
Okay, well, welcome to Mexico.
It's so good to see you.
- You too.
- It's been so long.
- It's crazy.
It feels like a year.
- I know.
- So what do we do?
Go to
the all-you-can-eat buffet?
Actually, yeah.
Well, no. There is something.
And um, it's something
I'm really good at
that you maybe
have never done before,
but I'm excited for us
to learn and grow together.
- What is it?
- So do you wanna see?
- Yeah. Let's go.
- Okay, we'll see.
I'm nervous.
- Don't be nervous.
No.
We're playing tennis.
Oh, God.
- I thought we were
gonna be dancing.
- No, no.
- I was ready to dance
or something...
- I know. I sold it.
- "I'm good at it."
- So Jason and I
are playing tennis today,
which is something
that he loves.
He played tennis in college,
and I wanna be able to share
all of the passions
that my partner has.
So I am excited for him
to like teach me
and see him in his element.
I did it.
You missed it.
- No, we're supposed
to go back and forth.
- That was good.
Oh! There you go.
- Oh, my God.
I'm so good.
- Getting on the tennis court
with Gabby was amazing.
And I kinda was just
in the moment,
and she was good.
She was actually like a natural.
- Do you think I'm good?
- I think you're like
the best player I've ever seen.
No!
I want him to actually hit me
in my butt with the racket.
So hot.
We'll see.
Teach me how to serve.
That's all I care about.
- I'll teach you how to serve.
- Yeah.
Why do you have so many balls?
- 'Cause you're gonna need them.
Let's go to that side though.
The sun.
What? What?
- Jason and I are just
like so easy together.
You know, we're just doing
something kind of mundane,
like tennis, but somehow
we make it so fun.
I feel like I never
have to explain myself.
I can just like be
whoever I wanna be.
- Get low.
Like this.
- I can't stay low.
- No, that's it. Right there.
I didn't say to be a crab.
I said get low.
- I think like we
just get each other
and accept each other
for who we are.
- Damn.
- That was fast.
- That was actually good.
That was like 220.
220 miles per hour.
Yeah. I think today
was just like kind of
what I needed
just like to feel...
feel at home a little bit.
We should do target practice.
- Yeah. What's that?
- We have to hit
the water bottle.
- Okay.
Let me get up here.
- Okay. Fine.
- I did it!
- Oh. What?
I had more fun today
than I could have imagined.
It just felt special.
If there was any date
I could ask for,
today was what I would want.
Honestly, I think
you're ready to go pro.
You're amazing.
But yeah,
in the back of my mind,
there is this
big conversation tonight
about the future for us
outside of this.
At the end of the day,
like, I might not be having
the same path
as some of the other guys,
but I know
what feels good to me,
and seems like we're both
feeling good.
- I'm dying.
Should we change into our
swimsuits and go to the pool?
Please. Please.
- Do we get in?
- Yes.
Let's go.
Are we cannonballing?
- Yeah, sure.
- Yeah. Ready?
- Yeah.
- All right, let's go.
- It's not very deep!
Ah!
- I can't stop thinking
about Gabby.
The last time,
you know, I saw her,
um, I let my insecurities
kinda get the best of me.
Ah, you're so strong!
- I brought up
her other Fantasy Suites,
and she was upset.
Makes me think like I don't
necessarily know where we are.
Ultimately, at the end
of the day, like
my biggest fear
is like losing her now, so...
Like this week, I know
when I'm just by myself,
she is on a date
with somebody else
and like has a relationship
with somebody else.
I know how special our date
was, and for her to experience
that with somebody else now
at this point
just feels like weird.
Okay. Okay.
Okay! Ah!
- This has been
like by far the hardest week,
because I have told her
how I feel truly.
So now to feel this strongly
about somebody
and know that like you
can lose that person,
that's a horrible feeling.
How was it
talking to my mom and...
- She was like, so nice.
We got along easy.
I told her, I don't know,
things I saw in you,
and like how good you were
and are with me.
- I was telling her how like
genuine and real you are.
And she was like, "No, I
can tell, like instantly."
- Oh, that's good.
- Like she's...
I think
she's your number one fan.
- Aw!
- Oh, my God, that means a lot.
When you were outside,
we were like talking
about touching up our roots
and stuff.
Like that's how
I know it's real.
- Yeah.
- Like she gets me.
- But no, this is so much fun.
- I did have fun.
- I just like being with you.
- Yeah.
That's what I said too.
Like every time I'm with you,
it's just like,
no matter what we do, it's fun.
Yeah. It's a strange place,
but when I'm with you,
it feels normal.
That's what I think.
- Yeah.
- You know, I can't
wait for these dates.
It's the best.
- I know, me either.
Every time I see you,
it's like no time has passed.
Today has been such a great day.
And being with him
just really feels
like completely
effortless in every sense.
I think it has really
exceeded all my expectations.
I know we have fun together,
but this is like more than fun.
It's really just comfort.
You're so salty.
- You're salty.
I am truly falling
in love with him.
Going into dinner tonight,
I'm hoping that Jason and I
can talk more
about our feelings.
I know my feelings
are really strong,
and I can definitely see him
at the end of this with me.
After today, I just know
it's gonna work for us.
- Going into dinner
with Jason tonight,
I'm really excited.
I think today
I really didn't know
where my head was gonna be at,
but like Jason just gets it.
I can see myself
engaged to Jason.
I think that we would
really balance each other.
I mean, he really is
everything I've ever wanted.
It's so nice out tonight.
- That's what's so good here.
Today was definitely amazing.
Like, there's real
feelings here.
I think like each date
that we have together
deepens my feelings for Gabby.
I feel like we're heading
in the right direction.
- This is us.
- I know.
This is actually nice.
But I haven't really
been able to like
put it all out on the table
so that she knows
exactly where I stand.
- Thank you.
- I just wanna be
up-front with her
and let her know that I'm
not ready to get engaged.
Being authentic
and transparent with Gabby
is all I wanna do.
And yeah, tonight I think will
be the first time that like
I can really share where I'm at.
- Thank you for today.
- Oh, thank you. It was fun.
- It was such a good day.
- Cheers.
I don't know.
Like, I'm just kind of curious
what she's gonna say
and, um, how she'll take it.
Like, hopefully...
Hopefully well.
Yeah, today was... it was fun.
Like I was... first day that like
felt like totally normal
and like
a real day outside of this.
- Yeah.
- I felt like I was like
fully present the entire time
and like not thinking about
like everything going on
and it just felt good, so...
- No, yeah. Me too.
I feel like we can
kind of do anything,
but today was like so easy.
- Yeah. Um, I think it's...
Yeah, it's never... it's never
been easy for me here, but...
- Yeah. No, totally.
How has your time been
like after seeing your family?
And it's like a weird
transition, I feel.
- Yeah.
Seeing my family was...
It was great, you know.
But it's such a short time
to see them
and then you obviously
wanna like keep that going,
but then you come back
here and like...
It's kind of like a tease.
- Yeah.
- And then like I came here
and like was spending
like a week just like...
- By yourself.
- Kind of by myself.
- Yeah, I know.
- And just like wanting to
like... looking forward to today.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, this...
I think I've kind of told you
how like crazy
and weird this has been for me,
but like,
it actually has like...
It's been so challenging
in so many ways but, um...
- I think it just speaks a lot
about like your character
and that you do know
yourself and like it's okay
to be uncomfortable here.
And I'm so happy
you're still here.
And it means like so much to me.
- Honestly, this whole time
I've just tried to focus
on you and like me and you.
And it's kinda all that matters
to me, but, uh...
Yeah, I think obviously tonight,
like I wanted to talk to you
kind of just like
how I'm feeling and stuff
and I wanna be fully honest
and transparent
'cause that's kind of like
what I have wanted to do
this entire time.
And, um, you know, obviously
I do know that I'm into you
and like I... when I'm with you,
I feel, um,
like I'm having
some of the best days ever.
And I know like
what the expectation of this is
for, you know, a lot of people,
is like being engaged
and like being fully in love
and like...
- Yeah.
- To be like completely
transparent and honest,
I-I don't think
I'm fully there yet.
Um, I think it's
because in this environment,
like it's like constantly
in my head,
like what's real,
what's not real?
I'm like... I'm like questioning
so many things.
Yeah, I just... I don't
think in another seven days
I'll be ready for... for that.
Like, it's just not something
like in my heart
that feels right.
And I just wanna be
like fully transparent
and let you know how I feel.
- I know... honestly, like
I know how hard it is for you.
And I know it's like
a big expectation and...
but I don't also know,
like if you're,
I guess, at a place in your life
where you can see me
like with you at all
in the future
or like what?
- It's so hard for me
to like see that right now
within this bubble
because like I feel like
you don't even know who I am
completely.
And like I don't fully feel
like I know who you are.
Yeah, I would love to kind of
like hear how you feel too.
- Yeah.
Um, I think obviously, like...
I think... yeah, I think there's
honestly like a part of you
that has to decide whether,
um, you're like able
to believe in kind of this
like hopeless romanticism.
- For me, I'm more of a realist.
I don't think it's like
this is not real,
but like, it's been hard for me
to like feel at ease
with cameras
and microphones and stuff.
But yeah.
- Yeah, I know.
I think it's just like hard
'cause if you kind of feel
like you don't really know me,
how can you like really
make a promise?
Like...
- Yeah.
He was always someone
I saw myself with,
from the very beginning.
So to wait this long
to hear where he's at,
like definitely hurts.
It's just like...
I guess that there was
a piece of me that wanted him
to play along for like
just a second,
but he can't.
I just like knew
it was gonna happen.
Like I have to be honest
with myself, you know.
Maybe it just is,
you know, a love
that's not destined
to be together.
- Tonight at dinner, a lot
of things were said to me.
Jason said he's highly
uncomfortable here.
And he said that he's
not ready for a proposal.
It would've been good
to know before now.
Unlike, you know, other people
who can kind of
be themselves fully,
like he can't.
And it's a huge disadvantage
for him,
and I don't know
like why we're here
together if it's that hard.
But this is where we're
at, so I don't know.
- I just feel upset.
I'm just trying
to stay true to myself
and like it's obvious she was
upset about what I told her.
- Yeah. Are you okay?
- I don't... I don't know.
- I definitely don't wanna
like just walk away from this.
Like I truly feel like a unique
connection to her and like,
I just wanna be sure
she knows how I feel.
This is truly, I can't tell you
how challenging
this has been for me.
Like I was about to go home.
Like you are the reason
I stayed.
Like I'm literally here
for you, and I'm serious.
Like, I wouldn't be here
if you weren't here.
Yeah, today was like
a really special day
that I truly felt like
was just a big step
in our relationship
and something
that I think we can
really build on.
And I'm excited for that if
I can get the chance, so...
- I don't know.
There's just like
a part of me that's like,
are we like pulling at strings
kinda?
- No. I think like,
I totally see us getting
to a point like in real life,
like where we can
spend time together.
- I just don't know.
I don't know.
- Like, I truly feel like
a unique connection to you
that I haven't in a while
and like, when I'm with you,
like, I do feel good
about this, and like
I see that as something special
that could turn into
like a serious relationship.
And like, hopefully,
that by the end of this,
like that's where we're at.
And I truly care about you too
and like you truly
like mean a lot to me, yeah.
I see, like in you,
like somebody that kind of
just gets it.
- I'm feeling conflicted.
I think now
I have to decide like,
whether it's worth
moving forward or not.
Jason did tell me like
he can see a future with me.
I don't wanna say goodbye to him
because I'm not ready
'cause I know
what's in front of me
is so precious.
Are you okay?
- Yeah.
I don't know.
I truly just wanna know
like what you think
'cause like I do wanna
be on like the same page.
- I don't... I mean,
maybe I like appeared upset
because I do really care
for you and I didn't know
if that was maybe it for us.
Like I wasn't ready to like
say goodbye in that moment.
Then after talking to you more,
I don't think it was ever
for me like,
"He doesn't like
believe in me."
- I do really care
about you too.
And like I think
we do have like a really
solid foundation that
could build into something
outside of this.
I think being off camera
and like being,
you know, private in privacy
will help me like understand
like the situation
and like maybe
I can like hear you better
and like you can hear me better.
- I agree.
Like we do just need tonight.
Yeah.
- And it's just like
a night unlike any other
that you can truly just like
share things with each other
and really get
to know each other
in a way that isn't really
possible otherwise here, so...
- Do you want to like
spend the rest of the night
kind of trying
to figure this out?
Maybe.
- Yeah. I think that is...
All I want is just
like time to spend
with you that we can truly get
to know each other and um...
Yeah, in like
an intimate, private way.
That would be
the best thing ever, so...
- Me too.
Tonight, I do really wanna do
an overnight with him.
I know one night
can change everything,
so as much as everything is
working against us right now,
like what if we come out on top?
Then like nothing
could ever take us down.
This is nice.
I've never met anyone like him
and I might not
meet anyone like him again.
And I just still have
to figure it out.
- Cheers to this journey.
And I'm grateful for you
for staying true to yourself.
And I'm just trying
to stay true to myself too.
And I think that's all we can
ask from each other.
- Cheers.
- Tonight we can truly share
our feelings with each other.
And then who knows what can
happen like the next day
and how things might change?
No, I know it like
hasn't been easy for you,
but we owe it to ourselves
to try and see it through
as much as we can.
A future with Jason
would be full of surprises.
He's so sensitive.
He's so warm.
I could tell just by
the way he looks at me
that he really cares about me.
He's especially guarded.
But days and nights
feel like years here.
One conversation
with Jason really
could change everything.
- Waking up,
I'm hurt and I'm devastated.
Last night with Jason,
once we got behind closed doors,
we were talking in circles
and couldn't agree
on like how things were gonna go
and if we needed more time.
And honestly, I was like
running out of patience.
I was like, "Maybe
it's just not meant to be."
And then he was like,
"Yeah, definitely."
Like when were you gonna
tell me that?
So, you know, I wanted to leave
and give it space.
Right before
I walked out the door,
he was like,
"Basically like this is it."
And as much as it hurts,
I know that I need
to say goodbye to Jason.
You know, I'm ready
for somebody to love me
the way that I love them.
Hi.
- Hi.
- Um, I think overall,
just like waking up
this morning,
I think my mind's
just kind of spinning.
Like really like,
what we were doing,
I guess, all of these weeks,
'cause you were willing
to be here and participate.
So I took that as like
you did at least
see it going somewhere
week after week.
But then last night it was
like, you're questioning,
you know, if this is real
and like you can't
see me in the outside world.
- Um, yeah.
It was... yeah,
incredibly tough for me.
And I truly needed that time
for me to realize like
this wasn't gonna work for us.
Um, yeah, I'm sorry.
I genuinely want
the best for you
and think you're an amazing
person, but I-I-I'm...
I'm really sorry.
- You... like, you honestly like
don't have to apologize
or say things like you think
I'm an amazing person
'cause it doesn't like...
Like lessen the blow, I guess.
I wanna be with someone
and with someone
who's ready to be with me
and no questions asked,
and that's not us.
So like,
you don't have to say sorry.
- Okay.
- I get it.
- Yeah. I don't know.
I was just trying...
Fighting for it
and trying to like see...
- I don't know if like you
were really fighting though.
I think I was and you were
like following my lead.
It's like, I think you're
like so terrified to hurt me.
You've been treading so lightly,
but it's like
you knew how you feel
and like couldn't tell me.
- And I'm sorry like
that it happened like that,
but I got that clarity
when we were up there.
- It's okay.
You don't... like really,
I'm not looking
for you to apologize.
Like I truly
just want you to realize,
you know, I've been led on.
- Yeah.
- So... but, um...
Yeah. I-I don't think
I have really anything else
left to say.
I think that's it.
- Yeah.
- Yeah. Okay.
It's like I feel so stupid.
I thought I knew him,
but like, I really don't.
I've tried so hard to not be
reckless with other people,
and he was reckless with me.
He never loved me.
So what were we doing?
It's not even that he
didn't want an engagement.
He didn't want me.
How do you just keep trusting?
Johnny also doesn't want me.
Is it me?
I just don't know
what it is about me
that's so hard to love.
I'm terrified.
Like, what if Erich decides
I'm not for him?
Am I too broken
for anyone to love?
It does take the right person
to know how to love me,
and they might not be here.
- It feels really exciting to be
at this point in my journey.
So far, my overnight week
has been a dream.
It is so gorgeous
here in Mexico,
and I'm so close
to an engagement.
It's incredible.
Having this uninterrupted time
is just really huge for me
to gain clarity
on who I wanna spend
the rest of my life with.
There was Aven,
who was my first overnight
of this week.
I think it went so well.
It was a good night.
- It was a great night.
- I am falling in love with you.
- I'm falling in love with you
deeper.
- We were really able to get
to know each other deeper
and see that we have
a great connection.
- This is so rad.
- And then my next overnight
with Tino was so perfect.
- My heart's a little bit
in my throat saying this,
but I love you, Rachel.
- I love you too.
I really do.
Felt so amazing to hear him
say he's in love with me,
and to say it back.
I'm excited
to have my last overnight date
with Zach today.
We had such a great Hometown.
He told me he was
in love with me,
and I'm falling
in love with him too.
So I am a little bit freaked out
because I have three
incredible guys,
and in ten days,
there's gonna be one.
Hi.
- Hello.
- How are you doing?
So hopefully I can put
my nerves aside today
and have an amazing day
with Zach.
- You look beautiful.
- How are you?
How are you? Oh.
- Hi.
- Good to see you.
Welcome to Puerto Morelos.
This is my first time in Mexico.
We're gonna have a really fun
day on the town and explore.
What do you say?
- I can't wait.
Let's do it.
- You ready?
- Let's do it.
- Zach is everything that I want
in a partner.
I don't even have a question,
"Would Zach get down
on one knee?"
or "Is Zach ready?"
'Cause I know he is.
We're gonna go in here.
- Interesting.
- The last time I saw Zach was
in Anaheim for his Hometown
and I definitely see myself
being a part of his family
for sure.
Cheers.
- Cheers.
- Because of all the families,
his family was honestly
the most welcoming.
You have to drink all.
Yes, fill the tequila.
- Okay.
- You have to kiss the tequila.
- Kiss it.
- Just a little.
- Just a little?
- Yes.
- So good.
Very good.
- Thank you.
- It's a pleasure.
- That's dangerous. Oh, yeah.
So you got to meet with
my dad, talk about planes.
- Mm-hmm.
We had the best time.
I feel like I fit in
perfectly in this family.
- You're welcome.
That was a fun day.
You survived it, you know.
- And your house
is so beautiful.
- Thank you.
- Truly your backyard
is like my dream backyard.
- It was, you know, like
the summer go-to hangout spot.
- I was gonna say
your house had to be.
I imagine your mom had
to make so many meals for all
of your friends growing up.
- So many.
So many pizzas
that have been ordered.
My dad just at the grill.
- Yeah.
Your mom seems like,
oh, my gosh,
just, she is such an angel.
So sweet.
And like the way
she talks about your dad.
They talk about each other
the exact same way.
- They're very much still
in love like the day they met.
- Aw, I love that.
- They just went
on like a however long
road trip together,
and my mom said,
you know, "Me and your father
"just were on a 20-day road trip
in an RV
and we didn't fight once."
And she's like, "We've been
married for almost 30 years."
And I was like,
"That's what I'm looking for."
- My parents have been
fighting the whole time.
- No.
- Well, not fighting,
but they like,
the way they communicate
is by like raising their voice.
- Gotcha. I don't think
I've ever raised my voice.
No one in my family
raises voices.
- Oh.
- I don't think
I've ever raised my voice
ever in an argument.
- Really?
You have such
a like striking voice.
- Booming.
- Booming. Yeah.
Can you try to speak
in a high-pitch voice?
Is this high enough for you?
- That was the worst thing
I ever heard.
- Isn't it?
When I'm with Rachel,
everything is
just so bright and fun and easy.
And that's
a pretty great feeling.
Oh, hot.
- It's kind of coastal grandma.
- We have, you know,
no like rhyme or reason
for anything we do or say
because we just get each other.
- Ooh, that could be us.
Could be a dead couple.
- We're just doing fun stuff,
which is
kind of how I operate.
What is that one?
- Ooh, that's a big one.
- You can eat it?
- You wanna try?
- What kind of a bug is that?
- Grasshopper.
- We have to eat the bug.
- Here, I got you.
Mmm.
I mean, there's no way it's...
These are good luck.
It tastes like a chip.
- Ooh.
- Mmm.
- I'm having an amazing time
with Rachel today.
I mean, everything you could
ever ask for in Mexico,
we're doing it.
- And now you're
gonna buy me a ring.
- I'm feeling confident
that the love
has just been growing.
Oh, oh.
- Oh.
- And that she can
without a doubt,
see a future with me
as a spouse.
'Cause I'm feeling it.
And I think she's feeling it.
But on the flip side...
- Hmm.
- The thought does
constantly creep up
like, oh, you know, there's
other relationships,
you know, being formed here.
That's not a fun
and easy thought.
- Hmm.
The reading was saying that
I'm worried about the past,
and to not worry about the past
because the future is positive.
And I feel like I've definitely
been worrying about the past
because of what happened
when I was in this position
last time.
The day Clayton told me
to go home,
I was just so heartbroken
and so blindsided.
And now I'm in a position
where someone can get hurt.
I love Mariachi.
- Zach has kind of
been killing it today.
We have a great time every
single time we're together.
And the relationship between
Zach and I is really powerful,
and he loves me
and wants to take care of me.
But with Tino and Aven,
I also have
such an incredible connection,
so I'm just struggling.
It's like a lot harder
than I ever thought.
And I think people can't
even begin to understand
how much stress I'm under,
because how do I even get
to a point emotionally
where I can break up
with any of these men
who are the most incredible
men I've ever met?
I'm very confused right now.
- Isn't this tree so pretty?
- This is so nice.
- I know.
- And it's breezy.
We kind of match too.
Yeah, got some style.
After today's date
and during today's date,
from what I could tell
from Rachel,
I like to think I'm the one
that's gonna be here at the end,
you know, proposing to her.
And I'm feeling
more than excited.
Wow.
- It's so beautiful.
- With Fantasy Suites, tonight
is just another opportunity
to build on the relationship
that we have,
where there are no cameras
and it is private.
And we can talk about
everything and anything.
I already see a future,
because I love this woman,
and I want to be with her
for the rest of my life.
Cheers to all the memories
you and I have shared
to this point.
- Mm-hmm.
- That's the fun,
the laughter, and the dancing
to Mariachi music.
So cheers to many more to come.
- Cheers.
Not to Mariachi.
- I truly had no idea
how to dance to that.
- I don't even know
if there's a way to.
- Exactly.
And then what'd you think
about the psychic?
- That's right.
The tarot card reader.
- Yeah.
- Well, that was
the first time I've
ever done something like that.
- Mm-hmm.
What'd you feel about it?
- I like what it said.
I don't know.
What did you think?
- Well, I actually wanted
to like talk to you about that.
I don't know
if today you noticed
I was a little bit off.
I hope you didn't.
But what she said was there was
a lot of like fear of the past
and a lot of like challenges.
And like right now, I really
feel like that is true.
- Yeah.
- I have struggled with
the feelings I felt last time
being like almost bleeding
into this week
and kind of tainting this week.
- Mm-hmm.
- No matter how happy
and how excited I am,
especially to have you here
and to be doing all this,
I think I do have those fears
of like still failure
and being blindsided
and leaving here alone,
because this is the point
in my own journey
where things started
to go really bad.
So like, I'm really just
trying my best to remember,
like she said,
that this isn't the past.
Like the psychic,
she literally said,
she's like,
"This isn't the past."
This is like
kind of a new journey.
And this is your future.
And you obviously make me feel
so safe.
And I'm so thankful that you
are here because, you know,
I do see a future with you.
- Well, I want you to know
that, you know,
you... you didn't show it
but it's okay if you did.
Because I couldn't imagine,
you know,
what you were going through
last year
with what Clayton had done.
And that was obviously
the worst thing a man can do.
And I just want you to know
that I don't wanna
ever put you in
an uncomfortable position.
I know you're feeling a lot
of anxiety from, you know,
the past and this,
and I don't wanna make that,
you know, heightened.
I wanna be there for you.
I wanna just enjoy
this time with you,
because I have these incredibly
strong feelings for you.
I'm in love with you,
and going into a night like this
where, you know, what's to come
is what excites me.
Obviously we all know
how things went down
with Clayton last season.
And the last thing I'd ever want
is for the woman
I love and care for
to feel like she's not being
watched out for and protected.
And so I want her to know
that she can always be,
you know, safe with me.
- I have something for you.
- Oh.
- Do you wanna read it?
- I would love to.
"Rachel and Zach,
I hope you enjoyed your day
"in Puerto Morelos.
"What could be better
than a little tequila
"and a glimpse into your future?
"And by the way,
you better have brought
some of that tequila back
for me."
"Should you choose to forgo
your individual rooms,
"please use this key
to spend the night together
in the Fantasy Suite. Jesse."
And here is the key.
- Yeah.
So what do you think?
- I think I would love
the opportunity
to spend the Fantasy Suite
with you tonight.
- Let's do it.
- I think after today's date,
I'm more than confident
Rachel and I's future
only looks bright.
It was incredible.
So tonight will be the night
Rachel and I will have answers.
- Wow.
- Oh, my gosh.
- Isn't this so pretty?
- Wow.
I'm in love with his woman.
And I want tonight to be
where we can talk
about the really important
stuff.
- Gosh.
- What a room.
- This is so beautiful.
- In the morning,
I'm expecting to feel
more in love
with future Mrs. Shallcross.
- And nothing coming out
of tonight can change that.
- Do you put limes on fruit?
They have some limes.
- I think so.
- Or should we
just eat the lime?
- Do you want that?
Oh, what's that, yogurt?
- I think.
Do you wanna drink it?
It's good for you.
- Cheers.
- Pretty strong.
Cheers.
Ah.
- That's some good... some
good cup of joe right there.
- Do you think it's good?
- Yeah.
- Really?
I mean, it's kinda bitter.
- I love it when you can
just taste the beans.
Like you just chewed them up?
I'm ready for bed.
I'm like so tired.
We didn't sleep, right?
We went to bed so late.
- So late.
I mean, we did have a big night.
- Mm-hmm.
- We talked about
a lot of things.
- Yeah.
It was like
a tough conversation, but...
- Mm-hmm.
- I'm glad you handled it well,
and hopefully it helped,
you know, gain clarity.
- Gain clarity.
- Clarity.
- You're feeling okay, honestly?
- It's a lot to digest.
- Yeah, for sure.
- 'Cause we did cover a lot
and, you know,
a proposal is right
around the corner.
- For sure.
- You know?
- But, you know,
I'm here for a reason and...
you know,
you're that reason, so...
- So I hope
we're on the same page.
- I think we are.
- Okay.
- Waking up this morning,
I'm feeling a little confused
after last night.
Fantasy Suite night with Rachel
was not the night I expected.
Initially in the
Fantasy Suite, you know,
I was feeling so sure.
We're having this amazing time
and we're one step closer
to engagement and we're having
that important conversation
about religion, politics,
all of that stuff.
And Rachel brought up
her fear that
maybe I'm not ready
for a commitment like marriage
at this early of an age.
- Well, I'll see you soon.
- Bye, beautiful.
- Bye.
- See you real soon.
- See you later.
- I'll see you soon.
- Bye.
And I was like,
"Don't worry about that.
I'm here for you."
But then she got really adamant.
Like, "Are you ready?
Like, are you sure?
Are you sure?"
And I was like...
"Are you making me
like second guess?"
That was a surprise.
It was like we
were two strangers.
I don't know what it could be,
but Rachel's concern
came outta nowhere.
And I think...
it's, to be honest,
And she was putting on a front.
That scares me.
That scares me a lot.
Jesse.
- Zach.
What's up, man?
- Can we talk?
- Uh, yeah, come on in.
Have a seat.
- Thank you.
- What's going on?
Are you okay?
Excuse me.
- Yeah.
Take your time, man.
- Things are obviously
taking a turn.
- Yeah.
To be honest, I'm
completely lost right now.
Every moment
that Rachel and I shared,
from the moment we met
to the moment
we had our one-on-ones,
I mean, everything
was just so easy, fun.
We clicked,
we had that connection
and things were immediately
different
when we were
in the Fantasy Suite.
Just completely the
way we were together,
you know, that feeling?
Took like a 180 and you know,
she was different,
I was different.
And the strange thing
for me was, you know,
when the cameras were away and
it was just her and I talking,
it felt like she was just like
not showing her true self.
It was very
unauthentic sometimes.
- Like, was it stuff
she was saying?
Or was it like the tone
of the conversation?
- Her major concern was my age.
And she wasn't sure
if I was ready to commit
because I was 25.
- And you're 25.
- And you're 26...
- She's 26.
- She's 26,
a couple months older.
And, uh, you know...
I kind of felt
blindsided by that.
You know, with proposals
around the corner,
that was the last thing
I could have ever expected.
Like I thought I saw my future,
you know, with this woman.
And...
when I was there, it was
hard to rationalize, you know,
what was going on.
And...
I was praying 'cause
I thought I had something.
I thought I saw
this future with her
and just to be completely
gut-punched
and not feeling it at all.
- Zach, I am so sorry,
because I know that's
not what you were expecting.
- You know, there were quite a
bit of times where I was like,
she could be my future wife.
And you know, you play it in
your head, and it's exciting.
And you think that, you know,
this week is like
the natural progression
to make that a reality.
And I learned it wasn't
and, uh, it's shock.
I'm sad 'cause there's
feelings for her,
but I need to figure this out
as soon as I can,
because we made it this far.
And how am I gonna recover
from this, you know?
And, I don't know.
I don't know how
to go about it right now.
Like, she met my family.
And they saw something.
- God, I'm sorry, man.
- It's all good.
It's okay.
- Sounds like you really
care a lot about her.
- Yeah.
- What do you wanna do?
- I need to tell her.
- And she needs
to see this side of you.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Tonight's the Rose Ceremony
and uh, it's tough because
Rachel, I know would love like...
I mean, I saw that woman
as my future wife.
But it's made me wonder like if
that's where her head's
at with me.
The only thing left to do
is to talk to Rachel.
I need answers to accept
the rose from Rachel.
- I'm gonna whisper this
once, and only once.
- I'm overwhelmed.
Going into this Rose Ceremony,
I'm ready to be done,
especially after overnights.
Erich is the only man
I have left.
I said goodbye
to Jason and Johnny.
I'm still kind of upset and sad
and just processing
exactly what happened
and how it affected me.
And now it's right
in front of my face,
is my person might not be here.
Not because
I don't want them to be.
Of course I do.
I want to be loved for who I am
and I know I just have to
continue to follow my heart,
but now more than ever,
I'm scared that
I could leave here alone.
- I don't have any idea how
the Rose Ceremony's gonna go.
All I know is that
my feelings towards Rachel
haven't changed.
I definitely, you know,
I'm falling in love with her.
I love her as a person.
I love the way
that she makes me feel.
And I wanna be with her.
I see myself with her
in the future.
Starting life together,
getting married,
having kids and starting
a family, all of that stuff.
I see that with her.
Not getting a rose
would be really hard.
It's her not seeing
a future with me
and seeing a future
with two other people.
And like, I really
do care for her a lot
and I don't wanna like lose her.
- I'm feeling very confident
about my relationship
with Rachel.
My Fantasy Suite
went so flawlessly.
Like I can't imagine it
having gone any better.
It was perfection.
But it's still Rachel's choice.
You know, I know
that she's really stressed
about how she was received
by my family.
It was pretty hard for her.
I just see her as
like my future,
and like,
if she doesn't see that back,
like that would be pretty
like soul crushing.
I'm feeling sick to my stomach.
Tonight's Rose Ceremony feels
the complete opposite
of what have gone into
every Rose Ceremony.
I thought our connection
was the most strong.
- Hey, Zach.
- Hey, Jesse.
- How you doing, man?
- I'm getting there.
How are you feeling?
Um, sadness.
Kind of overwhelming.
But before she gets the
opportunity to offer roses,
I'd like to talk to her.
- You think you
need that clarity?
- I think so.
- All right.
I wish you the best, man.
- Thank you, Jesse.
- Good luck.
- Rachel made me feel special.
And I felt like what
we shared was real.
Felt like the love was actually
forming and building
with her together,
something that
I was totally buying into
and...
all of that went away
in one night.
- Hey, Aven.
- How we doing?
- Good to see you again, man.
- Good to see you.
How you doing?
- How's everything?
- Good, good.
It's been a fun week.
- What do you think
the overnight date did
for your relationship together?
I think it grew a lot.
I think we were able to talk
about some really good stuff
and spend some
really good quality time
to just kind of be ourselves,
and it was amazing.
- And are you falling
in love with her?
- I am falling
in love with Rachel.
- Wow.
- Yes, I know. Big.
- I'm glad to hear you say that.
Wish you all the best tonight.
- Me too, Jesse.
It's good to see you.
- Take care, man. You too.
What's up?
- How are you doing, man?
- How you doing?
- Oh, yeah.
Cooking.
- Tino, what's up?
- How's it going?
- How are you?
- Not too shabby.
How about you?
- Pretty good.
You got a smile on your face.
Looks like someone's overnight
date went pretty well.
- Yeah, it was really fun.
- Tell me about it.
- We took another gigantic leap
and me and Rachel
told each other
that we're in love with
each other and it was amazing.
- So you're in love with her?
- Absolutely.
Stronger after the
overnight portion, for sure.
- Really?
That night in Fantasy Suite,
I mean, the body language,
the way that we both interacted,
it felt like we
were two strangers.
We had like the most
inauthentic conversation
I've ever had.
I felt like I wasn't
talking to the same Rachel.
I mean, I'm terrified right now.
My heart's pounding
out of my chest.
I'm not feeling okay...
Because I do have
feelings for her.
Like that just won't go away.
I have to salvage what I have.
I need to tell
Rachel how I feel.
- Hi, Jesse.
- Hello.
- How are you?
- So good to see you.
You look great.
- You too.
You look amazing as always.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
- You got a beautiful smile.
How's the week been?
- It has been so incredible.
I just really had the best time
with all three of these men.
And a lot of clarity, a lot of,
you know, questions,
hard questions, but they
all definitely stepped up.
- Right.
And after this week,
you feel like
there's a proposal
at the end of this for you?
- I really think
there might be a proposal.
I'm hoping so.
- I'm so happy
to hear you say that.
Well, there is something
I do have to tell you.
- Okay.
- Gabby will not be joining you
at this Rose Ceremony.
You're gonna be the
only Bachelorette here.
- Okay.
- All right.
This Rose Ceremony
really is all about you
and your relationships
with your men.
You forged your own path,
your own journey,
and tonight is really
all about that.
Gabby's on her journey,
and you're on your journey.
- Ah, it's gonna be
so weird not having her here,
but I'm ready.
- I know you are.
All right, well,
your men are anxiously waiting.
- All right.
Thanks, Jesse.
- I know it's a big one.
Good luck.
- Bye.
- That was me.
I showed her who I was.
I was more than ready
to get on one knee.
The Rachel, you know,
that I was falling in love with,
I trusted her, you know,
at least to show me her real...
Her real self.
And I don't think I got that.
And I still don't
know why or how.
What was that Rachel
that I was getting?
That's the biggest concern
to me.
So yeah, I'm upset.
I can't just be here and
not share my feelings with her
because I need answers.
- Hi, guys.
It's so good to see all of you.
I just wanted to say that
I truly had the most wonderful
week with all three of you.
I'm so thankful
for you guys to be here.
- Rachel, can we speak?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Oh. Why the heck?
- Oh, my God.
- I'm kind of still
conflicted and nervous,
but today I do know
what I need to do.
And I just need to find Erich
and really tell him how I feel
and lay everything out
on the table.
I am scared that the
last conversation went awry
and that we can't kind
of get back to that.
I don't wanna play games.
I think I've like
worked really hard
and have been honest
with myself and my feelings.
But I've been waiting
for the right moment
and this is so clearly
the right moment.
And now, I'm really
not afraid to say
that I do know what I deserve.
- I'm getting ready for the
Rose Ceremony,
and I'm afraid
that I might loser her.
I am in love with Gabby,
and this whole process,
I've kind of misjudged
from the start
how hard it is on her.
I brought something up that
wasn't in the right place,
right time.
And it's something we
had already talked about.
And for me to just still
kind of harp on something
that was bothering me,
I realize how
insensitive that is.
And I don't know
what she's thinking.
I'm sweating and I'm nervous
and I'm shaking
and I don't know what to do.
- Right now, like,
I'm so scared.
In the end,
I deserve being with someone
who isn't afraid to love me.
Erich is the only man here
and I think that's
what makes it more scary.
I can't tolerate any more pain.
And I know walking away from him
would be what I need
to protect myself.
I don't know what's
gonna happen.
I can't predict anything.
And I just... am gonna
have to see how I feel.
If it's my decision to leave
here alone, I know it's mine.
Hi.
- Hi.
- How are you?
- Good.
How are you?
- Surprised?
- I was not expecting you.
- You weren't?
- No.
Oh, this is your outfit.
Um, how are you?
- I'm good.
- Good.
- Are you okay?
- I'm just gonna jump right in.
- Yeah. Go ahead.
- Um, this week has
like been so crazy,
um, and I think I've been
learning so much about myself
literally every day
and every week.
And, um, I knew it would
be hard, everything,
but I honestly didn't know
it would be this hard
and I've been making decisions.
You know, the situation
when like you and I were
speaking last was like...
Didn't...
I don't think go as planned.
It was just hard.
I don't know.
I think we were like
misunderstanding each other.
Um, and I think I was so upset
'cause I was like,
"Why doesn't he just
like trust us?"
Going into, you know,
my date with Jason,
like I did just
need more clarity.
Um, and I know
he's a private person,
so I think
we just needed time alone.
Um, and having our date
and our time together,
it was the first time
I was able to like
come around to what
knowing what I deserve.
But like, I know in my heart
that like you've fought for me
so much and you love
in this very secure
and comfortable way.
Like you've taught me how
like I wanted to be treated
and that's okay to like
ask for those things.
You know, sometimes
it is hard for me
to just like take
things at face value
because of everything
that I've gone through.
But you have like
taught me that it's okay
to feel safe and
wanted and loved
in maybe a way that I haven't.
And you're the only one left.
I know it's like so hard
and I think I've felt it
for a while,
but I do know that I love you.
I love you.
This is fricking amazing.
I'm so happy right now.
That's the best
feeling in the world.
It's like,
all I wanted was this,
and then you get it and it's...
I just couldn't be happier.
And then anybody that I
connect with like so easily
and like so deeply
right off the bat.
And then I got to know you more
and like about who you are
and your family and
past relationships.
And your life hasn't been easy
and it's made you just like
such an amazing woman.
And I'm so freaking
lucky that it is you.
- I've been waiting so long
to tell Erich how I feel.
He's been so vulnerable and
confident and secure with me.
He's the best thing
that's ever happened to me
and it feels so right.
I do have like so many feelings.
I'm able to get to this point
'cause you've always
made me feel so safe.
And I like, honestly,
never gotten it before.
It has like come from the past
and not just like
with romantic relationships
but in some other ones,
just having like to ask
for those things.
And you've never made me ask.
I think I needed to like
process and come to it,
you know, on my own terms
for it to like make sense
'cause it is so foreign to me.
- I love you, Gabby.
- I'm getting emotional.
- Okay.
- And honestly,
it feels like a fairytale.
I just like can't believe
that he's all mine.
There's no point
in having a Rose Ceremony,
and it's just you and me.
I like the sound of that.
- Me too.
Erich is definitely
the love of my life.
I think everything in my life
has happened for a reason,
and all of the arrows
and the stars
are pointing straight to him.
It feels so good and it feels
so incredibly meant to be.
I love you.
I finally get to live
what I thought
was only gonna be fantasy.
Sometimes I'm like, pinch me,
'cause it's way too good
to be true.
- Rachel, can we speak?
- Yeah.
- Uh, um...
- His look when he asked her
to walk out,
he just looked like
pretty upset.
- Yeah.
- Interesting.
I guess he kinda saw it
as a now or never.
- Hey, Jesse Palmer here.
I know, look,
I know you're all expecting
to watch the end of
that dramatic Rose Ceremony
in Mexico right now and I know
you're all very anxious
and eager to find out
what happens next,
but unfortunately,
you're not gonna
see that tonight
and I'm very, very,
sorry for that.
Things have just been
so emotional,
they've been so dramatic
for both Gabby and Rachel
that we felt it was right
to take a moment
and to prepare ourselves
for the shocking events
that are about to take place,
events that are gonna change
both Rachel's and Gabby's lives
forever.
So next week, we'll all watch
the most emotional finale
in "Bachelorette" history,
and it's gonna take place
right here on this stage live.
And we felt it was best to wait
until both Rachael and Gabby
and their men could be here
to address all of the drama.
And of course, we'll have our
live studio audience
and you will all bear witness
to the crazy controversy
that's about to ensue.
So take some time
and get yourselves ready
and prepare yourselves...
for the most shocking finale
of all time.
Here's a sneak peek.
- This is actually crazy.
I don't want to do this anymore.
- Gabby.
- I want to leave here.
- For people who
say that they care about me
to question my character,
it's really disappointing.
This is straight-up
shattering everything
that you promised me.
- Next week...
- Breathe, okay?
You're okay.
- The most emotional
and unpredictable
season finale
of all time begins.
- There's no way this works out.
Please just keep me out of this.
Let me out.
- We are literally about
to be engaged tomorrow.
To our dream guys.
- Literally dreams.
- Will Gabby and Rachel both
find the love they so deserve?
Hi!
- I'm, like, really thankful
it's just us.
- You think he's ready
to get down on a knee?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- I just love her.
I want the best for her.
- If you think
you know what happens...
- We have a problem.
- Guess again.
- He was unsure
there would be an engagement.
I think you should definitely
kick him in the.
You don't deserve this.
- You changed your story
so many times. I'm done.
- I know that there's still
somebody involved in this.
- Why are you yelling at me?
You told me things,
and then you went back
against what you said.
I want this to work.
I've given him
nothing but the best.
- - I just, like...
I want to date you.
Getting engaged
before that happens
is not how things usually go.
- I feel like
I'm so sick of this.
What am I supposed to do?
Walk away because
he's not ready to propose?
Makes me feel that I'm,
like, unlovable.
- You're lying
straight to my face.
I want an answer
for why you did what you did.
- The shocking, live finale
of "The Bachelorette"
starts next Tuesday night.
- In Amsterdam.
That artwork was European,
right?
It wasn't from America.
- Mm-mm.
1600s.
- Is that the Renaissance?
- Yes.
I believe so.
Are you a history...
Are you a history buff?
- I really like history.
- Yeah.
- But I don't know
like time periods.
- Yeah.
- All I know is I look like
every kid in those pictures.
- I don't even know
where you're getting that.
- Tell me I do not.
- Every single one of them?
- I was reincarnated
from a Renaissance child.
- Not even...
Not even a little bit.
- I looked at the kid, I'm like,
that's how I see myself
in the mirror every day.
- Stop.
- 16th century child.
- I'm incredibly attracted
to a Renaissance child now,
I guess.
Thanks for making it weird now.
- Never say that out loud again.
You said...
- In Amsterdam.
That artwork was European,
right?
It wasn't from America.
- Mm-mm.
1600s.
- Is that the Renaissance?
- Yes.
I believe so.
Are you a history...
Are you a history buff?
- I really like history.
- Yeah.
- But I don't know
like time periods.
- Yeah.
- All I know is I look like
every kid in those pictures.
- I don't even know
where you're getting that.
- Tell me I do not.
- Every single one of them?
- I was reincarnated
from a Renaissance child.
- Not even...
Not even a little bit.
- I looked at the kid, I'm like,
that's how I see myself
in the mirror every day.
- Stop.
- 16th century child.
- I'm incredibly attracted
to a Renaissance child now,
I guess.
Thanks for making it weird now.
- Never say that out loud again.
You said...
>>>>oakislandtk
www.opensubtitles.org