- Tonight on
"The Bachelorette"...
- Bring it on.
- This is definitely not
the normal situation
because we do have
two Bachelorettes.
- Do you think it's gonna be
two separate group dates,
or are they both
gonna be on one?
- I cannot prepare for anything.
- How this is gonna work
with two Bachelorettes
is one of the biggest things
on everybody's mind.
- Whoo!
- There's two Bachelorettes.
I want to start
being able to figure out
which way am I leaning.
- What's up, Gabby?
What's up, Rachel?
What's up, Gabby?
- It's complicated
because you're dealing
with two amazing women,
but they have polar opposite
personalities.
- Things will get messy.
I have no doubt about it.
- There has to be
a point in this
where they're both gonna like
the same person.
- Can I kiss you?
- Yeah.
- I do have to tell you
something.
- What?
- I kissed Logan.
- What I'm not interested in,
is you guys' way
of going about this process.
- That is a form of control,
and that is manipulative.
- I feel really bad.
He's, like, this incredible guy,
but then something's off.
I just don't know what to do.
- Everything's just way harder
than I expected.
- We have no idea
what's going to happen.
- Do you feel like it's
appropriate to be
talking about
Fantasy Suites this early?
I do think it would be time
for you to go.
- You came back.
- Can we interrupt you guys?
- Yeah, you need to...
- What's going on?
We did ask you to leave.
- Last night was crazy.
I feel like we have so much
time to make up for...
We have 29 guys.
And we didn't talk to more
than half of them.
- I literally can't believe it.
I can't believe we canceled
the Rose Ceremony.
- We had to.
- Yeah.
- But I'm looking forward
to, like, having a group date
this week and really
getting to know the people
that we haven't spoken to yet.
- Yeah.
- But like, what can we do?
Like, it's so rainy.
- I know, I know.
Initially, we were talking
so much about a pool party...
- Yeah.
- Which would have been nice
to, like, see
their six-pack abs, yeah.
- Like, how do we get them
to show us their six-pack abs?
- Yeah.
- When it's raining.
- Without being too obvious.
- We have to come up
with some idea.
- Last night,
after the Rose Ceremony
was canceled,
29 of us moved into the mansion.
There's not enough beds
for all of us.
I mean, you can't walk
around this mansion
without stepping on someone.
- All right,
we're making breakfast?
- Yeah, I'll make some eggs.
- I got you, I got you.
- We need bowls.
- Got, like, a lot of OJ,
or a little bit of OJ?
- Right there. You...
- Hey, watch your eyes.
Opa!
I'm trying to get a grasp
on how the rest of the week
is gonna go.
I don't know
if they're gonna split it up,
like, half and half.
Is Gabby gonna take
the guys that she's feeling?
Is Rachel gonna take
the men she's feeling?
How many one-on-ones?
Are there gonna be
any one-on-ones?
- So you think it's gonna be
two separate group dates
or are they both
gonna be on one?
- I hope they just give
a one-on-one
to a guy that they haven't
even talked to yet.
That would be phenomenal.
- I think that's gonna be
really tough
'cause there's so many guys.
I mean, we're here to hopefully
get an engagement at the end
of the day, you know,
really fall in love
with somebody.
And how do you do that if you
don't even speak with them?
I have no idea
what's gonna happen,
but that makes it fun.
- Surprise!
- How is everyone?
- How are you?
Today, we have something
really special planned
for the guys.
Of course, last night didn't
really go as planned.
We didn't get to talk
to half the guys.
- We saved a seat for you.
- Oh, my gosh, thank you.
- Yeah.
- Are you guys excited to be
in the mansion,
finally out of the hotel?
- We want a way
for the men to go
one by one and show us
their personality.
And I think it'll give us,
like, a bigger picture
of who they are,
because we only got to see,
you know, three seconds
of some of them.
Since there's so many of us,
we wanted to think of something
that we could get to know
you guys kind of individually.
So naturally,
we thought a pageant
would be the best way...
- A little talent show.
- A little talent,
a little interview.
But before we get started,
we have one last thing
for you guys.
- Really?
- Yeah.
To help you along, maybe.
- Uh-oh.
- Your first gifts, yeah.
Don't look.
- So you guys have
30 minutes to prepare,
and you guys better bring it.
We'll see you soon.
- Oh, mysterious.
I like it.
- Hey, what's in there?
What's in there?
- Open it up.
- So the girls,
before they left,
dropped off some gifts.
And I was thinking,
"Oh, what's in the bags?"
You know, what kind of gifts?
I love gifts.
- Speedos!
- What?
Little did I know it was gonna
be this type of gift.
- All right, guys,
let's go get changed.
- Oh, my...
- Bro.
- Oh, there's no chance
these fit.
Zero chance.
- This is wild!
- I was expecting maybe
something a little bit,
you know, slower and like,
"Hey, let's get
to know each other."
And then it's boom.
We're in Speedos.
- Yeah, they don't cover up
very much.
- 200.
I'm honestly ready to show them
everything that
they need to see.
And that's not just outside
but that's inside.
- It's like every day is more
nervous than the last day.
So I'm actually really hairy.
So... and pale.
I was expecting
to present myself,
but not with a Speedo on.
- Is that a sock in there?
- Yeah.
- This guy's cheating!
- Put another one in there.
Put another one in there.
This is insane.
I'm about to go on national TV
in a Speedo.
It covers next to nothing.
- I appreciate this, guys.
I'm gonna remember this.
- The things you do
for love, right?
- All right, fellas.
Come on downstairs.
I'll meet you
in the living room.
- Bring it on.
Let's bring it!
- Let's do it!
- Bring on the men.
It's a little hot in here.
We're ready.
Bring it on.
- See 'em in Speedos, baby.
This is great.
- I know, I'm sweatin'.
- All right, gentlemen,
you are gonna be
competing here today
in a pageant of sorts,
for both Gabby and Rachel.
And the prize today,
it could not be bigger.
Whoever does the best
here today,
the guys who show
the most heart,
the most creativity,
maybe the most skin,
just saying,
will get invited back
to Gabby and Rachel's place
later tonight for a very
exclusive afterparty.
- The prize of being able
to go back to their house
and have a party
with the two of them,
I mean, that's high stakes.
I didn't get
the opportunity to spend
much time with them last night,
so I'll do whatever it takes.
- So this is how this is
gonna work.
You will disrobe,
and you will show us
your "look,"
forward and backwards.
- Oh, my...
- Yes.
- Whoo-hoo!
- Up first, Logan.
- Sorry to my mom,
sorry to my dad,
sorry to my grammy.
Uh, to my niece?
Never watch this.
- Some support, yes.
Shoes and socks.
- I'm gonna make a fool
of myself,
but I'm gonna go all out.
This is part of the deal.
This is how you find love.
- Let the competition begin.
Up first, Logan.
- Oh, my God.
- I can't make eye contact.
- Yeah, I'm like, mm.
- I don't know where to look.
- Today's group date is like
a beauty pageant...
Bachelor style.
And the winners get to have
more intimate time tonight,
so there is a lot on the line.
- Gabby, Rachel, you have any
questions for Logan Palmer?
- We do.
How would your exes
describe you?
- A bit stubborn.
That's a good word.
Honest, kind.
- Love it.
Logan has definitely
been on my radar
since night one,
and today isn't any different.
I think we're ready for talent.
- All right, ladies,
before a relationship turns
into a beautiful, uh...
butterfly,
it has to start as a worm.
- Oh, my God.
Like a true professional!
- It was nice,
with Logan going first,
to go in there fully confident,
hit his worm to perfection.
Everybody go crazy in the crowd.
I think he really set the tone
for all of us
to step our games up.
- Let me show you what a real
man's body looks like.
- So many butts,
so many dudes
who don't skip leg day.
- It's unbelievable.
It's just like me looking
in a mirror.
- When you're wearing
a Speedo, it's nice and snug.
You can feel it
kind of ride up at times,
and you got to get rid
of that wedgie.
- I've never went to a store
and thought,
yeah, let me get the thong one.
Yeah, the one that gets
in the crease.
- Whapow!
- This is something
I do not normally do.
But it was like, bro,
the stakes were on the line.
- Do you feel like
this is something
you could wear regularly?
Like, what if we asked?
- Please, no, please no.
- Stiff competition.
I think we're ready
for the talent.
Today I'm just looking for
maybe a little bit
of creativity,
how much fun can you have
with the talent?
- My mind's been spinning
about all the ways
that I could connect with you.
About all the things
that I could show you.
- The things that I look for
are definitely confidence,
effort, and how willing you
are to kind of commit today.
- We both want them to show us
their personality.
Oh!
- I think it'll be good to just
get a feel of who they are.
- All right, ladies.
This talent is very important.
I'm gonna help you guys
save $60,000 a year
on a 30-year fixed mortgage.
So let's talk about debts.
- I'm taking notes.
- Jacob is Tarzan,
dressed like George of
the Jungle/my mortgage broker.
I liked it. I was into it.
I appreciated the glasses.
- All right, next up,
he makes the best
6-foot meatball sub
in the world,
Meatball!
- Yeah, I'm just trying to,
you know, impress the ladies.
I think they want to see
our personalities,
and Meatball always comes up
with something interesting.
Gotta be patient. You'll see.
What are meatballs...
- I'm scared.
- Without some sauce?
- No!
No!
- No! No!
God!
- I honestly think
it's gonna take
a while for me to eat
spaghetti sauce.
I mean, even just the smells
in the room
and then associating
that with him
pouring it on his body,
I was like...
- It smells just like spaghetti.
- I'm Italian,
but I don't do canned sauce.
- How many serious
relationships have you been in?
- So what is your
beauty routine?
- Hufflepuff or Gryffindor?
I think with the questions,
it's gonna be important to see
if they're gonna answer honestly
and really try and get to know
the important parts.
Kind of core values, I think,
will be important.
- Oh, I love Johnny.
- Oh, my God.
I think Rachel and I find a lot
of the same guys attractive,
and there's some overlap,
but we are allowing
ourselves space
to kind of figure it out
together.
Johnny, if you could kiss
one of us right now,
which one would it be?
- Is there a chance
that I can pick both?
- Absolutely.
- Good answer.
- Oh, he's confident.
In the Speedo!
- Johnny's wearing
the pilot hat.
Have to take notice of that.
It was pretty hot.
- Chris.
- So what's gonna happen is,
I'm gonna start a beat
for you guys.
If, when I dribble the ball,
you guys could stomp your feet,
and when I slap the ball,
you can clap your hands?
All right.
I'm totally crushing it.
So what I did was,
I gave them a little taste
of three things that are
really important to me.
One of those things is sports.
One of those things is music.
One thing is leadership.
Ultimately, like, I believe
I'm, like, the alpha.
I'm, like, number one leader.
- Whoo!
Personally made song
right there on the spot.
Did you have a question for me?
- Honestly, no question.
- Gabby and Rachel,
they are gonna head back
to their place,
and they're gonna decide
who they're gonna invite
to this exclusive afterparty.
- I think it's gonna be
a tough decision,
but to have them pick you now
is just, like, huge.
- I did all I could
with what I had.
Everybody feels like
they did enough,
but it's fair game for anybody.
- I feel like we got to know
you guys a little bit better,
and this decision is not
gonna be easy.
I will be there.
- If we can put our
glasses higher,
let's do a toast to putting
your cheeks out there today.
What is that?
Hey, someone go get it.
- I got it, I got it.
- Today, I was in a Speedo
in front of 30 other guys,
Jesse Palmer,
Rachel, Gabby.
Yeah, and after putting
it all on the line,
there's no question that I want
to be on the date card.
An envelope.
- For those lucky guys
who get to go,
it's a big moment because
it's a lot of alone time.
- Aven.
Logan.
Brandan.
Jason.
Johnny.
And Colin.
- You know, I kind of left it
all out there.
You know, literally, like,
my ass cheeks were outside
today, you know?
Not hearing my name,
I'm just like,
is there something
I could have done better?
- I'm excited.
It's gonna be a fun experience.
- Honestly, like, for you guys
who are going,
the six of you...
there's some people,
including myself,
who they don't need a test
with right now,
who they already know
how they feel.
But for those of you
who are going,
it's awesome to you guys,
so hope you have a good time.
- How do you feel?
- It's nerve-racking.
- It is.
I'm excited, though.
I think we're gonna
settle in just fine.
Today went really smoothly.
We had so much fun with the men.
I'm so excited for this to be
our first, like, afterparty.
- All right, boys,
let's do this.
Hey!
- Come on in!
- How are you?
- Tonight would be a good night
for us to kind of get an idea
of who is more compatible.
I do think
it's going to be telling
on who may be the guys
we vibe with more.
We're really excited
to have you.
This is our first date night,
so cheers to you guys.
Cheers.
- I am really looking forward
to getting to know Jason.
He definitely caught Gabby
and I's eye today,
so I'm excited to see how he is
more on one-on-one time.
Thank you!
Best-case scenario,
I get a kiss.
Maybe two.
- How's it going
for you, though?
- I wanted to ask you.
- Two Bachelorettes,
like, this is crazy.
- How do you feel
about that, like...
- Yeah.
- With both of us?
- It's been wild to just, like,
do this.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, I don't know.
I feel like I should be upfront.
To be honest,
like, when I got here,
like, I felt, like,
a connection to Gabby.
Yeah, and like, you know,
I truly, like,
think you're the most,
like, genuine
and, like, beautiful...
- No, you... believe me.
- You're fine.
- No, like...
No, I'm not trying...
- Yeah.
- I just want to tell you that.
- Thank you. Thank you.
- Yeah, I can feel that
you're, like,
a truly genuine, like, person.
- Yeah.
I was a little disappointed.
This is the first conversation,
but he is someone
that is basically
going to be for Gabby.
Of course, it's disappointing,
but I know that there's
gonna be men where I have
amazing connections.
So I really hope it starts
to turn around tonight.
- How was today?
- It was wild.
- Yeah.
- That was so uncomfortable.
- Welcome to the life...
- I love it, yeah.
- Of minimal clothing.
- I give you girls props.
That's crazy.
- Well, you exude confidence.
- Really?
- I think so.
- Love that word.
Exude confidence.
- Exude? Yeah.
- So I know I kissed you
on the cheek today,
but I think I kind of want
to retry that.
- Is that okay with you?
- Yeah.
- Come here.
- So I'm a little unsure
about where I stand tonight.
I mean, we're open to both
exploring similar connections,
but I'm still trying
to find my footing.
- So I've travelled to almost
every state in the U. S.
- Really?
- I think I have, like,
12 or 14 left.
At this point, I'm just like,
I might as well
just do the last few.
- Absolutely.
It definitely wasn't going
the way I expected it to.
It really feels like
these guys are
just having friendly,
small talk conversation
that you could have
with your cousin.
- I'm a huge Harry Potter fan.
I listen to all the Audibles,
watch the movies.
I love the Audible because
the narrator is incredible.
And he does every character.
It's like, it's... it's excellent.
- I do feel like these guys
are holding back with me.
I don't know where they stand.
And I want to hand out
a rose tonight,
so someone's got
to step up their game.
How did you feel like
today with, like,
really pushing everyone
outside their comfort zone?
How do you feel?
- I felt good. Um...
one thing I've noticed...
- Yeah.
- About you.
- Oh, tell me.
- Oh, yeah.
I've been paying attention.
- Tell me.
- Very brave.
- I'm brave?
- I think you're brave.
- Why is that?
- I do.
Well, for you to, like,
jump back into this process?
- Mm-hmm.
- Like, I still believe in it.
That's, like, incredibly brave.
- Thanks.
- So when I get my name
called up first
to do a little dance
in my Speedo,
I figured I'll take a page out
of your book.
- Awesome.
- So, yeah, yeah.
- I like it!
- Yeah.
And I think we did have
a nice connection as well.
- Yeah.
- I want to see more of it.
- I do too.
I'm really glad you're here.
And not a bad kisser, either.
- You don't think so, huh?
- It's more brownie points.
My night had been disappointing,
but I think Logan
turned things around.
He is really funny.
He really put himself
out there today.
We have really fun banter,
and he's very cute.
So... we'll see.
I really like Logan.
- That's one thing that I
really was drawn to about you,
was, um...
like, you're someone who makes
people smile and laugh,
but there's, like,
a whole ocean under that.
- Yeah.
- I just want to say, like,
I do recognize that.
- I feel like you've been,
like, really sweet to me.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Can I kiss you?
Logan and I had
a really good conversation.
He's super fun, very charming,
so I think I could
definitely see myself
giving him a rose.
- I'm kind of nervous
about the two roses there,
a little bit.
- Yeah.
There's two girls.
- There's has to be a point
in this where they're
both gonna like the same person.
- Yeah, things will get messy.
I have no doubt about it.
- Right now,
who would your rose go to?
- Yeah, I don't know.
Logan and I had, like,
good banter and, like,
kind of easy connection,
and he was like...
- He's a cool guy.
- Yeah.
- Um... I do have to tell you
something.
- What?
- I kissed Logan.
- Okay. Do you like him?
- I do.
- Yeah. Mm-hmm.
Like, kind of your type?
- He's sweet. Yeah, I do.
- Yeah.
- I like him.
You know, my heart
kind of dropped a little bit.
I think that Logan
is exploring both sides,
which is what we're asking
of the men,
but I already felt like I had
a really strong connection
with him, and I was excited
to see where things go.
So it feels weird.
- I just... I want to get
where your head's at too.
- Yeah.
- Because if he's someone
you're like, super,
super interested in, like,
I will completely be like...
you know?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
- Hmm.
- It is a weird place
for Rachel and I right now.
You know, we're both exploring
both sides of our relationships.
- Hello.
- Ladies.
- Hi.
Everything's just way harder
than I expected.
And this is, like,
kind of the first time
we're figuring it out.
Tonight, I want to give
this rose to someone
who made me feel really special
and made me laugh.
Logan, will you accept
this rose?
- I will. Thank you.
Okay,
I'm not sure how to pin it on.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Rose looks good on you, kid.
- Yeah, I know today
was such a crazy day,
and I've loved getting to know
each and every one of you
tonight, but I'm gonna give
this rose
to someone
who surprised me tonight.
So...
Johnny,
will you accept this rose?
- Of course I will.
- Rachel feels very strongly
about Logan.
I want to be able
to give her that space
in order to nurture.
It's truly not worth stepping
on Rachel's toes
in this scenario.
- Thanks for being our first
date night.
- Yeah.
- Two Bachelorettes
is causing some hurdles
that we didn't really know
to even plan for,
and I'm not sure how we're
gonna figure it out.
- Gentlemen, how we doing?
What's going on?
Hey! We doing all right?
Good to see you. All right.
Well, listen, guys,
some of you gentlemen
got roses last night, right?
Logan, Johnny.
- That's right, yeah.
- Congratulations, gentlemen.
- Thank you.
- All right,
so here's the fun part.
For the rest of this week,
both Gabby and Rachel
will each have
a one-on-one date.
Now, obviously,
only two dates left this week,
so that means time
is at a premium.
Okay, on that note,
got the first date card
right here.
- Wow.
- This one's from Rachel.
Gentlemen,
I wish you all the best
and hope to see you
at the next Rose Ceremony.
If there is one... I don't even
know at this point.
See you guys. Good luck.
See you, Jesse.
- I'm very excited
for the possibility of a date
with Rachel.
Rachel is so beautiful.
Like, she's the real deal.
My heart is beating
out of my chest.
- I'm just crossing my fingers.
I'm like, "Please, please,
like, just say my name."
- Jordan V.
- Wasn't my name.
- "Love is in the air.
Love, Rachel."
- Coming into this,
you don't know what to expect,
and I definitely didn't expect
to get the first one-on-one.
But now that I got it,
I'm elated.
And I'm super grateful
that she sees something in me.
I came here for love, you know.
I came here to find the person
I'm supposed to spend
the rest of my life with.
The beginning of forever
could start today.
- We have a cool car.
- Ooh, look at that.
- I figured it was fitting.
- I love it. That's beautiful.
- Last night,
I was very concerned
that no one wants me,
but it ended up being great.
- That is awesome.
- Convertible?
Today, my greatest hopes
are having
a really good connection
with Jordan.
I'm driving, though.
- Absolutely.
I wouldn't expect
anything different.
- He told me that
he was here to meet me,
which is a really good feeling.
I couldn't let you drive.
I know.
- You drive every day.
- I know.
- Something I noticed right
away was how passionate
Jordan is about his career
in race car driving.
Yeah, the stakes are high today.
There's going to be a rose,
so it's a big deal.
Lot of pressure.
Just kidding, Jordan.
You'll do fine.
- We're haulin'.
Give it a little bit.
- Whoo!
- Yeah, give it a little bit.
Yeah, throw the hands up.
Whoo!
I'm like,
blinded by my long hair.
- I feel like I want
to hold it for you,
but I don't know if I should
do that or not.
- I have something really fun
planned for Jordan today.
It's something that gets
your adrenaline
going a little bit,
and I'm excited
to give Jordan a little taste
of my brand of adventure.
- No way.
No way.
- Have you ever
done this before?
- No, oh, man, I'm in for it.
I'm in for it.
Are you kidding me?
- Zero gravity means you
basically get to float around
like an astronaut
without going to space.
- Starting to freak out
a little bit.
I am 100% nervous.
I'm... you know,
I'm scared of heights.
Zero gravity terrifies me.
- You get to be
in my element for a day.
- Holy cow.
Rachel, you know, her being
a pilot, she can handle it.
I think I would feel a little
safer if she was flying it.
Oh, now it's getting real.
- Boarding the plane, I am like,
shocked by the fact that Jordan
is having such a scared,
strong reaction because, I mean,
he is a race car driver.
- It's crazy.
- Is this crazy?
- Yes.
- Are you scared?
- Are you?
- No!
- Of course not.
Can't do the heights.
I can do the speed.
And I feel a little nervous,
obviously,
but she's gonna be
right by my side,
and I can't wait
to share it with her.
- Oh, my God!
Oh, my God.
- I got you.
- You got me?
- Oh!
You're stronger than me!
How did you do that?
- I don't even know,
I don't know how to stop.
Heights make me nervous.
If I was alone,
I would be terrified,
but Rachel and her
calming ability,
it helped... it is helping
calm my nerves.
- Are you feeling sick?
Are you all right?
- No, I'm good, yeah.
I did forget about
the world today,
and I was just super grateful
to her for choosing me to be
on this date with her and have
this experience with her.
So yeah,
I forgot about everything.
I didn't care about the guys
in the house.
I didn't care about
anything at all
but spending time with her
and having this experience.
I think today,
up in zero gravity,
we really,
really found a connection.
I feel only excitement
for tonight.
And now it's just time to build
on what we have already.
- So who here has spent time
with my girl so far?
I have not.
- Which one is your girl?
- I'm honestly open
to both of them.
I'm, like, rubbing my hands
together at the opportunity
to, like, get some
one-on-one time for sure.
Because I plan to be here
all the way.
But ultimately, like,
there's definitely
some deal breakers for me,
like, especially if I'm talking
about one person who I would
spend the rest of my life with.
Like, for me,
it would be a deal breaker
if we got down
to the final four,
which I plan to be in,
and we go into
Fantasy Suite and we have
this sexual experience,
and then the person
who I'm most interested in
decides that she's
gonna have sex
with multiple people
and feel it out.
That would be the situation
where I'd go, "Okay, I'm out."
There's no chance.
- Whoa.
What are you talking about?
I really don't think that
we should be talking about
Fantasy Suites at all
at this point.
I think it's a little weird
that Chris is thinking
that far ahead.
It's a little presumptuous
and disrespectful
to Gabby and Rachel.
- You're kind of talking
about something
that is way down the line.
- Yeah, this
is a long time away.
- We kind of need to focus on
what's in front of us right now.
- Chris is bringing up
Fantasy Suites.
It's kind of a jerk-y move.
I'm sure he's gonna cause
a wildfire of.
Wow.
- Isn't this gorgeous?
- This is absolutely gorgeous.
- I truly had
such an incredible day.
Jordan, I think, was the
perfect choice for this date.
Thank you.
Tonight, I'm really excited
to get to know Jordan more.
I mean, we have
a playful chemistry,
and I want to see if
it can go further than that.
I'm really hopeful.
I, of course,
love the fact that we got
to experience something
for the first time together.
We do have such
different passions,
but in a way, it's so similar.
And I think for me,
that's been something
that's been hard for me
to find in a partner.
Someone who shares, like,
a passion,
and I noticed that with you
right away.
- It's been hard to explain
what I do to most people
'cause most people
don't know what I do.
They hear "drag racing,"
they have no idea.
The fact that, you know,
you're a pilot,
and the fact that
you understand that feeling
that we get before we fly
or before we drive...
- Mm-hmm.
- It's a little, you know,
easier to explain to you
'cause I know you get it
and you get me.
- Absolutely.
- Yeah.
- You know,
I'm cool with everybody here,
but there are some people,
you know,
even here, I feel like Chris,
you'll say, like,
subtle things, you know.
- Like what?
- You'll say, like,
subtle things
in a group environment.
- Like what?
- You spoke on, like,
a fantasy room subject.
- A what? Be clear.
What did I say?
- It was about,
if you're not first
in that fantasy room,
and you're last...
- You wouldn't want to be there?
- Yeah.
- My personal perspective,
and I hold true to this, is,
if you're in a situation
where there's four people,
and there's four people invited
to this Fantasy Suite,
and the female in this situation
has sex with someone else,
I wouldn't be interested
in that person
being the person I'm with.
- Okay, I have a question,
because this is
what kind of happened
last season.
Would you be...
Would you vocalize that to them
before Fantasy Suites,
during Fantasy Suites,
or after Fantasy Suites?
- Good question; it would be
dependent on the situation.
Because something that's also...
- Well, you wouldn't know
the situation...
- Listen, listen, listen.
- You wouldn't know
the situation.
- Let me finish speaking,
please.
For me, what I'm
not interested in
is you guys' way
of going about this process.
- When you talk about
Fantasy Suites,
you're there
because you're in love.
- When you're at Fantasy Suites,
you're there because
you're in the final four.
That's the only guarantee.
- So it's a game?
- If you're there,
then that's a game.
That's a game to you.
- That's a game, dude.
- Ah, gosh darn it,
I did not say that.
Like, I did not even
use the term...
- Didn't he?
- May I speak to you?
Look at me.
- Why are you telling me,
you're really,
like, allowing someone
to speak like
you have this, like,
this... this approach?
- Of organization?
- No, you're trying
to control it, though.
- So I've let you speak.
I've let him speak.
- I'm just saying the way
you saying it
is still rubbing us wrong.
- It's rubbing you wrong.
- The way Chris speaks
is all about control.
He's very kind of intense.
Maybe you don't mean to deliver
a condescending tone,
but in general, that's
what it sounds like to people.
He's drawing a lot of lines
in the sand that
kind of surprised
a lot of the guys.
- Any time that you have
a premeditated thought of,
"You won't do this,
unless that,"
that is a form of control,
and that is manipulative.
This could be our queen,
this could be
the mother of our children,
and this could be
someone we spend the rest
of our lives with.
You cannot have preconditions
to love.
It's just the form of control
that a lot of men just
don't realize that they do
that damages good women.
- Well, I would love
to know more about your family.
You kind of mentioned
your siblings.
- Yeah. Okay.
Yeah, so, um,
I have a younger brother.
- Mm-hmm.
- And then I have
a younger sister.
Her name is Morgan.
She is 22, I believe, right now.
- Okay.
- And yeah, you know,
just growing up,
being the older brother,
we went through
a tough situation
when we were younger.
I mean...
My parents got divorced
when I was 13 years old.
A lot of things
kind of went through me.
I had to kind of take care of
my little brother and sister.
- Yeah, how was that?
- A lot of communication
ran through me.
- Oh, wow.
- And it forced me to grow up
really quickly
'cause I used to take pride
in them being together.
Like, I really, really enjoyed
having a family unit.
- Mm-hmm.
- And yeah, family
is super important to me.
Not only that, I mean...
And that taught me a lot
of life lessons like...
Things aren't always gonna go
as planned,
and that's okay.
And you just have to pick up
the pieces and become stronger.
So that's just a little more
insight into why I am
the way I am.
- Yeah.
- Jordan, he is so perfect.
He's exactly
what I've asked for,
and he's here for me.
He's being honest.
But the more the day
is progressing,
the more I just know that
there is something missing.
And the more I feel it,
the more I'm pushing it down.
- Yeah.
- Well, this truly means
so much to me,
that you were able
to feel comfortable enough
to share all of this with me.
- Well, thank you.
I appreciate that.
- Okay.
- Sorry, just a minute.
- You're good. You're good.
You're good.
- I feel really bad.
I'm just trying to...
I don't know.
It's hard because I don't know.
And I want to know. I don't.
- About him?
- Kind of curious,
he's been gone all day.
His bags are still here.
I guess there's a connection
between him and Rachel.
- Someone's here.
Let me get the door.
- I can't go wrong
with either lady.
I definitely want one-on-one
time with one of these girls.
Like, I wanna to take every
opportunity and try
to make these girls laugh,
try and make them smile,
try to really just stand out
from the pack.
- Hey, boys, we got a date card.
- The hard part for me
is, you know,
I want a date card
that every other guy wants.
- "Nate, meet me at my place.
Love, Gabby.
PS, bring a bathing suit."
- Good job, good job.
- It literally feels like
I just won the lottery.
Let's go. Let's go!
- You better smile.
You better be smiling, dawg.
- No, like, I'm so shocked.
I'm happy for sure.
- You better be happy.
- Yeah, I'm happy,
but I'm like, no,
I'm like, I'm legit shocked.
Like, I literally thought
my name was, like,
the last name
that was gonna be called.
But like, I'm genuinely happy,
like...
I feel like I could run
through a wall right now.
Whew.
Get to be Gabby's first date.
I just can't believe it.
This is crazy.
- How are you feeling?
- I feel really bad.
- About him?
I guess I'm just confused.
- That's okay.
- Sorry about that.
- It's okay, it's okay.
Everything okay?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Okay.
Um...
I truly could not have asked
for a better person
to spend
this incredible day with.
But...
There is just something
that is missing for me tonight.
And for that reason,
I don't want
to bring you into next week,
knowing that I don't know
if I can truly
get there with you,
and I just really want
to be honest.
And for that, I am sorry.
But for that reason,
I can't give you
this rose,
and I do truly apologize,
because you are
absolutely incredible.
I can't tell you enough.
Am I able to walk you out?
- Yeah, absolutely.
I'm so sorry.
- It's okay.
- It's okay, it's okay.
I understand. It's...
- I feel horrible.
And I also feel guilty because
this is my first one-on-one
as the Bachelorette,
and I want it
to be so perfect and it's such
an amazing night,
but there's something
I can't shake.
- One last hug.
- Of course.
- Thank you, I... it's okay.
I appreciate everything, okay?
- And I had such
an incredible day planned out
for my first one-on-one,
ending the night
with a private concert from
Ashley Cooke and Brett Young.
But it just wasn't meant to be.
- I feel a lot of pressure
as the Bachelorette.
If this first one-on-one
isn't working,
that I'm failing in the role.
It's hard
because I really want to be
the best Bachelorette
for these guys, too,
and I just don't want them
to feel like
I'm failing them either.
- Oh.
- Yo, what are they doing?
- He's holding his bag up?
- They grabbed his bags?
- I didn't ever expect
to be Bachelorette.
And so it's just hard to, like,
really feel like I deserve it
'cause I never feel like I did.
I don't want to be
Rachel the Bachelorette,
I just want to be Rachel.
- How was your night?
How, like, how are you
feeling this morning?
- Last night,
I just kind of realized,
like, I just don't see Jordan
as my future husband.
And I think
it's so hard to, like,
be really honest with yourself,
especially when Jordan
was someone
I was so excited about.
- Yeah.
- And I mean, he is great.
It's just so confusing.
- I'm actually
really scared, like...
I don't know.
- Right.
- I mean, even with Nate,
I'm, like,
super attracted to him.
I think he's really fun,
but I'm like,
what if the same thing
happens to me?
- You know that
you're attracted to Nate
and you want
to see where it goes.
Trust yourself
and be 100% honest.
- Yeah.
That's good advice.
- I just really hope that
these guys know we're, like,
taking it seriously,
'cause I'm sure
they were all shocked too.
- Yeah, that's what
I was thinking of too.
I'm like, "Damn, I bet
they know we mean business."
- Yeah.
- I was so sure that Jordan
was gonna come back.
- No, like, we all
looked over and like,
next thing we know,
his bags are gone.
So it's just like,
it was just a trip that, like,
it happened that quick.
We'll see what happens today
with Nate.
- Yeah.
- Jordan V got sent home.
I did not see that happening.
I could be in the same boat
since I'm Gabby's
first one-on-one.
You never know,
so I'm going to dig in
and just show her who I am.
And the biggest part of me
is my daughter, you know,
so I'm probably gonna share
with her that, you know,
I'm a father of the most
amazing baby girl in the world.
I miss her a lot.
I love that girl so much.
I think she understands
why I'm here,
and she's happy for me.
Oh, my gosh,
this place is so cool.
This person could be the person
I spend the rest
of my life with.
Like, I have the chance
to realize my wife today.
- Hi!
- Hey!
- How are you?
- I got you, girl.
You did... oh! Thank you.
Oh, my gosh,
it's so good to see you.
- Oh, my gosh.
You look so good.
Thank you, so do you.
Are you excited?
- I am so excited for today.
- Me too. Come in.
- Is this your place?
- Yes.
Should we get some champagne?
- Yeah, absolutely.
- Hello.
- We're gonna have some
champagne, do you want some?
- Oh, my gosh, maybe.
- Yeah!
- I guess.
What do you think
about our place?
- I love it, you know, I...
I think the favorite part
is everything, you know?
- Cheers.
- Yeah, it's my first date.
- To you.
- To us.
- Yeah.
- Watching Gabby and Nate,
you can tell
that there is a connection
and a spark,
and it's not forced at all.
Even just the way
she looks at him.
It's just completely different
than how I felt
yesterday with Jordan.
Of course, I would have
liked mine to go
that way as well, but it is
good to see that Gabby's happy.
- Thank you for coming today.
Oh, no, thank you
for inviting me.
Like, my... my heart dropped
whenever they said my name.
I kind of blacked out
for a minute.
Did you?
- I just really wanted
to make an impression
because I feel like
I do care about you
and a lot of who you are
resonates with me.
Oh, my God,
my first kiss with Gabby.
It was magical.
Like, her lips are so soft.
I... I knew she was
a good kisser, but damn.
There's our ride.
- Stop it.
- Yeah.
- Helicopter came out of
the sky and my jaw just drops,
I'm like, this is so cool.
- Oh, thank you.
- Oh, this is so cool.
This is the best day ever!
Oh, God.
- It is so beautiful.
- Oh, this is amazing.
Holy!
- Son of a gun.
- Bye.
- All right, bye, guys.
- Is he waving at us?
- I'm sorry, but not sorry.
Yeah.
- That was not fun to watch.
They're rubbin' it in our face.
Only we're having a good time.
Yeah.
- This is cool.
- Yeah.
- How are you
with roller coasters?
- I do roller coasters
just fine.
Except for being afraid.
- Except for being terrified.
- Yeah, but, like,
would rather be
on a roller coaster
than, like, skydiving.
- Oh, ten times out of ten.
Whoa!
- Whoa!
- Oh, man.
- He was doing backflips,
and we were like "Ahh!"
In the helicopter,
it seems like I can see
the entire world,
but I found myself looking
inside the cabin at the hottie
to right most of the time.
- Oh, oh!
- Oh, this is awesome.
- It really is.
Flying on the helicopter
with Nate was really romantic.
I really feel
like I'm on a first date
with the guy I'm super into.
- This is easily
the best date ever.
Yeah.
Oh, oh, wait, are we...
- Oh, are we stopping?
- Oh, we're landing
on something.
- What?
Oh, my gosh, this is awesome.
- This is our hot tub.
- Oh, my gosh,
this looks so cool.
Oh, we got champagne there too.
- Look how cute it is!
Yeah!
- Look at this.
I'll step down.
- It's the perfect size.
Oh, thank you.
Did you bring your Speedo?
- Gabby looks so good today.
I can easily say, like, I've...
I've never had
the chemistry, you know,
kick off so well, so early.
Her smile is so radiant,
and her personality
just makes it shine even more.
- How old are you?
You seem so mature.
- 33.
I'm 33.
- I've never met a mature man.
- I've never met a mature woman.
I love your voices,
I do them all the time too.
It's cool,
but no, I could just...
It's one of those things...
Like, I could sense
that you are very mature.
I know that, you know,
you're funny and goofy,
but there's a deeper side to you
that is serious
when you need to be.
- Yeah.
- You just make me
feel good around you,
and I just want to be,
like, around you more.
For a first date
to be this good,
like, it's kind
of setting the bar.
I just kind of just want
to keep getting to know her
because there's so many levels
to her that it's just beautiful.
- This has been really good.
- She just has a way of
bringing out the best in me,
and I just like
who I am around her.
And I think there's
something there,
so hopefully
tonight ends with me
getting to continue
this journey.
- Nate has been
gone a long time.
I feel like so far this date's
a little bit longer
than maybe Jordan's yesterday.
- I thought there was about
a 95% chance
Jordan came back, and he didn't.
- It was definitely
shocking that he
did not walk through that door.
- Absolutely.
- I mean, and then
now we have Nate
on his first one-on-one
with Gabby,
so it's...
- What could happen there,
and that's the thing too.
I... I in my head,
am just thinking to myself,
those bags could
honestly leave too.
- I don't...
I guess we'll uh, we'll see.
- We will see.
- Thank you.
I think today has really
showed me that
Nate has great character.
He's so easy
and fun to be around.
I don't think I've ever
dated someone quite like him.
That's sweet, thank you.
I know there's a lot more to him
and I'm just getting
the beginning.
It's just been
so fun to really, like,
peel back the layers
and get to know him.
I'm so glad that you came today.
It was just fun.
It felt like I genuinely
hung out with someone
that I've known
for longer than,
you know, three days.
- Yeah, totally.
- You know, like,
such a familiar soul,
and I think it's 'cause
we're similar in a lot of ways,
and I know we still have a lot
to get to know about each other.
But I like how this is starting.
I really do.
- Yeah.
I think immediately,
I felt something.
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Intrigue, a connection.
- It was... it was funny
whenever you were like,
we're just gonna chill
in the house because, you know,
it could have been that or
the most extravagant of dates.
Like, granted, I loved it.
- Yeah, totally.
Yeah.
I prefer the helicopter.
- Yeah.
- Oh, my God.
Oh, my goodness.
No, but there is one thing
that I do want to...
To tell you about,
so the biggest part of me
that I really haven't discussed
thus far is, I am a father,
and I have a beautiful
baby girl who is six.
- Aww.
- And she is... she is my world.
Like, a pocket of my heart
just... just burst open
the first time,
you know, she said, "Dad,"
or the first time she told me
she loved me the first time,
like, I felt her...
Her hug me, like, it's...
It's just I'm...
I'm a girl dad, 1,000%.
- You're gonna make me cry.
So sweet.
- Oh, thank you.
Please don't make me cry,
oh, my gosh.
- What's she like?
She is... she's like
the human form of coffee.
She's, um, I don't know.
She's like a little me,
for the most part.
- Aww.
- I love her a lot.
- Yeah, no, that's so sweet.
I'm actually
really close with my dad.
- Really.
- And he... just 'cause...
I think he's always
wanted to be a dad too.
- Mm-hmm.
- And I feel like sometimes,
you know,
with parents and stuff,
you feel like
you have a calling.
It was definitely his
to be a dad, and he always,
like, had a huge presence
in my life, so...
- That's amazing.
- I'm not really close
with my mom.
I think that is a lot
of the reason why I am
who I am today.
- Mm-hmm.
- But I had to be really
self-sufficient
and independent and relearn
what it was to be loved
'cause I didn't totally
get it as a child.
So for you to, like,
step up and want to give that
to your daughter is amazing,
and it's the best thing
that is ever gonna happen
to her.
When Nate told me
that he was a father,
I started to think,
"Am I there yet?
"Can I be a mother?
Is this a life I want?"
But I don't have
to make that decision
right now,
and I feel like it does
bring me closer to him,
just knowing that he
feels comfortable
telling me all of these things.
- I really do see, like,
that I can have
a potential future with you
and a potential for love.
Meeting you has been one
of the greatest days
and moments, you know,
that I could have...
- Aww.
- That I could have
gone through.
So I appreciate you.
- Oh, my gosh, thank you.
- I genuinely appreciate
who you are as a person.
- Yeah.
- I just want to say
I didn't know what to expect,
you know, bringing you here.
I had a really good feeling.
Listening to you speak
about your daughter,
watching you be able
to give this unconditional love
that's gonna go with her
forever is, like, really
the best thing I could ask for
in a partner.
Nate...
Will you accept this rose?
- Absolutely.
Perfect, just perfect.
- Giving Nate my first
one-on-one date rose,
it feels so good to be able
to let him know
that I appreciate him.
Hearing his story
about his daughter,
I know if I were to ever become
a mother, like, it would...
It would be, like,
so hard, I think,
'cause I feel like you would
just love it so much.
I think I've been
afraid to be a mom
sometimes because I think
it would hurt too bad.
- And we spin.
- Oh, can you dance actually?
- And then you are... yeah.
- Aw.
He gives me the confidence
to not be so scared.
Some people have
the ability to love greater
or maybe feel things more.
And I can just see him having
such a big capacity for love.
It's easy to see
my life with him.
He really is like
a true, true man.
- I feel like tonight, you know,
the tensions gonna be high.
- Yeah.
- A lot of people
are gonna want time,
and we'll just see how it goes.
I don't know.
It's gonna be interesting.
- If you had a choice,
who would you
want to talk to first?
- I'm not leaning
towards one or the other.
So you know, we'll see
what happens, I don't know.
- Yeah.
- Really waking up
this morning is...
Is there's a lot on my mind.
Tonight's the cocktail party.
You know, we started the week
off really, really good
until Jordan had
his one-on-one date
with Rachel,
and he ain't come back.
You know, so it left some
questions in the air.
For me, I'm just, you know,
really trying to understand
how this whole ceremony
can work tonight.
That's really gonna be
a big game changer.
- I'm a little scared, I'll be
honest, I'm a little scared.
- The way that this Rose
Ceremony is gonna work
with two Bachelorettes
is one of the biggest things
on everybody's mind
in the house.
We're not sure if each
Gabby and Rachel are gonna
hand out a certain
amount of roses.
If they're collectively
gonna give one rose
to one person.
Decisions are gonna be made,
tough decisions.
But it's up to Gabby and Rachel
and whatever they decide to do.
- Hello, you two.
- Hi, Jesse.
- How's it going?
- Good, how are you?
- You both look fantastic.
- Thank you.
- So fill me in,
tell me about the week.
How'd it go?
- It was pretty crazy.
- It was.
We each had a one-on-one.
- Yes.
- So we had
different experiences...
- Mm-hmm.
- Which is, I feel like,
gonna be normal moving forward.
- Yeah.
- How hard was it to juggle
all those men together?
- It makes it easier
to have her with me, honestly.
We bounce ideas off each other
and kind of check in
with one another
throughout the night and day.
- So how do you decide
who's more into...
That part to me
seems like it would be
really, really confusing.
- I think it's a little
too early.
- Yeah.
- I think there will be
a natural time
when it splits off...
- Mm-hmm.
- But it's still so early.
- All right.
Because you canceled
the first Rose Ceremony,
there are 28 guys in there.
As always, I'm here for you.
If you need anything,
the night is yours.
Go on in,
have fun, and good luck.
- Ah!
- Let's do it.
- See you guys.
- Thanks, Jesse.
I'm very excited to go into
the cocktail party tonight,
but I definitely had
a more rocky start to the week.
I definitely thought at this
point I would have more guys
I was extremely ready
to further a connection with,
and right now, I'm at
square one with a lot of them.
What if they don't like me?
If these guys
don't step it up for me,
maybe I'm gonna get
to the point where
it just doesn't work out.
- I think... I mean,
I think the most exciting part
about tonight is,
we're finally gonna get
some clarity and validation.
Like that's really
when this journey starts.
- Thank you.
We just wanted
to welcome you guys tonight.
Thank you so much
for an incredible week.
As you guys know,
I sent Jordan home
during our one-on-one this week,
which was not an easy decision
for me,
but I want to use this
as a lesson to everyone
that one conversation
can truly change everything.
- I'm actually
really proud of Rachel.
We're gonna have
to make these hard decisions.
It might seem like we have
a lot of time now, but things
do move pretty fast
around here, and we want to be
able to foster the connections
that we do feel like we have.
- Absolutely,
so cheers to a great night.
- Yay!
- Cheers!
- You know, guys are
starting to name drop
and be like, "Oh, I'm team
Gabby, I'm team Rachel."
You know, I got a chance
to connect with Gabby and was
fortunate enough to get
the First Impression Rose.
I don't want to neglect
the significance of that.
But at the same time,
if there was any time
to get to know, you know,
Rachel, it's now.
What's up, Gabby?
What's up, Rachel?
I appreciate your time.
- Yes, absolutely.
- We honestly haven't
had a chance to connect.
- I was gonna say...
I was looking forward to it.
- I was excited about
the Chicago vibe,
so I was just like...
- Cups.
- I met Gabby, I was like,
let me talk to Rachel.
- I'm glad.
No, I'm glad you pulled me.
- So, as a career, you know,
I'm a personal trainer,
and so I want
to take you
through a mini workout.
- Yes, please.
- Where you are not
gonna be doing much...
- Okay.
- But I'm gonna be
supporting you...
- Okay.
- Because a part of being
together is supporting
each other.
Okay, so follow me.
- Are we gonna go?
- Yeah, we're gonna come
right here.
- Okay. I'm ready.
I definitely was interested
in Mario night one,
but I am thinking about Gabby.
Because he's her
First Impression Rose,
it's a big deal.
- I just want you
to stand right here, okay?
I want you to face this way.
Okay, keep turning,
keep turning, keep turning.
Okay, I want you to be
right here,
and I'm gonna pick you up.
Beautiful, and we're gonna do...
We're gonna move forward here.
All right, and I'm gonna do
three squats with you.
Okay, you ready? Here we go.
- When I saw Nate
on the helicopter last...
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Yesterday, when I saw Nate
on the helicopter yesterday
with you I was like...
- Uh-huh.
- "Oh, man, dude, that's fun."
You're good. Three.
- Oh, I'm positive.
Hey, how's your day going?
My name is Mario.
Oh, my gosh, get up.
Three, beautiful, okay.
- I do think that I could
feel something for Mario.
Like, he's very attractive
and passionate,
and he picked me up,
and I was sweating a little.
If the rest of the guys
continue to bring it,
tonight might look pretty good.
- For my job, I own a seasonal
business on a boardwalk.
- The Jersey Shore boardwalk.
- Yeah, exactly.
- Is that where you work?
- Yes. My brother...
- No way!
- My brother and I own a bunch
of the basketball games
up there, so we got 60 seconds.
- Mm.
- Whenever you're ready...
Oh, it started up.
- Oh, I only have one.
I only have one!
- How many do you have?
I was about to block you too.
No way.
- No, the Bulls
aren't very good.
- What did you just...
- I don't know what to say!
- All right, well I won
at the end of the day,
so I think I get a kiss.
- After my one-on-one
with Jordan,
it was extremely disheartening,
but then tonight,
I'm like,
so pleasantly surprised,
like, oh, my gosh, I feel,
like, really good again.
I hope that Gabby's having
as much fun as I'm having.
- Like, I am excited
to get to know you.
- Yeah.
- Like, you do seem like
a really, like, amazing person.
I thought we had, like, a...
- Do you have a mullet?
- Yes, it's...
It doesn't go anywhere.
Do you want to know
something ridiculous?
- What?
- I was gonna come in tonight,
like, I was gonna, like,
have you... be able
to cut my hair?
- No, I'm so good at it.
You should have.
You look terrible.
- These guys tonight,
they were kissing us,
they were planning out fun
games and dates and activities.
I was laughing all night.
- Uh-huh.
That's considered out,
but we made it.
Good job.
- I finally feel like
the Bachelorette tonight.
- To tonight,
first Rose Ceremony,
first actual Rose Ceremony.
- First real Rose Ceremony.
- I think we should talk about
what happened
in the house with Chris.
Um...
- Right.
- Do you feel like,
you know, one of us should
kind of bring it
to their attention?
- I mean, if we could bring her
over here and sit her down,
I 100% speak on basically
what we talked about that night.
- I just...
I think it's important
for them to know his character.
They need to know
the type of guys
who are in this house,
and they're making decisions
based off that.
- Yeah.
- What he said was,
if you made it
to Fantasy Suites,
and if you were
the third one to go...
- He would leave them.
- Well, I feel like
because of what
they went through,
I feel like I, you know...
- Well, they're
even more sensitive.
- On the situation. Yeah.
- Exactly. Right.
- They just went to the same
situation that he addressed.
- Yeah.
- Oh, yeah, they're gonna
want to know, of course.
If someone says
something about me
and then you didn't tell me,
I will actually be
more offended that
you didn't tell me.
- Hello, how are you doing?
It's nice to finally
get to talk to you.
- I know.
- Oh, you're walking? Awesome.
I love the suit.
- I have to address, you know,
what's happening in the house.
- What do you mean?
- I think whoever overheard
the conversation and doesn't
bring it to their attention
is basically
keeping secrets from their wife.
- What's going on?
- Honestly, we just wanted
to talk about Chris.
I wouldn't want you
to not know something,
so I want it to be very truthful
and allow you
to give you a situation.
- Okay.
- So Chris
was talking to a few guys
this week
about Fantasy Suites,
and his whole talk was,
"If I made it to Fantasy Suites,
"and if they had
slept with anyone,
I would walk out and leave."
- Okay.
- So I asked a simple question:
"Would you bring
this up before?"
And he couldn't
answer the question.
- So people are talking
about Fantasy Suites?
- No, not everybody.
- Who was talking about it?
- It came up.
Chris brought it up
in a conversation.
- So he's bringing it up.
- Yes. Yeah.
- I don't even know why sex
is being brought up.
- Yeah.
- I can't believe
this is happening.
When I came into this,
I didn't want to look like
a girl that just got brought
to Fantasy Suites
and, you know,
almost sexualized in a way.
To hear that being brought up
before I have a conversation
with someone is truly
almost my biggest fear.
Okay, I just do want
to thank you guys.
I'm gonna step away,
and I'm gonna talk to Gabby.
The fact that Chris is already
discussing ultimatums
to try to take control
of our journey,
it just is extremely upsetting,
and it's not how I wanted
this night to go.
Hi, sorry, Justin.
- Oh, hi.
- Gabby, can I talk to you
for a minute?
- Yeah, oh, my gosh, yeah.
- Yeah, absolutely.
- Okay.
- Yeah, please.
- Sorry about that.
- No, please, by all means.
- Yeah, we'll go outside.
- Okay.
- Oh, my God.
- Oh, my God what?
- Yeah
- Tell me.
- I just got brought
some information from Quincey,
Jordan, and Hayden.
- Yeah.
- They brought me over,
and they told me that
Chris is, like, talking about
Fantasy Suites already.
- Ew, what is he saying
about it?
- He was basically saying
that if he was ever
in a position where he
was brought to Fantasy Suites
and we slept with someone else,
that he would leave,
but he wouldn't tell us.
- What?
- Yeah.
- I'm pretty shocked.
I haven't even had
one conversation with Chris,
so for him to already be
talking about Fantasy Suites
is... actually, it's, like,
entirely ridiculous.
- I think we do owe him
the opportunity to speak to us
if you're okay
with hearing him out.
- Yeah.
It seems very controlling,
and I think it's disrespectful
of our journey and our process.
- I feel bad that we had
to address it because I saw
a look on her face
and she was just, like...
- She was like, what the hell?
- She was disgusted.
- 100%, she felt
extremely disrespected.
- Oh, yo, bro, leave them.
Bro, leave them.
- Oh, good. Thank God.
- Hi.
Chris, can we speak with you?
- Yeah, I'd like to.
- If you'd like to come with us.
- Yeah.
This is about to everything up.
- No joke.
- Nice to finally meet you.
- So do you feel like
it's appropriate to be talking
about Fantasy Suites this early?
- Yeah, so I sat down
with the guys the other day,
and Fantasy Suites
was a conversation at the time.
You guys maybe had
some questions about it?
- I don't think
we have questions.
We'd like to hear from you.
- Yeah, I think
it's an appropriate thought
because the reality is,
if I were gonna be able
to find love,
I tend to think all the way
through till the end
and then be able to work it
backwards from there.
So that would be my response.
- Okay, but I guess
the problem I have is,
they were saying that
if you were in a situation
where you were
in a Fantasy Suite,
that if Gabby or I decided
to be intimate
with someone else,
that you would just leave
and you wouldn't ever tell us
that that was
an ultimatum for you.
And I think...
- That's not... I always want in
relationships, the opportunity
for me to be able to speak
for myself first
rather than for somebody else
to tell you what my words are.
Like, my exact
verbatim wording was,
"I wouldn't want to be
in a situation
"where that person
who I was interested in
"had a sexual relationship
with somebody else,
"and then myself.
"At that situation,
"I wouldn't be
interested anymore
in continuing
the relationships."
I'm not taking away
anybody else's decision.
And that's something
that I would never want to do
to a female is take away
their decision.
- I understand that you're
thinking way far in advance,
but big picture,
this is four days in,
and your very calculated
thoughts
about Fantasy Suites
are pretty inappropriate
at this time.
- I wasn't the only person
to speak about it,
but ultimately,
the conversation is about me.
- You were willing to talk
about it at depth,
which, if you've
seen our journey...
- Yeah.
- You would know
it'd be important to us.
And would respect our place
as women...
- Yes.
- In our position
to make our own decisions,
which it seems like if we went
against something
you believed in,
you would take that time
to leave.
- I feel like I'd like
the opportunity to meet you all
individually and speak with you,
but you all don't want
that opportunity with me...
- I'm gonna stop you
right there.
I really do feel like right now,
you could take the opportunity
to maybe apologize
and own up to what happened.
But instead,
I still feel as if you're
being condescending towards us.
I feel like you're dancing
around the issue.
- I thought that I did tell you
exactly what happened.
- We can help make
this decision at this point.
I don't want anyone to be
thinking about Fantasy Suites.
It's so early.
We don't even know
if we have a connection.
- Right.
- And it sounds like you have
pretty sure thoughts on it.
So to not even put you
in that place,
I do think it would be time
for you to go.
- Okay.
- I'm gonna agree with her.
- Yeah.
- Can we walk you?
- They told Chris to leave.
- Yeah.
- Excuse me, guys.
- You can actually lead us out.
- Okay.
- They kicked him out.
- Yeah, they just went
"You can walk us out."
- All right,
so how does this work?
I literally just walk
on this direction?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
You handled that beautifully.
- I thought you did.
Oh, my God.
- That was literally disgusting.
- Yeah, and he's like,
"What do I do now?"
It's like, leave. Just go!
- Leave. You walk out.
- That was so crazy
by Chris bringing up
these things so early
and trying to, like,
control and dictate, it just
really shows that he's not
the guy for us,
and I'm happy it's over.
- Ultimately,
if we didn't address this
and somehow,
it got back to them,
they would have
walked right in here,
addressed all of us, and we all
would have felt like.
- There he is.
- Yeah.
- Friends, can I talk to you?
- Definitely, let's go.
- And Nate, can you come?
Perfect.
- Chris comes walking back in.
I was sitting back just, like,
eating popcorn, like...
- Jordan, can I borrow you?
- Yes, sir.
Sweet. Where is Hayden?
Can we grab him?
It's pretty important.
- He came back.
- Can you guys just raise
your hands who was talking
to Rachel, I thought
I just saw Rachel, like...
So was that something that
you guys asked her to do
or did she ask you guys
to come and do that?
I don't imagine
she asked you to come
and do it because
she didn't know at the time.
- We were discussing
what happened
this week,
and that was brought up.
And we felt like they need to...
They need to know what was...
- Excuse me.
- Talked about that night.
- Can we interrupt you guys?
- Yeah, you need to...
- What's going on?
Ah.
- We did ask you to leave.
- You did.
- Yeah.
- I think that's all
that needs to be said.
- Okay.
- If they asked you to leave,
just be a gentleman and go.
- All right, yes.
- Okay.
- Yeah, absolutely.
- Thank you, appreciate it.
- What Chris did does not show
any qualities
of what I want in a partner.
The fact that he just thought
he could do whatever he wants,
I don't know if it's 'cause
Gabby and I are women,
but it's our decision,
and we told you to leave.
- I'm sorry to the guys that
that took time away from,
'cause that was
kind of brought up.
- Yeah, we appreciate, like,
the compassion, though.
- Gentlemen, I'm sorry,
but it is the time
of the night,
the cocktail party is over.
We gotta get ready
for the Rose Ceremony,
and so I do have to steal
these two lovely ladies.
Ladies, after you.
- I don't feel at ease.
Everyone got
their time completely
derailed by everything
that happened.
- It's been a long night.
I didn't get a chance
to spend some time with Gabby.
I think after that
First Impression Rose,
she was like, "Hey,"
and it actually
really sucks that
it happened the night
of a Rose Ceremony.
- I didn't get a chance
to speak with Rachel,
but hopefully I made
enough of an impression to,
you know,
make it through the night.
- Chris' drama took up time
that I could have had,
and I didn't even
get to see them.
And I don't know
what's gonna happen at all.
I have no idea.
I don't want to go home tonight.
- Gentlemen, welcome
to your first Rose Ceremony.
There are a lot of you
here tonight.
27, to be exact,
so you already know
there's gonna be
a big cut tonight.
Many of you will be going home.
You're also probably
wondering how
this whole thing
is gonna work tonight
having two Bachelorettes.
Well, Rachel and Gabby,
they've both informed me
that the roses
they hand out tonight,
they're coming from both women.
It means that
both Gabby and Rachel,
they want you around.
Logan, Nate, Johnny.
You all have roses,
which means, of course,
you're all safe,
and for the rest of you,
if you do not
receive a rose tonight,
you will be leaving here
immediately.
- I'm wicked nervous.
This has never been done,
two Bachelorettes,
having so many guys,
it's... it's insane.
- I'll go get Gabby and Rachel.
- You know, Jesse said
they're gonna hand out roses
jointly together
and present a joint rose.
But I'm a one-woman type of guy,
and I want to go all in
on Rachel.
She's every guy's dream girl,
so I'm hoping that
I get a rose, but I'd like it
to be from her.
- Hi, guys.
We just wanted to say that
we had such an incredible night
with all of you,
and this decision, of course,
is not easy.
You are all incredible men,
and we had such an amazing time
getting to know you all more.
But ultimately, we just really
have to follow our hearts.
- Yeah, and we just wanted
to let you all know that
receiving a rose tonight
means that Rachel and I both
would like to invite you
into next week.
Jason.
Jason, will you accept
this rose?
- I would love to.
- Aven.
Aven, will you accept this rose?
- Of course.
- If I don't get a rose
tonight, I'll be heartbroken.
- Erich.
Erich, will you
accept this rose?
- Of course, Gabby.
- I hate that I was
in the drama about Chris
and about all
the Fantasy Suite stuff.
Other than that, like,
I didn't get any time.
I'm worried these women,
they don't know
who I am
and where I'm coming from.
- Zach.
Will you accept this rose?
- Absolutely.
- Jordan.
Jordan, will you
accept this rose?
- Absolutely.
- Quincey.
- I want a rose so badly.
I mean, just to continue this
with Rachel and Gabby
would be amazing for me.
- Michael.
- Because of Chris,
I didn't get time
with Rachel and Gabby tonight,
so I'm kind of nervous.
- Tino.
- It doesn't matter,
at the end of the day,
whether it's
from Gabby or Rachel.
I just want a chance
to fully show them
who I am as a person.
- Jacob.
Jacob, will you
accept this rose?
- Of course. Thank you.
- Tyler.
- I am all in on Rachel.
No question about it,
it's Rachel every day.
Doesn't even matter.
- Termayne.
- I'm definitely nervous
right now.
Some of the guys
that I felt like didn't have
as strong of a connection
with Gabby as I did,
you know, have gotten roses.
- Hayden.
- It makes me kind of
question, you know,
was Gabby just being nice?
Did she actually enjoy our time?
- Meatball.
- You know,
I don't know right now,
and I'm honestly
a little worried.
- Looking around me,
everyone has
a rose, it feels like,
except for me.
I was very confident coming in.
That confidence certainly
has been shot down a little.
- Spencer.
Spencer, will you
accept this rose?
- Yes, ma'am.
- It's difficult
attempting to get to know
two Bachelorettes.
Well, I had
a conversation with Rachel,
and I do think Gabby
felt a little slighted.
I know she saw me with Rachel,
and she probably
was like,
"What the hell is going on?"
- Alec.
- This evening has been
a little challenging.
I am just hoping
that my name gets called.
- Ethan.
Will you accept this rose?
- Of course I will.
- Rachel, Gabby, gentlemen.
It's the final rose tonight.
When you ladies are ready.
- Mario.
Mario, will you
accept this rose?
- Yes.
- Gentlemen, I'm sorry.
If you did not receive a rose,
please take a moment,
say your goodbyes.
- Bye, thank you.
- Giving me time,
I appreciate that.
- Bye, John.
- That whole thing was tough.
- Pleasure meeting you.
- You too.
It was nice meeting you.
- It was an extremely
wild ride, and I didn't know
that I would be able
to have these strong feelings
in this short amount of time.
So that completely
blindsided me.
Gabby, thank you so much.
- Thank you. You too.
- It was so nice to meet you.
You be happy, okay?
- Wonderful, thank you.
- Rachel, nice to meet you.
- It was so nice to meet you.
- Have so much fun, go be happy.
- Thank you.
Thank you for everything.
- You think you know
how you're gonna feel,
and then saying bye to two
beautiful, amazing women.
It's almost like
it's over before it started.
- So I know these nights
can be very long,
but you guys truly all made it
so worth it, and you were able
to really have our backs today
and pick us up.
I do think
my person could be here.
I feel noticed and supported
by all of these guys,
which is the only thing
I can ask for,
so it has been
an incredible night.
- We really do
appreciate you all so much,
and we're excited
to see what's to come.
So cheers.
- Cheers through pushing
a super tough night.
You know, I was the last
to get called.
It was
a nerve-racking experience,
But I'm...
I'm happy to have a rose.
Just trying to process not only
what happened just now,
but, like, also my connection
with... with both of them.
This is actually more difficult
to navigate than I thought.
There's two Bachelorettes.
To love.
- Next week on
"The Bachelorette"...
- Bring on the men!
- Ready for my close-up.
- Gabby and I
want to feel chosen.
- Your smile melts my heart.
- Aw.
- Right now,
I feel so loved and seen.
It's really such a good feeling.
- Have you got a date for me?
- This is all about finding
love and, like, I feel like
I'm gonna remember this
for the rest of my life.
It just feels like
a really beautiful start
to what could be something
really amazing.
- If you were
the only person here,
I don't think I could
have the heart to continue.
"I don't want a woman
like you."
It hurts to hear.
- Like,
because there's two of us,
they think
they can act that way.
- I don't know if I have
the capacity to keep
doing this, like,
week after week.
- Will you accept this rose?
- Um...
- Dude, the girls
just walked out.
- My brain is spinning
right now.
- I want to know
what the hell happened.
- This whole thing
is just not working for them.
- That's bad.
- It's really bad.
- I'm leaving,
I'm literally quitting.
- And do you guys like
spaghetti and meatballs?
- We do.
- Yeah, that's one of my...
- I got a little surprise...
- Oh, my God!
- Got a little...
- Oh, my goodness!
- I'll be in the middle.
- Thank you.
- You know how I like meatballs.
I'm lucky that
I got both of you.
It's like getting
the president, I mean...
- Two of us equal the president.
I mean...
- Cheers to Meatball.
- Let's all cheers to Meatball.
And let's go.
- Cheers.
- Let's have a good night.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
- Gonna have to do that again.
So I come from a big family.
I got two brothers
and two sisters.
We all have nicknames.
My nickname is Meatball.
As I said in my entrance.
- What are their nicknames?
Sausage?
- So...
- Meatball can continue
to just pull Gabby and I
every single Rose Ceremony
and have a sit down
meal with us,
and he's going all the way.
- Gabby, can we...
Yeah.
- Oh, oh, there you go.
Wait, you guys need to kiss,
though.
- Oh!
- Sure you do.
You wish.
>>>>oakislandtk
www.opensubtitles.org